yep
you know something Cathy you've been
waiting give me a kiss
[Laughter]
Oh Oh
oh yeah giddyup
oh yeah
bitch
Oh
of your ass
so did you like it with you I always do
hey Rocky
wha - ladies want to talk to you -
ladies how many times will I tell you I
do not wish to be disturbed while I'm
here she's still okay let him come in hi
Rocky hi what's up it's a kind of tricky
subject is it Hey
we'll leave us alone okay well we want
to speak to you in private but I have no
secrets from my little dear Sara you may
speak freely you have nothing to worry
about
look at her I must admit she doesn't
look like someone who can keep her mouth
shut
oh who do you think you are wait outside
huh okay spit it out our village is not
a people some time now we've been
assaulted repeatedly by Pedro and his
band hmm what can I do for you I don't
see what you expect of me I'm sorry I
don't think I can help if you get rid of
Emperor's little pay you hear money is
not the only goal I have girls isn't it
then how about some rewarding kind
it's a deal
girl
oh yeah
Oh
tell me bitch you like it yeah
come on Suellen bakery near Boise yo
yeah
Oh
oh yeah
come here honey
yeah
we like it
[Laughter]
little slut rocky thank you what's up
glad to see you my friend brings you
here I was looking for you what I need
help I have a small job to do
these girls hired me bucks and sex and
pay for it chicks yeah enough for both
of us let's have a drink hell I not
let's go to the count about the saloon
all right
bad bears the heartbreaker up the time
so I tell you this girl is private
property you get for what boy what's it
to ya leave it hey how it's you just
like
listen it's only because you asked me to
dan I'm gonna let this one go
I appreciate that whenever someone does
me a favor you know I never forget in
that case all friend no it's okay okay
what do you say yeah all right
see ya let's go guys you're the limit
break off honey
I'm rocky how are you miss age no here I
have a proposal for you
oh yeah let's take a seat bring me a
bottle so tell me what's up
well it's a small job and I can do with
your help well he's already accepted
he'll you know they're all about it it's
a pretty good business if you agree to
join us there'll be a substantial reward
and as many women as you can handle true
you serious will of course Rick this is
a once in a lifetime
can I count you in a ride yeah scam free
my yeah what do you want well over are
you boys what you well you born to forge
on your first field sure c-elysee
you know how to use a gun to Armenia
fonder so what do you want me to do I'm
gathering a group to give Petro and his
gang a good lesson to make secure yeah
is that a problem no not for me
well then shake my hand my lady friend
and for four that's four of us ends it
him me I'm here for sons of bitches
well mister Noemi hi there I'm night sit
down come here Oh Thank You chummy
Oh
ah
that makes five of us rocky you oh whoa
Jess nice to see waters fresh pleasure
to meet you Jess fuck let's check if
your still is good with that gum oh not
bad of course oh yes I see you're still
good with that gun okay
tell me are you gonna join us on a
little job course if you have a problem
I need to know well you know you'll make
good money if you're interested come on
with us come on all right I'll be back
honey I'm gonna see how the horses are
at the stables huh hey come on let's go
no one's gonna bother us here come on
I'm not gonna bite you
yeah it's okay nothing's gonna happen to
you
calm down
that's all
haha
Oh
this waiting's driving me mad
Betty news we're waiting for him I knew
that fester does they're still in time
to quit if you want to no one wants to
quit I only said I wish this was over I
wish that too
but what else can we do we must be
patient hey someone's coming
come on Bodie he was spying on us want
me to kill him
No
let's give him an opportunity let's see
how he gets on only one of you can use
the gap move back
ready Willie to my signal
go yeah
what do you want
I have no what's ahead
yes and you want to join us yes okay
dear Willie he's one of us
how many do you think you're gonna pay
we're okay I don't know about 40 I
expect but only a few will turn up to
come for that
and what can we do wait for them in the
village over there let's do it let's go
there's not a soul in town
not even a miserable dog I don't think
they're really trust is let's check the
solute they might miss celebrating our
arrival
what about us enjoyed a drink I hope at
least the girls in there otherwise this
could turn out to be rather boring I
hope that son of a bitch turns up soon
I'm sure II won't be long
surprise is the key
surprise
precious
why don't you comfort me for a while
make my stay smoother while we wait for
better reto like the idea okay you know
what
I actually prefer brunettes to blobs
let's go out into the field no one will
interrupt us out there
it's
Oh
yeah
yeah you're acting just like a freak
though does not use different drying out
yourself
come on
Oh
Oh God
oh yeah
oh yeah oh my god uh yeah
Oh oh man yeah
you