you know something Cathy you've been
waiting give me a kiss
[Laughter]
Patchen yeah
oh yeah oh yeah giddyup oh yeah
ah
bitch
come on
of your ass
Oh
you
so did you like it with you I always do
hey Rocky
uatu ladies want to talk to you two
ladies how many times will I tell you I
do not wish to be disturbed while I'm
here she's still okay let them come in
hi Rocky hi what's up it's a kind of
tricky subject is it hey
we'll leave us alone okay well we want
to speak to you in private but I have no
secrets from my little dear Sara you may
speak freely you have nothing to worry
about
look at her I must admit she doesn't
look like someone who can keep her mouth
shut
oh who do you think you are wait outside
huh okay
spit it out our village is not a people
some time now we've been assaulted
repeatedly by Pedro and his band hmm
what can I do for you
I don't see what you expect of me I'm
sorry I don't think I can help if you
get rid of them purse will pay you here
money is not the only goal I have girls
isn't it then how about some rewarding
kind
it's a deal
girls
Oh
oh yeah
tell me bitch you like it yeah
ah swetha bakery near Boise yo
ah
Oh
oh yeah
come here honey
yeah
like it
you little slut rocky thank you what's
up glad to see you my friend brings you
here I was looking for you
what I need help I have a small job to
do these girls hired me bucks and sex
and pay for it chicks
yeah enough for both of us let's have a
drink
hell I not let's go to the camp how
about the saloon all right
ban bears the heartbreaker up two times
I'm gonna tell you this girl is private
property
you get for what boy what's it - yes
leave it there oh it's you just like
listen it's only because you asked me to
use and I'm gonna let this one go
I appreciate that whenever someone does
me a favor you know I never forget in
that case all Fred Harvey it's okay okay
what do you say yeah
all right see ya let's go guys you're
the limit right oh wait
last warning I'm Rocky how are you mate
no there I have a proposal for you
oh yeah let's take a seat bring me a
bottle so tell me what's up well it's a
small job and I can do with your help
but he's already accepted he'll you know
me all about it it's a pretty good
business if you agree to join us
there'll be a substantial reward and as
many women as you can handle
drew you serious of course Rick this is
a once in a lifetime can I count you in
all right yeah scam flying shit huh
what do you want well over hard you boys
what cheating well you born to Fotolia
first field sure see jealousy
you know how to use a gun trawl mean you
fondue so what do you want me to do I'm
gathering a group to give Petro and his
gang a good lesson Dmytryk you yeah is
that a problem no not for me
well then shake my hand my lady friend
and for four that's four of us ends it
him me and him four sons of bitches
well mr. Noemi hi there sit down come
here oh thank you coming
Oh
and
ah
Oh
that makes five of us better than
nothing
rocky you oh whoa Jess
nice to see Rogers French welcome meet
you Jess
fuck let's check if you're still is good
with that gun Oh
not bad of course oh yes I see you're
still good with that gun okay
tell me are you gonna join us on a
little joke or if you have a problem I
want to know well you know you'll make
good money if you're interested come on
with us come on all right I'll be back
honey I'm gonna see how the horses are
at the stables huh hey come on let's go
no one's gonna bother us here come on
I'm not gonna fight you know down there
that's it yeah come on it's okay
nothing's gonna happen to you
calm down don't worry
I'll get my pencil
haha
Oh
ah
this Wheaton's driving me mad baby news
we're waiting for him I knew that fester
does they're still in time to quit if
you want to no one wants to quit I only
said I wish this was over I wish that
too but what else can we do we must be
patient hey someone's coming
come on boobie he was spying on us one
would kill no
let's give him an opportunity let's see
how he gets on only one of you can use
the gun
move back
ready Willie to my signal
go
what do you want
I have no what's ahead
yes and you want to join yes okay
dear Willie he's one of us
how many do you think you're gonna pay
we're okay I don't know about 40 I
expect but only a few will turn up come
for that
what can we do wait for them in the
village over there let's do it let's go
ah
what
there's not a soul in town
not even a miserable dog I don't think
they really trust is let's check the
salute they might be celebrating our
arrival
what about us enjoyed a drink I hope at
least the girls in there otherwise this
could turn out to be rather boring I
hope that son of a bitch turns up soon
I'm sure II won't be long
surprise is the key
surprise
precious
why don't you comfort me for a while
make my stay smooth ER while we wait for
Federico like the idea company yeah
okay you know what
I actually prefer brunettes to blobs
let's go out into the field no one will
interrupt us out there
it's fantastic
oh yeah
Oh
yeah
yeah you're acting just like every girl
does not use different dry mouth just
says come on
Oh
Oh God
yeah
oh yeah
Oh
ah
oh yeah oh my god uh yeah
oh man yeah
yeah yeah
and