More subtitles:
https://av-subs.alwaysdata.net/
https://chomikuj.pl/swierszczyk_69
Author: Świerszczyk69
DIGITAL PLAYGROUND
PRESENTS:
== Feedback and corrections ==
== are welcome! ==
ANCHORWOMAN
A XXX PARODY
1975, Los Angeles
Well, pretty lady...
...looks like you've got all the...
...proper qualifications for the job.
- So, only one problem.
- What's that?
You're a woman.
Yeah we've never had a...
...female anchor here at channel 6 news...
I don't think now is the time to start.
I'm a lot more than a woman,
I'm a journalist...
...and times are changing, Ned,
and channel 6 needs to change with them.
Look...
I'm familiar with what happened down in San Diego.
But up here, it's a different market.
In our viewers are used to us delivering a solid product.
What does that mean?
Look...
I'm sorry you know there's nothing I can do for you at this time
You know, it's a shame too because,
you know...
You're... you're... your beautiful women, you know.
Remind me a lot of an ex-girlfriend of mine in college and...
She was a dreamer.
I'm not leaving until you give me one good reason
as to why i can't deliver the news as well as a man.
I give you two:
Those juicy and melons are flying out of your...
...bra right there.
I mean...
God!
How is anybody supposed to concentrate...
...watching the news when you got sweet puppies just...
...in their face.
You mean these titties?
Sweet baby Jesus, those things are nice.
Well, I'm glad you're enjoying the view.
A powerful man like yourself, should have the best seat in the house.
Uh... What were we talking about?
I think you were saying, how channel 6 news...
...was finally ready to bring on their first female anchor isn't that right?
well, I, you know, I mean, we haven't talked about adding
...a little diversity to the station...
But you know, I mean...
I can get a lot of trouble and hot water over it, I mean, searing....
is there anything else, maybe, you could do to convince me?
Well
How about you put me on for 1 week during prime time?
I'll make your ratings go up and I'll also give you the best fuck of your life
Alright
One week, but...
Don't get all upset when you fail and I have to...
fire you and all that stuff, I know how emotional you brat can get
You have to promise me...
...if the ratings go up...
you'll keep me on during prime time
Allright, it's a deal
I mean you literally got me by the balls right now
but, I can get catch hell for this,
I mean
The owner as far he's concerned women belong in the kitchen
I was the one responsible for hire all most of the... you know...
female employees here
Well
I promise you, that thinking progressively has its benefits and you won't regret it
Oh god
Here's the progressive thinking
- Oh my good, you want me to come?
- Yeah I do.
You wanna come on my pretty face?
This just in breaking news so hot
it will literally melt your television set.
so I hope you have two television sets
I'm Don Merlot,
and tonight I'm going to take you
inside to the dragon.
A topic so shrouded in mystery
That I am the only man on this planet, who can tell it properly
Now I know most of my viewers at home
- Who's he talking to? There's someone else?
- Quiet, quiet. Professional speaking here.
I know most of my viewers at home
thinking that what they're about to see is going to be
awesome and mind-blowing. And it is.
but let me assure you I'm a professional journalist so it is my duty to warn you
the images that you're about to see
are sexually graphic in nature
and disgusting
and possibly racist
as I'm a
46 year old white man with a young Asian woman
So...
God Bless America
and buy savings bonds.
Well my Lady,
I have to say it was quite fun
but
i have to
- ...go.
- Where are you going, Don?
well...
in the real world,
I do something very special:
I deliver the news to millions of people each night.
I am the voice of trust and reason
I am...
...Don Merlot.
I'm gonna use your jacuzzi to wash, before I leave
so, don't lock up behind you.
Can I just say what an honor it is to work with you on the news tonight.
Hmm don't get used to it, sister
One slip-up and you'll be on that fantastic ass looking for a man.
take care of you.
What did you just say?
Oh you heard me sugar tits, this is a man's job.
You think having a fantastic rack qualifies you to read the news?
Next week you'll be filing unemployment.
It's Channel 6 News
with your beloved, award-winning anchor, Don Merlot.
Good evening,  this is 6 o'clock news
- I'm Don Merlot
- And I'm Angela Fontana.
and keeping up with the stories are developing tonight in your world
a South Bay Area man is intensive care after being
bumped by two sea lions at a local
taco gym parking lot. On the story as it develops.
Ass, cash or grass?
As Americans are panicking over the most recent gas crisis in America
we give you great alternatives for transportation.
And could the lights in the produce section of your local grocery store be giving you brain cancer?
We'll have the answer at the end of the show, but first let's check in with our men on the field.
I'm Ryan Shasta. Pickup lines, do they work?
Been out here, the most popular jogging spot, after hours trying out new ones,
and I'm fairly certain I've narrowed it down to 10
watch I try them out
It says here you're a cheap.
or a dirty butthole, who likes to handjob in bus station.
Well you smell like dirty balls and red-hot.
That's actually my new cologne is called to 2-1 nights. It's an aphrodisiac. They actually put Spanish fly in it.
Are you feeling it?
Pretty soon, you're gonna be begging to gobble mine up.
You know I can give you a pearl necklace to go through those cheap earrings.
As tempting as that sounds, I would rather blow a homeless man, and put that shriveled-up dick in my mouth.
That's kinky, I would actually pay this. No joke.
This is a disaster. What are you thinking?
You said we need a gimmick to pique your interest.
Besides she's got great tits. I mean,
she's good I can.
What I meant, was like: get somebody
who was like a trained monkey
who could read their headlines. Not put some woman on the news.
How is this any different?
I hope you know what you're doing.
Ok, I gotta go take my heart medicine. My pressure is through the roof.
I anything should go wrong,
you'll be out on your ass.
Hey pretty lady,
what's your favorite number?
Oh wait, might 69, get it?
I love to get back. You know what I mean.
***
You're funny. What's your name?
My name's Jack Me-Off. I mean, Jack Hawk.
Want to see it?
That's hilarious.
- I think we should go out
- Sure
Nailed it. For Channel 6 news, I'm Ryan Shasta. Back to you Don.
Compelling stuff.
Now over to the weather.
Thanks Don.
I'm Rick Stormwatch, with your official local updates.
Prepare to see temperatures in the mid-80s throughout the week,
With some chilly overnight lows dipping down into the low 70s. 71 to be exact.
Back to you guys.
Any suggestions as to what the viewer should wear this week?
Well Angela, if they look anything like you...
...less is better!
Good one, Rick!
Let's head over to make burgers sports desk and check in with Jack.
What now is the point of having ***?
You take the top teams from the National League, you're playing against the top teams from the American League, and that's it.
But instead you let those damn gay babe greasy pricks into this league, they steal the whole fucking thing.
And I'm the one that gets dejected from the third base, ***.
You son of a bitch, it's not fucking over.
It's not fucking over, you hear me you son of a bitch?
Okay, okay,
another fascinating look at the world of family friendly sports,
with Tiger Jack.
Good work, Jack.
So we are all loaded up?
No.
No, thanks to you Ryan.
You know you could give a hand every once in a while?
Look, I'm the on-air talent.
There's one thing and one thing only:
I don't lift heavy objects.
This is with my unit.
And I prefer if you help me with that.
Where's the jogger you picked up earlier?
I turnt it down for you.
Now what you say? We'll go full round in that van again?
Listen.
I only jerked you off that one time, because you said my tits were giving you blue balls.
Not so we can hook up in the van every time.
Look I already know there's some raw animal magnetism at work.
Alright? Why fight it?
You told me you're going to get me in front of the camera with you,
i did this to become a reporter.
Not so I could be in command of jerking you off all the time Ryan.
Relax, cookie pussy.
Alright? I've already talked to Ned.
You done?
what did you say?
Well, I hate to break it to you but
he said there's no chicks
in the news
Then he said get your head out of your ass and threw a drink at me.
Kind of a rush.
There's a chick doing the news right now. You have to go tell them.
I will, sexy mom, alright.
But I'm gonna need more than a tug
if I'm going to war for you, my secret lover.
Fine. But you tell your friends
I'll deny it.
I can live with that. Now hop in that van. Wait, wait. In a kinkier way.
That's what I'm talking about.
(Fuck)
Technical difficulties. Please remain docile. God Bless America.
Hum, are you sure this is okay?
Oh don't you worry baby.
You just relax, I'm gonna take a look place is alright.
Just sit back.
- Yeah, alright, here we go.
- Okay.
Well, what if somebody comes in?
Doesn't matter. Doesnt' matter.
We take you on a journey, alright?
Yeah.
Interns gotta earn extra credit.
- Oh...
- That's it.
- Mustache tickles...
- A little bit?
It's a flavor saver.
What does that mean?
It means I'm going to take care of business.
- Wow
- Oh yeah.
It's business time.
A little dusty in here, but
that's why I brought my "womb-brow"
Oh my...
- Oh, your moustache you mean.
- That's it.
I get jokes.
Now that's what you've earned.
- Hey!
- What?
You don't touch these hair.
That's a golden rule on this.
Sorry, sorry.
Nobody touches that hair.
Thank you. I feel like a winner.
You have such a strong tongue.
- It's business too.
- Oh it's business.
- There we go, let's see what we got here.
- What do I have?
- America.
- I've been there.
- You're here now.
- Cool
I'm a patreon, now here's the flag.
There we go, get that flagpole up.
There we go, that's how you raise it.
- That's kind of romantic
- No, there's no romance in this
Okay, well whatever you were.
We almost went to brown town.
You're so funny, you're the funniest.
- You learned that trick?
- I don't know.
I used to be a dancer.
I thought you were. I'm gonna go to that strip club.
Oh god, you're funny, you're so funny.
***
Always ***
Yeah, you're you beautiful but I gotta get back to work.
- Ok, thank you.
- Don't flip side.
I'm signing out.
Do you have like a napkin or tissue?
IIIIIIIIIIIICIIIIIIIIIIIII
I have great news
Przyszły raporty
the reports came in and we're beating all the other stations by a whopping 50%
Daj mi to!
give me that must be fluke
To nie przypadek, wszyscy lubią Angelę.
it's not a fluke everyone loves angela they can't get enough
what turns out the light in the produce section does not give you cancer
...więc nie obawiajcie się i złapcie parę świeżych dojrzałych melonów.
so don't be afraid to grab a pair of fresh ripe melons you catch my drift Angela
Zgadza się Don.
that's right Don I've always found the best way to check your melons with to give them a gentle squeeze
with to give them a gentle squeeze
Cóż, to wszystkie wiadomości
well that's all the news we have for you tonight
Dziękujemy wszystkim za uwagę.
thanks for tuning in I'm down below reminding you to keep the class and good night
Cała przyjemność po mojej stronie.
Jesteś bezdusznym draniem Don Merlot,
you're heartless bastards Don Merlot and to think I used to look up to you
Wiesz w czym masz problem?
you know what your problem is  i'm going tell you problem is
you women
Masz mózg mniej więcej tego
you have a brain that's roughly the same size as the dinosaur
Wszyscy wiedzą,
everybody knows we domesticated the dinosaur so
and another thing to you have a vagina
and it has
...hormony, które przez nią przebiegają,
hormones running through it that make you unstable and irrational
Panie Merlot, jestem cholernie dobrą reporterką
mr below I'm a damn good female reporter and i will be respected sir
no but a cheap hooker scooter way
...do tej pracy, dobrze.
into this job okay I'm a professional you have any idea
...z jaką presją się dzisiaj mierzymy
the pressures that we face today doing the news
this is a huge responsibility
I don't even know why even bother talking news
like talking to a rock
Boże!
Wiesz, myślę że ta nowość przeminie,
you know I think the novelty will wear off and then come to it's senses
I wouldn't bet on that Don
Wygląda na to, że mamy ogromny skok oglądalności,
looks like a huge spike in ratings because Angela is here
stay
well super duper
Jeśli ktoś będzie potrzebował prowadzącego wiadomości ślubne,
I guess if anybody needs a ward wedding newscast will be in the bar after Dark
wonder
Tiger, chodź!
Tiger come on rigging it
Dobranoc śliczna.
good night slut, rear end you have theirs is it busy
wasn't gravy all over that
Zanurzył bym twarz między tymi ciasteczkami
bbury my face in between those biscuits and make you hauuu
careful sailor
I've been known to might release
what up pag
i don't know
Myślę, że jest trochę słodki,
I think it's kinda cute, in a retarded way
Widzisz,
see, it's thinking exactly that's holding us back in our careers
Jesteśmy urocze i nieszkodliwe, musimy zatrzymać mężczyzn,
we need stopping the men, is cute and harmless, if we want to break through the glass ceiling they have over us
Sama nie wiem.
i don't know we're still women right
i mean
I saw how you were looking at it when you sat Don
I saw you were fantasizing about him
you were practically drooling
Przyznaję, myślałam, że jest niesamowity,
I'll admit I thought he was super dreaming when I first started
Ale kiedy go poznałam i okazał się totalnym fiutem,
but once I met him, it was dick is, that completely went away
that's true
Ale gdybyśmy im się stawiały,
but if we held that against them, we'd never get laid
yeah right
ladies let's just put this all behind us
and go celebrate these awesome ratings
first rounds on me
lets go
good i'm morning a double
Okej, przyznaję,
okay I'll admit I've had a crush on Don Merlo for a while
but I didn't realize who is such a dick
made quite a first impression
don't let him get to you
nothing gonna truly of the station
it's no we go
You'll get used to it we all did
Kiedy mnie zatrudnili, myślałam,
when they first hired me I thought I was going to be the first female reporter on the field
but now I'm just rayan assistance
and you harasses me everyday
girl, you got it easy
Co myślicie,
what do you think, rights all the sports stats for Tigger
he's drunk all day long
and he farts,  all the f****** time
yeah Rick they let me do the weather one
and it turns out there wasn't even rolling
and that's the weekend forecast
Poczekajcie,
wait, I think there's a wrong type of the teleprompter guys
Była tam grupa Japończyków,
there was a bunch of Japanese guys, coming all over my face the background
and then the three rubbers, down me afterwards
who doesn't like a good crew khaki up
Chłopaki, myślę,
guys I think we really showed them today
- Za siłę i brak równouprawnienia.
strength and no equal rights,
as always a web
I doing with the article King down too hard
the hammer on the back ongun
Wiem, że to jedyna rzecz,
you know it's the only thing that you understand you know that right
Dajesz im palec
You give an inch, they take a  charge
Lubię dawać nowej, gorącej klaczy,
I like to give that hot new fillty in each of my balls in there too
thinking about this the wrong way
Wszystko co potrzebujesz wiedzieć to, to,
all I needs to be told if they have a pretty face
...i nazywana jest dziwką.
and tell their slut, it's been proven
- Kocham cię koleś.
- Czuję się bezpieczny w twoich ramionach
I love him and I feel safe in your arms you should  that's got
I'm very strong for a sports newscaster
- Opiekuńcza dusza
caring soul, read me a story
Myślałam o tym co powiedziałyście wcześniej o mężczyznach,
I've been thinking about what you said earlier about men being pigs with only one thing on their mind
Więc, podejdziemy do nich...
who gives a f*** about the Canadians
and let their hot rods
then worry about it
- Jakiś sport?
any sports ,curling very popular
- Tak
yeah  early
you know that was invented over and Easter Island
during Passover
Dziękuję
- Chodźcie za mną
- Nadchodzą.
act like a cured smallpox
what is this
well decided said they knew where the party was
this round's on me
as a peace offering
are you jealous
no idea
let the games begin sister
it's a peace offering from us
piece of ass i hope
are you so funny ....
ayo
are you are,
you mustache is beautiful
- Zauważyłaś?
I noticed, I think blue is your color
- Też tak myślę.
i think so too i prefer off
remember when you thought you were reading the news tonight.
there nothing but did all the scary behind you
i do
so hilarious
gets me to thinking
always want to do the newsroom
watch take your pants off
Będę to kręcić.
opens to
Dobrze
tonight's forecast
heavy boning
Niedługo nadciągną straszne chmury
nad twoją pierdoloną twarz i cycki.
Masz niezłego kutasa.
so nice cock you got it what are you going to do with it
Cóż, po pierwsze znajdę niezłą dziwkę.
well first I'm going to get this guy nice and hard I'm going to f*** you up your ass with it
...potem chcę go wyciągnąć
then I want to pull it out and smack you all over your face
Lubię kiedy mówisz tak sprośnie.
I like it when you talk dirty what else
I...
glitter jizz all over your face and titty's
Bezwartościowa, ssąca kurwa!
worthless, cum sucking whore
I'll go f*** you to your face blown off
To brzmi idealnie.
that sounds perfect I think your fans will love it
Chodź!
let me show you
giving away presents for my new back
Mam goracą kartę podarunkową dla ciebie kochanie,
I got a hot Robin gift card baby get over here
To jest takie ekscytujące.
- Robimy to w Newsroom'ie.
- Wiem, to takie niegrzeczne.
you see my warrior animal in my eyes
i'm do
what is this
an elephant
- Dokładnie
exactly. i know it
we say we ditch this popsicle stand
apartments right around the corner
Chcę zobaczyć,
I want to see what's underneath this polyester blunt
let me tell you
...po tym jak skończymy się kochać,
we get done making love they're going to add polyester to the periodic table
Chodź.
show me
Nie bedę czekał.
trigger don't wait up for me
i want
where did the bartender go
i sent him
Właściciel dał mi zapasowy komplet kluczy,
the owner gave me a spare set of keys I usually just kind of
collapsed in the basement
that's hot
I've always wanted to do it in bar
O tak?
Zrobię wszystko,
you make all of your dreams come true
yeah
mmm sounds good me
To było o wiele lepsze,
that was way better than I thought it was going to be
I know it was, you're welcome
and speaking of making dreams come true
Mam...
I am booked you a red eye tonight
Znasz tego sędziego,
you know that umpire that you wanted to be that
he's going to be at the game tomorrow in Dallas and
thought you want to give him a little visit
Dallas hold on to your cowboy hats because Vengeance Is Coming to Town
the streets are going to run red with blood tonight
Bierz ich skarbie!
so what do you think
sweet Connie Francis
you know I have to say
I totally misjudged you
Nie jesteś diabelską suką,
you're not she devil bitching about, you or your kind of like
horny prancing
Capricorn
horny and lust, like it
you have a soul of a poet
i've the cock cheer seed mess
take me to orgasm town
Oczywiście, dziewczyny z dużymi piersiami i tyłkiem,
yes, girls with big bushes and big butts  are we are going
Idziemy!
Muszę tylko powiedzieć...
really works your clouds
Jesteś cholernie niesamowita.
Jesteś moją nową, ulubioną znajomą.
Czy jest coś jeszcze,
is there anything else you want to try Angela
do you want to try something really kinky
kinky
how kinky
i'm afraid got some bad news
apparently
the video of rick
...o grożeniu naszym Żydowskim widzom,
threatening to Jews on viewers face with accidentally broadcast this morning
we've had calls from churches
I...
and one creepy fan threatening us
i'm afraid that
...że bedę musiał go wylać.
A ty...
...będziesz musiała przejąć stery i dopilnować pogody,
I'm going to have to take over and do the weather until we can get another weatherman
well I'd be honored sir
now, wher is Don
it's almost six o'clock
tried calling several times
Dzwoń dalej,
will keep calling we can't on without him
Ale kończy nam się czas,
but we're running out of time what do you want me to do
Oh...
I can't believe what I'm about to say
i mean I'd rather have my nuts
slammed in a car door thousand times
...a dopiero potem powiedzieć
then say what I'm about to say
but
- Angela, możesz być główną prowadzącą dzisiejszego wieczoru.
Angela you can have to be the lead anchor for tonight
Nie, nie, nie.
don't don't get don't get all
weird with me i can change my mind
Wporządku,
alright just for tonight
of course
don't go
guys alive
thank you good evening
Don below has the evening off
Jestem Angela Fantana,
I'm Angela Fantana and here are tonight's top stories
Hallo?
angela, it's you
they fell asleep smoking a cigarette
Nie.
Mężczyzna doznał oparzeń twarzy trzeciego stopnia,
the man suffered third-degree burns on his face and he knows but is expected to live
Obecnie znajduje się pod stałą obserwacją
he is currently on suicide watch at McGregor's General Hospital
Dodatkowo, wściekli prostestujacy
plus, angry protesters demand former Channel 6 News weatherman
Rick Storm, issue them a formal apology
you whore
Dopadnę cię!
who is doing a special perverts in the park
thanks angela
Służby parkowe i lokalne władze policji
park services and local police authorities have recently received a rush of complaints
...o ludziach uprawiających seks w furgonetce,
about people having sex in a van, in plain sight of residences
but by the time the authorities have shown up
they're no longer to be found
Dlatego dzisiaj udaliśmy się pod przykrywką,
which is why today I went undercover to uncover the pervert in the park
hej foxy lady
you ready for another shot of love
why haven't you hop on in here
- ...umieścisz...
put  oh no
Ej, czekaj, czekaj!
i'm fucking a up
Co ty robisz?
what you doing what you doin
you can't arrest me Jones goes for
this has been justice for the people
I'm Brianna on Channel 6 News
thank You Angela
To dobrze wiedzieć,
it's good to know another dangerous criminals Behind Bars
Dziękujemy Briana.
Thank You brianna stay safe out there
W Southland było gorąco,
it's been a hot one here in Southland and it's only going to get hotter
Przejdźmy do naszego stanowiska pogodowego,
let's head over to our weather desk see what's in store
thanks Angela
Tak więc,
so we set record highs for today
wwhat temperature is reached as high as the 90ss
and it's only going to get hotter as the weekend goes on
Aby uniknąć przegrzania się,
keep from overheating you have to make sure you get yourself nice and wet
they so
Dziękuję Harmony.
Thanks Harmony, it's important to stay hydrated
Przejdźmy teraz do zakątka sportowego,
lnow let's head over to make burgers Sports desk, where Lizzie is filling in
thanks Angela
The Rattlers walczyli z The Buzzards
the Rattlers took on the buzzards in the big desert Showdown
covering the spread by 10
Dając każdemy trochę więcej dodatkowych pieniędzy
giving everyone a little bit of extra drinking money for the weekend
Dobra robota chłopaki.
great job guys, way to go
and other sports news
Seattle Dogs Cleveland...
Oakland Ferndown Tampa Bay...
my uncle Louis made a pile of money on Ohio
his bookkeeper is all pretty good
Ale jeśli się spóźnisz,
but if you're late I'll break your finger
A w pozostałych wiadomościach, człowiek który wjechał dzisiaj
and in other news a man who accidentally drove on an Airport runway today
...Powiedział, że myślał,
said that he thought he could take a shortcut
Donald Ronald told the judge
that you find  short is her
currently undergoing psychological testing right now
Nie!
I dlatego słuchaj swojej żony,
and that's why you listen to your wife when she tells you to stop and ask for directions
Cóż,
well that's all the time we have for tonight
Dziękuję za uwagę.
thank you for tuning in i'm Angela Fantana
...pamiętaj, cokolwiek robisz,
remember whatever you're doing keep it sexy
look I upheld my end of the bargain
but you know, time to go back to the way things were
W porzadku?
all right you had a good run
sorry but
Ale Ned,
but Ned, the ratings are way up
Pokazałam swoje piersi w godzinie szczytu
I show my breasts on Primetime and they loved it
Posłuchajcie, nie mogę mieć, kobiet które prowadzą program z newsami.
look, I can't have a bunch of women wearing the news station, it's absurd
Dlaczego nie?
why not we did way better than the regular guys
Uspokój się księżniczko.
calm down princess I know how you girls all get when your periods all sync up
but the owner the station
...nigdy na to nie pozwoli.
would never allow it, I can hear him right now saying
over my dead body
not to fast Ned
Hej Sandra,
hey Sandra does Gary know you're here
Wiesz, jak się denerwuje,
you know how upset he gets when his dinners not ready on time
Gary's dead
Zakrztusił się hot dogiem,
he choked on a hot dog when he's watching Harmony and wet t-shirt
Widzicie, mam nadzieję
see I hope you're happy
you killed a man
Daj sobie spokój.
give it a rest ,from now on I'm in charge
Te dziewczyny nigdzie nie idą.
this girl's on going anywhere, it's time for a change
Wiem Sandra,
now Sandra I know you're upset over the passing of Gary but
how about we just go and let me do my job and now
go back to things way things always are
I don't know about you ladies
but, I've had just about enough, for one man, in a lifetime
I think it's time for change around here
Jesteś zwolniony Ned! Wynoś się stąd!
you're fired Ned go, get out get your s*** and get out of here
you know nothing
about running station
Wiesz co,
you know in fact by next week
you can be begging to have me back here
Uważaj, żeby cię drzwi nie trzasnęły w dupę,
don't let the door hit you out jackass
what about Don and his news channel 6
I'm getting rid of them as well
Wyniki potwierdzają,
ratings prove it's time for a change
from now on you
and you girls are going to be the new channel 6
how does that sound
like music to my fucking ears
Tak.
oh baby don't you stop
you're so good so good
I have no one like that before
Ryan Shasta został głównym bohaterem
ryan shasta became the host for a new late night cables series called sex on wheels
he was arrested 16 times during his first week
Tiger Jack zaczął pracować
tiger jack went on to work for a regional affiliate on their sports desk
W weekendy lubi uprawiać jogging
on the weekends he enjoys exposing himself to joggers and getting his ass beat
Co mogę Ci podać?
what can I get for you
allright
one footlong hot dog diaper  but that's ok
Dziękuję bardzo.
thank you so much. Should go nicely with these
mild temperatures were having, right, remember
cold front coming in by the end of the week so remember to pack your jackets you plan to go outt
okay thank you
Rick kupił wózek z żywnością i teraz sprzedaje słabej jakości Hot-Dogi
rick bought a food cart and now sells sells low-tier hot dogs outside of sporting events night clubs and bar mitzyahs
nothing refreshes you more than the tall warm glass
...od Don'a Merlot.
I wracamy do "Booby Talk".
we're back with booby talk
more boobs
...cyckach z Kansas.
including, Asian boobs
black boobs
Cyckach w bikini,
a nawet o Marsjańskich cyckach.
Cycki każdego typu
boobs of all types for all walks of life
don started his own show on public access called boobie talk, which became an instant hit with frat guys carnies and men still living at home with their mothers
that's what's happening in your part of the world tonight
thank you for joining us here at Channel 6 news
Gdzie wiemy, jak Ci to przekazać,
but we know how to give it to you just how you like it
and remember
keep sexy
Angeli i jej koleżanką udało się zostać numerem jeden w Ameryce.
Angela and her girls went on to be the number one news team in america, starting a trend that payed the way for other women to fuck their way to the job of their dreams
KONIEC
WYSTĄPILI:
Po więcej napisów zapraszam tutaj:
https://av-subs.alwaysdata.net/index.php
https://chomikuj.pl/swierszczyk_69