[*tapping a mic*]
Is this on?
We're recording?
Oh, okay
Hum, hi,
my name is Bob, and,
well,
this is my story
=======================
Fix or feedback: please let me know
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
Fart hole
Damn, here's a fine bitch
Oh, I'd eat your fuck pussy
Bring your pussy over here
I'll eat it right
So *** porns, what you got, what you got?
***, more?
I got it. Put those on the shelf
(Damn this girl is smoking,)
yo, this girl is ***
(Look at this)
Yo dog, would you stop talking black, man?
Yo man, I'm just keepin' it real, dawg
But you're a real white, man
Shit
Shit, all I know is
meeting this girl right here
We gonna have a date tonight
It's gonna be me, her, and
foxy-roxy right here
Yeah, I'll be looking at her,
but I'll be fucking foxy
Uh
Yo, don't you got some lotion
in the box too?
Yeah man, ***
That's gross
Hey, come on,
Give me...
Stop it
Come on
What you got?
Is that *** mother fucking *** yo?
Come on
he  genomic the
He like a 9 year old man
Is your mom that shipped it for you?
I made it
You make up a *** lotion out, dawg?
Yeah man, don't use it all
***
Why is your shirt so fucking wrinkled?
Sorry Mr John, ***
And you, quit jerking off in the back bathroom
on my cock... Uh, "clock".
"Clock"
I'm already *** in your pay
4 hours for last week
If you do it again, you're fired
(Yes, sir)
And you:
keep up the good work
[*slap*]
I would bloody beat that
motherfucker down the street
I've heard that
What do we have here?
That's nice
Why don't we uh... put that in?
Oh
Oh fuck yeah
Tell me I'm the sexiest woman in the world
Tell me I'm fucking beautiful
Oh it's so good
Fucking cock is shit(?)
I'm gorgeous? I'm gorgeous?
Fuck yeah, I'm so gorgeous
Fuck that pussy
Do you look boy?
*** like that I'm being
a filthy little whore?
Uh?
It's good. Tell me it's good
It's so fucking good
[*alarm clock*]
(A forecast plenty of sunshine)
(for today with seasonal temperatures)
(We should reach our normal high)
(of about 82 degrees by this afternoon)
(Clear skies tonight with a low near 70)
(Increasing cloudiness tomorrow sticky and humid)
(with a high of 96)
[*slap*]
[*alarm clock still ringing*]
[*alarm clock stops*]
*** ever make resolutions?
Reso- huh?
IIIIIIIIIIIIIICIIIIIIIIIIIIIII
resolution you know that shit at the
begin of the year self-improvement shit
oh yeah restitution yes what my peeps
are supposed to be getting dawg
I resolved to do more charity work man
you are
charity work shit that's it what yo
hey dude I know it's safe to say that
you've never gotten laid right course I
have you silly
well I bet my right motherfuckin
testicle that you still a virgin 44 year
old virgin me fuck you reckon I got a
roll record man oh you guys there's a
new hot waitress neighborhood I'll check
it out cheering you gonna have to wait I
want the must-see one out dataverse wait
up
another bourbon on the rocks on I'm
gonna make that to both on me you buy me
a drink just thinking about it
look buddy I don't swing that way I'll
get my own drink thank you
yo you dissing him uh what you trying to
sit I'll sort of pole smoker look bite I
don't care what you are whatever they a
tasty plate
you want you to top your buttons on that
there blouse slide your hand in there
you can keep the change
say one more inappropriate word do a
pencil dick and I'll have you thrown out
on your ass so will some of that PB and
J man squid that peanut butter and jelly
man now you're talking yeah so much for
that new year's resolution dawg
I'll try to buy that dude over there
Drake man and you thought I was a
motherfucking pole smoker hey that's a
motherfucking shit
can I get your drink order you guys
ready to eat milk I would like a passion
fruit iced tea with a sweetener on the
side and your house salad just iceberg
let us know please with Italian dressing
on the side
[Laughter]
ah
right
Oh
ah
haha
new for pussy pie
pussy huh excuse me
Popeye short he said he said Popeye I
can lose her art degrade shit dog get
over yourself
hey wait a second
she's supposed to be manning the store
who's Manning the store do you think I'm
scared of Ron I can take him down one
hand tie down my back do you know what
the difference is between X double X and
xxx now actually I don't but don't you
work here yeah that's really how my
department okay um well um don't you at
least watch them you know what I'm on
break um great II could help you though
he watches them all time um I heard you
and watch adult movies um do you know
the difference between X tell me I'm
shorty perhaps I could be of assistance
to you uh sure yo Dawg she sent up here
she's talking to me and you come in like
a bone it was don't give a fuck she was
looking at me over there man suck it
host we're not looking at you don't want
the ADA's service you want the 10 inch
servers you don't want to be pounced on
like a fucking cougar she want to be
heard on like I look like myself you're
not even a play pepper you more like the
white shadow and shit where is it well
you know what I better cut out of my
black hand man it's always about this
letter view I'm always talking the well
type of shit man I'm gonna warn this
world can a folk tale ocean kind of
bigness fuck them yeah no shit man I
can't even be leader state Hargitay
right now come y'all gotta ask like a
little dog look at you
hey get your well ass up and come out
with me come on mama it's Thursday night
and you're young and you're using Styles
are you kidding me
Styles is amazing yeah for a geriatric
hey like drop the dead guy and come out
with me as your boss I insist you can't
do that I can and I did
come on I give you ten minutes and put
something sexy on Oh everything's sex
why are you
I am where zombie night but I don't have
anything oh man I thought I thought I
told you to fucking dress nice oh shit I
did I went out and I bought this new
shirt and everything back tell doc if
you wouldn't have hung up on me I was
trying to tell you that I don't have a
bunch of nice clothes in my closet calm
down now relax
fuck enjoy yourself little bit cuz shit
listen I really appreciate you guys
inviting me out and all but I just don't
feel comfortable in a place like this
look no you ain't go nowhere
we should toast toast toast to the boys
night out boys night out yeah it's my
dog all right uh wait what is this
tequila
I can't turn why not cuz it's gonna make
my stomach upset yeah but it's gonna
make your head fucking feel
fan-fucking-tastic yo your little
wee-wee very happy can we drink now oh
don't go whoa
Oh baby come on Mike shake it shake it
come on go
go for it oh I don't like places like
this why I guess you never know until
you find out
look consider yourself a pet project of
mine there's a big smooth side he's
screaming to get out and I'm gonna free
her and this is just less than one I'm
going to show you how to own yourself
I'm sorry
well what are we own in here well it's
amateur night hon I'm gonna dance and
you're going to see the way that all
these guys are warship you mean you're
gonna get naked here takes clothes off
oh you're going to see what you've been
missing staying at home at night reading
Etha negra dog paw its Edgar Ethan style
whatever you're gonna see what owning
yourself can really do for you
well what sit up straight and take off
those damn glass well if I do that then
I could see you owning your so okay good
point contact lenses will come next
no no just say I want to tap it it I
want to tap that ass lovely he's got you
Oh God yeah get my take you're bringing
world is welcome oh yeah yeah yeah bring
it out ring it up whoa drops like
stopping trouble like a tie another
toaster
Hey ready to fight you a special task
that VIP room sweetie they're special
dance
mm-hmm Thank You hero VIP come on
no no pony good go let's go over get all
go into it all right
I know you guys can I pee route dark and
animals that have been run over on the
road if you get Nam war my grandmother
Oh
Wow
uhh
Wow see how the guys go crazy when you
own your own sexuality girl it's amazing
isn't it yeah now I want you to loosen
my top three buttons but dick I want you
to take your hair down
mm-mean and I want you to take those
glasses off I can't see can we get two
more shots of sex on the beach please
and can you bring a seat dry martini as
well it's home button
um so Hertz appeal Eureka I mean there
never had one of those did they pick one
pick one okay you're joking right
well um except in my dreams my dreams
are little not naughty just a little bit
well no a lot I'll tell you what a
little makeup on you some contact lenses
spike your confidence put you in some
sexy clothes and you'll feel it too okay
you really have never had an orgasm
before okay never shaving a little huh
you're good
and there she was my Aphrodite the girl
of my dreams god I think I'm gonna be
sick
yo dog get up man coming out tonight go
to party so he's rollin with us or we
going party she's gonna be there look
she a girl from the bar man
Aphrodite don't think about it let's go
down
sorry
tonight innocent one we're gonna go out
and we're gonna get you lead I listened
I think come on I'm going to fix you up
I'm going to just see to the nine I'm
going to make up your face in your hair
I'm gonna make you look stunning
oh I don't know it's okay you don't have
to know if I do
teamahma it's on the attitude the way
that you carry yourself is more
important than being aesthetically
beautiful you can either walk like this
okay or you can walk like this hey wait
a minute wait a minute
normal am I supposed to say to her now
what dog it's how huh
excuse us
look man you got to make her feel
uncomfortable so that you don't exactly
why would I want to make her feel
uncomfortable though it's either you or
her dog you or her
works every time I don't know if I feel
comfortable acting like that you guys
what if she's a nice girl like cool man
today dog life's a game like this two
types of party and I know this party's
the winners and then there's losers who
do you want to par you with the winners
winners
yeah well I'm not all sounds so
confusing you guys look I know what
you're talking about yo I mean take me
for instance I used to treat these
bitches all nice and shit they would
walk all over me so I pushed it up my
game and shit with now I got these
bitches beating out my head you too man
right we're kind of gonna get here man
hey dawg we late yo come on
hey bitch g2c oh you're good enough to
eat which is what I hope happens see you
tonight
damn Negro Club with that stripper - man
shut the fuck up why yeah yes
hi I'm a I'm Bob mm Bob I'm off you look
look nice tonight Bob I do don't I
you look nice too
smoking as a matter fact oh thanks um
you work it the video store right yeah
when I'm not doing better things yeah
I've had the hots for you since the
titty bar you look almost discuss the
girls that work there your it can be
feel really uncomfortable right now is
this a test because if it is I'm leavin
already you know what let me finish that
for you I hi I'm an asshole that's what
you are no wait wait wait wait were you
I'm sorry this is bad this is very bad
it's wrong I think that the guys told me
to to act this man oh I have very little
like no experience actually it does to
be honest with you hey I like you oh I
thought for you to like me that I had to
be stupid I'm stupid
we try this again
Thanks the I'm a the Bob hey a girl
supply outfit
hey shit head up on my bedroom floor
over you no more mine much they say get
the fuck out of there
really all right but we got to go to my
house I need to change of clothes
Jimmy's and some styling products
damn crazy bitch okay don't take all the
cream damn
Oh
yeah
oh do what'd you do that for the bad
advice they're screwed everything up bad
advice then I was damn good
hi I'm sorry sorry Bob I don't blame you
from hitting me
I just don't hit me so fucking hard me I
don't think you realize how strong you
are
you just can't treat women like pieces
of meat no not the ladies there are
feelings too you know they're just like
me and you how many women do you get
anyway
yeah a lot yeah a lot of one see yeah I
don't think so
otherwise you wouldn't be in the back
masturbating half the day like that all
right
hi Sonia LaHood i'ma get some I just
have a problem keeping them well maybe
if you treated him with a little more
respect you know took an interest in
things that they like where they like to
shop music they like the food to eat you
serious yeah I'm serious
maybe if you looked at a woman like she
had something more than just genitals I
mean like the teeth yeah no you know Bob
he's pretty smart for a version straight
up do man
all right thanks
here it's for you
so after that night we never left each
other's side days walks spending every
waking moment together
boom
I want to do it to it like - well sure
sure
well I mean is it's been six months and
and you're the only one I care about and
I really want you to be my first
mm eyelid I mean if there's a case yeah
I got it man let's let's do it dee da of
carnem um yeah I have
get a couple actually okay crystal like
a year supply well that that works but
it's great
mmm can we go freshen up okay yeah yeah
okay
I'll be right back okay all right all
right
I've never worn one of these before
well let me help you with that Wow
you look great but first
and down
oh gosh
Eddi
Oh
jeez
yeah
yes
now
Oh
Oh God Oh
Oh baby
right now Oh baby I'm sorry
Oh
oh my god
oh my
Oh
oh wow I need a hard now cuz it's so
good Oh
Oh
this is orders not mine
soon the end is all about finding the
right one and not just about getting
laid but connecting to someone who could
love me for me there's far more
important to experience love for the
first time it happened I found love
come to Daddy
I'm sorry are we good welcome to the
club man she's gonna be there who's she
the fag the one that's the hermaphrodite
between excuse me shorty yep perhaps
you'd like some assistance I'll hold you
oh talking to me yo go give a fuck she's
talking to you she's looking at me over
there man she wants my help
Dawg I'm sitting there trying to help
but she don't want the ten-inch service
dome for the tomorrow hahahaha I'm
jerking off to this pink color bitch
right I was wrong
kidding baby I love you my grandmother
saggy boobs shit Oh
quite first Kitty that hung itself in to
you Stuart
hey how you doing how you doing
you