don't worry dr. Harper's
more-than-capable just so scared for
George was this really necessary
absolutely without a complete identity
change your husband's life was in grave
danger we received Intel that after the
capture of Hussein an angered four
terrorist factions to put a price on his
head I understand yeah looks like he's
almost done do you want to go in and
take a peek sir how much was it what the
price I'm George's head four dollars ha
$4 ha excellent work doctor that's quite
a transformation yeah this is incredible
who is this anyway some famous porn star
Evan Stone agent Z was quite insistent
on his new face he also thought you'd
appreciate this ha holy shit what is
that a penis implant we had to special
order the extra huge size he requested
look at the size of us testicles I am
yes a curious side-effect I'm afraid
after performing a facelift as magnitude
we had so much extra skin frankly we
didn't know where else to put it so hmm
my waist he's finally got some balls and
he will be fully functional in about
three days
yeah while you're at it doc can you
laser off those stupid tattoos sure easy
enough
to
three days
you
just as we thought we were done for it
was to be the end of us there was a loud
crashing sound plane missile come first
in through the palace roof just missing
us by energies do you have any idea how
difficult is to operate a successful
mission while resting lady done what we
was wearing is inconsequential Watson
I'd have to disagree sir it's quite
difficult to outrun the hostiles at a
skirt enough Watson so there we were
battling our way through the palace
guard heavily outnumbered the bear in
mind we never expected to make it out
alive but still we battled on we fought
away for the flames and the falling
debris until we caught up with the evil
terms the same save the world from
impending doom and rescue the harem
girls quite and now our Majesty the
Queen has decided to mr. Jass and I with
the utmost honor yes we ought to be
knighted tomorrow morning
can you believe that man sir Jack's sir
what yes now if you wouldn't excuse us
ladies um we need to get our rest for
tomorrow ceremonies slipper sir thank
you wasn't are you sure we can't stay
just a bit longer perhaps we can help
you relax before the big event
yes I never made it with a night before
well technically we're not quite not yet
what sir
Oh
whoa
ah
Oh
Oh rise to the occasion
George it's after 7:00 you better be up
George if you make me late on my first
day as an agent I'll kill you myself
George George George what the fuck is
wrong with you
George you would kill me touch you're a
hostile hostile or show hostile you'll
get up
you
idiots
walk much
yeah back in the day I was was quite the
athlete it's pole vaulting or elderly
but after the sex well that's when she
actually knighted me it was question
Union speech and Z oh I have a mission
for you go down and get me a cup of
coffee
[Laughter]
I just never gets all
take these authorization forms down with
labs we can finalize testing on formula
I will take that haven't mean to have a
little chat with Amy down in the lab
happy to do it
now you remember what happened last time
we ventured down to her little stand of
iniquity I'm thinking about it your Pig
yeah it's going to be a cat bite
where are you Amy little slut
that's right you better hide I was going
to come down here kick some ass good yes
that's interesting hi you're not Amy
no ah Amy's out in the field she's
collecting samples she won't be back
until next week I'm her sister Martha
where are your pants
oh I'm working at a top-secret project
called formula 69 a formula 69 all right
you people are into some seriously kinky
shit down here mm-hmm
well you see we've managed to isolate a
pheromone that's only detectable to
females and although odorless and
colorless it induces extreme sexual
arousal and pleasurable endorphins when
inhaled thus clouding the judgment of
any female and when mixed with any
standard men's cologne it becomes an
invaluable tool to our male agents to
stracke and obtain information from
would be females acids mm-hmm God all
you freaks you the same mumbo-jumbo well
thank you for the chemistry lesson there
doctor no pant but I think I'll be going
back upstairs where the sane people work
now you don't really think that that's
gonna
uh I I didn't mean to actually lie I'm
not really into huh so tell me do you
think your wife is actually murdering a
me or just beating there beyond
recognition just a thought
flatten oh fuck oh yes I get harder
harder yeah oh that was some good shit
huh oh my god yeah make me drool fucking
lab whore
Oh
yeah yeah
yeah he's fucking me oh oh
very fucking piece of my pussy oh yeah
oh yeah oh my god Oh put your fingers my
ass we can come yes
Oh
where is everything
come on your pretty face
ah
there
Oh
fucking wet
oh me oh you're my favorite fucking
whore
Oh
fucking corner that's me
oh my god
test formula complete subject reacted
with optimal results
hmm why see she got to you too
can't believe sir let me again I told
you not to drink so much tea this
morning
puts a colorful stench God sir standing
dog poop
the shoes man just quit those shoes
hurry up in remembrance of elf given and
received and for outstanding service to
crown and country and on behalf of the
Commonwealth I hereby dub thee sir
Marcus Jack you may rise
whoa
agency agent D there's an important
satellite transmission for you in the
control room it's the president
oh go here mr. president this on I don't
get good reception in my office
ah agent Z&D I'd like to congratulate
you on the successful mission and in
capturing that really really bad guy he
was a deuce named dick and capturing
that really really bad guy Hussein
I also want to thank you on behalf of
the American public because they would
have been very sad to have been blown up
it was our pleasure sir as a personal
gesture
I would like to grant you to the use of
my really big boat and it's a fancy one
too
to celebrate your anniversary oh my god
Thank You mr. president sir look at that
yes well that's what I call a miss
oh my god can you believe it going on a
cruise on the presidents of both Pacific
huh so awesome oh my god I never get to
go anywhere
what who that well since you're an agent
now excess auditioning new assistants is
replacing me this is a top-secret
mission of the utmost importance
I need for you to take this phone answer
it whenever I call if you don't I could
be killed do you understand
is replacing me
mm okay okay do you understand I
understand what what was the question
again
okay you're perfect you're hired me me
no me no me he's talking about me okay
me okay both of you you're both hired
okay stop it
right
so you guys are Asian axes new
administrative assistants huh no silly
respect carries unbelievable
but it doesn't happen to anyone will
happen to me I must have keep rubbing it
in like that
so Jack sir Jack at your service
humph
look on the bright side it's not every
day you get into the Queen's knickers
now is it actually he wasn't wearing any
washy
come on tea biscuit and translating
dragon
agent Jackson agent Watson do you read
the stage queue please respond
this one we have just intercepted a
coded transmission seems that North
Korean leadership Hill has hit by March
1 unknown substance produced in a weapon
mo needs we are not sure but the message
lose to an impending large-scale attack
we attract a vessel transport one of the
shipments which one have file proceed
immediately we can keep air force base
your women's is ordering enroute and he
tells us waiting to further review
before your halo jump this message will
self-destruct
when they do that it's the fourth one
this week and I wanted Santos tonight
Noah Miller on the wall who's the
sexiest
any pardon
supreme commander sir your hole is here
to see you
Oh have a way to my office
yeah I saw sassy she not we just need a
stop
ah Jung ho with the pressure
sorry for the interruption commander I
was sent to informing the doctor Quan
has arrived safely and is now working on
your formula
she is guaranteeing me she'll have
results shortly extra rinse repeat
Americans keeps searching for nuclear
weapons they will never suspect this
isoh smart ideas so dr. Kwan he has
exactly 24 hours general so hyung will
be joining you to oversee completion of
the attack Oh Jung ho shall we make with
the sex
I hope oh you pretty hard to get Iraqi
I've been stretching it up and go
from now on you're going to be known as
agents T and day you know it is a
terrible thing though to think that you
may not come back from one of these
missions I'm sorry I'm okay though
because it's just something that I CIA
agents of the put up with you know we're
like a bad father
Stella thought of never and the lemon
tattoo of them all right yeah can't like
that no oh no
alright I'll hold it okay okay ladies
there's enough agent acts around and
listen if you're gonna be a team I'm
gonna see how you're going to work
together
Oh
shit
ah
Oh
it
[Laughter]
ah ah ah
the supreme commander will not be
pleased with another failure
uncouth I'm close I just single time you
are almost at a time doctor
oh I'm the captain of the captain of the
captain of the ship and the captain of
the biggest ship river sailors in the
captain of the temple of the ships of
the sea
Oh bougie bow at the Edwards
beautiful it doesn't get any better than
that
unknown I didn't think
I can't think of anything too
with me
you want to have stick with me
or do you want to have sex with the guy
that looks like Evan still
ah
Oh
hardly
big 4120 procedure
Oh
Oh baby
right there right there fucking awesome
yes
Oh
yes yes yes oh my god oh you were so
fucking
yes
Oh
what's gonna fuckin come yeah yeah fuck
Oh God Oh
are you doing
well captain you have worn me out I
think I'm gonna go have a nap before
dinner all right do that now what are
you gonna do with that this that
dangerous beef
you got to be careful there's pirates
around I'm not sayin tyrant
no they're monitoring that when I got
dis speech it's the last of them so
how's it going well I'm using satellite
imaging to look for a bunker or
warehouse but I can't find any sort of
structures especially nothing large
enough to store weapons well keep
searching all chap so Jax is going to
take her
so Jax can kiss my house this better be
good
the Supreme Commander does not write to
be interrupted during his mani-pedi the
tests have been successful the formula
yong-ho have you called to reconsider my
offer to make a sweet rough
Curro Curro hello
you
I'm so horny so horny is right ringing
gorge
that's just me on my throne our wrong
with my puppet I'm so horny I don't want
to be frank a virgin no more
there's no body for this pint-sized
dictator so I just leave and go out
I'm so horny
I wash my happy
Oh radish
Rachel saw my fall thought my fault
Rachel don't be mad don't be mad how can
I be met you just say the president yes
how exactly does one think we got anyway
I fell asleep on my rocket launcher oh
you and that fucking rocket launcher
whatever again is how the doctors were
able to fix your tiny crooked little
dick so they couldn't do anything for
your pea brain yeah that's right you
have to be the stupidest person alive
actually wait a minute no that would be
me because I married your dumb ass but
what you are definitely the worst secret
agent in history
you take that back no you pick that
backwards Oh nope fuck you George
I hate you I hate you more I hate you
forever
hey eternity times 20
I should have let you drown that's
coming from a guy in water wings you
can't even swim George
fucking idiot unbelievable
there goes my raise
I'm still not sure how you intend to get
the American public to just poison
themselves ha ha ha this is one thing no
redneck and resist this weekend they're
gonna have their silly 4th of July
they'll enjoy their last how to cook out
ha ha ha
I am sure I know I mean I her I'm in red
you said you'd call
you said you'd go to anger management
Oh
yeah
I'll be back
George always sunset
what if he doesn't come back
my husband tonight I don't wanna go
attend together oh god oh god oh god
well
here we go here we go hey big jungle big
jungle
well my rivals important in a jungle I
must live have to have food have to have
the water water
the water nice and copy Tommy nice hot
cup
[Laughter]
I'm never get out of here
and it's mine
references
well
I don't need no rituals you know that I
hate you I the king of the jungle and
the king of the waterfall
ah
chupa Divya he'll be back
ma
dart tortious idea
George George is so not funny George
you
oh that's my favorite
Jack's Rachel what what are you doing
here are you on the mission
yeah Mike
I don't know he doesn't tell me anything
oh okay
I think it's Claire let's move quick
this move here
don't likely be needing these Thanks
so you're really sir Jack's now huh I
can't believe you guys don't Knight it
oh um well one of us did things in go
quite as planned for Watson
really what happened I want to talk
about it okay but Sir Arthur keep
rubbing it in my face
there was a sensitive man there just
briefed Rachel now would you
well as you know this islands the
smallest of the group belonging to North
Korean leader jong-il now a british
intel has informed us that he has hidden
some sort of weapon here in preparing
for attack we've been using satellite
imagery to scan the terrain for any
photographic evidence of anything
man-made existing out here so we began
searching the island on for two days go
thinking perhaps jong-il had stashed the
weapons in a cave but so far we've had
no luck have you guys consider the
possibility that maybe it's underground
no money yes okay here I'll hack into
one of the u.s. heat-seeking satellite
repositioned it to scan this island see
what we can find
Wow she really did and your top secret
clearance now didn't you did you doubt
me sir Jack's never again my dear never
again look it's working good God
spin what beneath an all-time it appears
to be about a mouse round self of us oh
my god but we have to tell George George
yes where is the old shop
oh nice care very nice statues in Hoxton
Derek nice wonderful free oh look at
fire oh oh well that was painful
oh thank you oh thank you very much
I could have walked that was that rule
yeah oh whoa hey oh hey whoa time out
time out
hold on time out time out whoa secret
wedding ring I know it means something
to some people but saw the people with
me nothing but stir me
I love spray Cho whoa Rachel Rachel
loving Rachel loving Rachel whoa
something else is up - sighs Rachel
hello hello okay whoa
keep summit and stop it from getting
wood
hi I'm getting wood whoa getting wood
give you wood stop
Oh okay okay just a little bit okay just
a little all right just a little bit
back okay okay okay all right
I wouldn't want to be rude
ah fuck
Oh
ah ah oh yeah
Oh eat me up all yaki
one of the security details found an
intruder on the beach Oh woody ruminated
she escaped from a bitch shit have my
mentality bruh
George don't move slowly quite so coming
Rachel what the agent Jax meet my new
friend
Rachel Wow top-secret pheromone spray
formula 69 females find it irresistible
obviously species is not a factor
outside love it no oh so what are you
doing so time for a siesta Watson come
get up what happened
no fainted that's what happened thank
you yes
I told you once I've told you twice
that's one crafty bird come on Kraus
furball said it before
I don't get it what do you mean anyway
it's George he couldn't have gone that
far
who knows have you seen the safe he's in
look this is his floaties he couldn't
have gone far
so so what I think it is cannibals
cannibals there's cannibals here what
what does that mean for George George
number one find you prep horseshoes
check number to update my my praise page
yeah check number two II brought
something up okay check number four
father Moore original children
about to be checked
yong-ho I need you to consider my offer
we can make beautiful evil offspring
together intruders were discovered in
the island commander we'll just as
rewarding cute with your dragon faith in
your big cans go get them and it's
Twitter oh wait ah tell me Rachel I'm
sure he knew how you really felt kind of
what I'm afraid of
you see the last time I saw Stuart I hit
it with my
Oh
to George from a gentleman spy and a
great soldier well chortle Rachel many
comrades fall in the spirit it is the
nature of our business but George died
saving his country you should be very
proud
dear cute
you sound like that little insurance
lizard on the TV oh we should make out
Oh
yeah
I do love a natural woman
nazy Tiger doing fuck you doing you
touching my leg
put your right there put my user what
shut don't don't move on it don't put it
where it's worse to get fucked for yours
no let's take a quick over here you
freak
guys I think somebody's out there how do
you know I don't know I just I don't
know I can sense it
oh you can sense it can you I think my
hearty trained instincts would have
alerted me to anything is going on out
there huh don't you like that how do you
know that oh shit
you
got the big gun now
sorry I'll be over here
Oh
oh good job Woodson yes sir
things up all the other yeah
so we better get it definitely more
coming
okay so film
Alice if some of the sacrificial drums
Patrick Gill think George
wait a minute that's not George looks
like that porno shadow yes it does
what's his name Evan stone sir ah well
that might look like Evan stone but
that's my George new-and-improved and
all the right spots on my dad oh how are
we going to save them well sir Jack's
doing great instincts to know we're
going to need a distraction
what kind of distraction there's so many
of them
this is
I think I have just the thing
but Rachel what are you doing here I'm
rescuing you
now come on let's go rescue I don't need
you rescue not from someone like you
these these are my people and they they
love me unlike you right well your
people are going to eat you yeah
somebody's jealous
no you jackass
look around they're going to eat you up
there cannibal
yeah they're good
[Laughter]
yeah
ladies oh oh come on des what he's good
enough to eat it I'm not what bloody
hell with you I think we should get out
of here I'm gonna come back yes good
idea
Oh George have you heard I'm suggesting
now come quick
hey settle my scene Watson okay I think
we should split up
Watson I will head to the mainland and
take out jolly ol Rachel George you say
hello for the underground bunker corner
the sonar images directly beneath us
entrance has to be around here somewhere
Ivo Dee's waiting offshore swing it
again
yu-er and
the hell did he mean by that what I mean
what the hell do you mean by that
you were fantastic don't start with me
George I know the cannibals do to people
before they eat them that's right I
watch the Discovery Channel I know what
cannibal do before they eat there don't
worry I watch the Discovery Channel I
don't get it
Jack said the hatch was here I can't
find it
are you looking at the right place I
don't think Jax knows all what Jax is
talking about oh really
and you do let me get this straight you
who sank the president's yacht got us
stranded on an island almost got
yourself eating by cannibals well while
I think you know how to find it oh my
god honey you found it let's on what the
hatch oh yeah I found the hatch you
dipshit
look what yeah oh that ha ha ha
yeah well open it yeah all right not
like that try the handle yeah oh oh oh
go after you sir
down there down there somewhere down
there
stop it down there out there hun
what watch it just if we don't make it
out I wanna tell you I'm sorry I said I
hated you I don't hate you I'm sorry -
I'm sorry about everything I'm sorry
about ruining our anniversary you didn't
write it and hey this is its memorable
right right
I guess he's something up ahead
what are you doing
I'm gonna call headquarters they have no
idea where we are or what's going on
that's right it's where no spot
so
and
Oh
you
oh you see a news conference list Carla
what is all this talking my barbecue
sauce kind of weird Georgia the vast of
a poison has been mixing to the sauce
all other bottles of packaged ready to
be shipped the supreme commander shall
reward you for your dedication to this
cause by this time tomorrow these
bottles will be on their way to every
American grocery store
not if I can help are you go ahead make
my day would you this RV and hit me the
nose at the same time all right quick
you are but I have to know your shaman a
match right Jolin
what they I do with flying grasshopper
yeah sorry bender Messer
let's see how well you do with a broken
back
bitch aah
[Laughter]
ah
have a little fun yeah doesn't fit on it
Dadda Dadda rashida
George what are you doing I just killed
the most deadly midnight assassin ninja
Shan Master the world has ever known
he's right over there you don't have to
lie
I quit fucking around let's go fucking
manage yeah I just kiss let's go on the
chopper let's go let's go man
Edward in excuse me mr. president
there's a very important call for you on
line one
I told you I'm doing important president
stuff and I don't want to be disturbed
tell that dick to take a message okay
will there be anything else yes what's
the capital of order
uh-huh it's Tallahassee but that's Texas
sir that's Texas yeah you know your home
state yeah yeah t e X a thanks King go
but figure out a way around like God
loading the bloody entire army I'll let
it you do what take up fuck hey good
idea I'm bloody stop take out can talk
about take out how many thinking about
our stomachs it's kind of time
and do you speak English Oh serious
this blood bug no idiot its barbecue
sauce mmm
god damn it Wilma it's the third time
this week I've had to come looking for
you
and why did I fight you where did I
fight you on the other side of the other
was like god damn coconuts again I can't
take it anymore
please Wilma I'm sorry I'm sorry it
won't happen again
I'll take you to the mall I'll buy you
those shoes you always wanted well got a
couple therapy I'll do what do you think
please don't lose that I guess so a
volleyball or something like that a lot
of work shit on this island yeah let's
get out of here
what is that
take a look thank you the special
Oh complement or for mr. the Supreme Kim
Oh me
good job come on good job
my king Lisa I just check every door oh
good god honey
that's me Oh
Rachel what are you doing nice first
kill she can't but it'll cost too much
commotion we gotta rescue the Brits
ah
Oh
now that was a silent e not good god man
what are you doing don't worry sir I
know what to do muttered no what's it
fussing no no my mother thumbs up
no shit
agent e mistaken axe choppers on route
you just on the roof in half an hour
God name's max rooftop and happiness
over there
Jharna this way you go ahead have an
idea oh nothing nothing
yeah there are other ways many ways to
make you talk
No
Watson don't do it man get all yourself
and after my parents divorced I uh I
went to live in the English countryside
with my Nana she made the most run chief
crop it continues and a storm they would
die for
let's see that antique Gertrude the most
amazing
George good trouble
oh no would you man huh
crazy goes to the enemy's step what are
you training let's go y'all
no wonder they didn't make you a knight
get outta my sight
gone I'm gonna train comets with your
fucking Nana call I never wanna see your
sorry face around here again
enter who are you
hi-c temp agency send me Oh
I bring you midnight snack Oh
most excellent i starving what this is
Domitian just right uh tell you that's
right the taste of your own mess my
first kill
right well done my dear thank you
well looks like the missions completion
is dead
where's Watson don't ask who cares
well looks like the mission is complete
then I'll guess I'll be off combing
Pegasus
this is agent Jack's requesting
transport out Adonijah T what was that
about some kind of lovers quarrel right
let's get to the roof agent X should be
here any minute
yeah yeah yeah yeah well well I had in
this way Ritchie
too bad really
what then just stay up poor dumb
secretary ha I'm a double agent
no I don't believe you you are usual
Rachel good
come in headquarters SSH Knox mission
aborted
I repeat
satis who's there