[Music]
[Applause]
don't worry dr. Harper is more than
capable just so scared for George this
is really necessary absolutely without a
complete identity change your husband's
life was in grave danger we received
Intel that after the capture of Hussein
an angered four terrorist factions that
put a price on his head I understand
yeah looks like he's almost done do you
want to go in and take a peek
sir how much was it
what the price on George's head $4 ha
$4 Oh excellent work doctor that's quite
a transformation yeah this is incredible
who is this anyway some famous porn star
Evan stone agent Z was quite insistent
on his new face he also thought you'd
appreciate this huh holy shit what is
that a penis implant we had this special
order the extra huge size he requested
look at the size of us testicles oh yeah
yes a curious side-effect I'm afraid
after performing a facelift in magnitude
we had so much extra skin frankly we
didn't know where else to put it so hmm
no waste he's finally got some balls and
he will be fully functional in about
three days
yeah while you're at it doc can you
laser off those stupid tattoos sure easy
enough
three days
you
[Music]
just as we thought we were done for it
was to be the end of us there was a loud
crashing sound bang
missile come bursting through the palace
room just missing us by energies do you
have any idea how difficult is to
operate a successful mission world
resting lady garments what we was
wearing is inconsequential Watson I'd
have to disagree sir it's quite
difficult to outrun the hostiles in a
skirt enough Watson so there we were
battling our way through the palace
guard heavily outnumbered the bear in
mind we never expected to make it out
alive but still we battled on we fought
away for the flames and the falling
debris until we caught up with the evil
tariffs the same to save the world from
impending doom and rescue the harem
girls quite and now our Majesty the
Queen has decided to stage acts annoyed
with the yes we ought to be knighted
tomorrow morning can you believe that
man sir Jax
sir what yes now if you wouldn't excuse
us ladies we need to get our rest for
tomorrow ceremonies slipper sir thank
you what are you sure we can't stay just
a bit longer perhaps we can help you
relax
before the big event yes I've never made
it with a night before well technically
we're not quite know it yet what
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
occasion
George it's after 7:00 you better be up
[Music]
George if you make me late on my first
day as an agent I'll kill you myself
[Music]
George George George
what the fuck is wrong with you George
you almost killed me thought you were
hostile hostile
I'll show you hostile if you don't get
up
[Music]
idiot
what much
[Music]
yeah back in the day I was was quite the
athlete it's pole vaulting where I wear
only after the sex well that's when she
actually knighted me agency got a
mission for you go down and get me a cup
of coffee that just never gets old
take these authorization forms down to
the labs we can finalize testing on
formula 69
I will take that haven't mean to have a
little chat with Amy down in the lab
meeting to it now you remember what
happened last time you ventured down to
her little den of iniquity thinking
about it your Pig that's gonna be a
catfight
[Music]
where are you Amy little slut
that's right you better hide I was gonna
come down here kick some ass
that's interesting hi you're not Amy
no uh Amy's out in the field she's
collecting samples she won't be back
until next week I'm her sister Martha
hmm where are your pants oh I'm working
at a top-secret project called formula
69 a formula 69 right you people are
into some seriously kinky shit down here
mm-hmm
well you see we've managed to isolate a
pheromone that's only detectable to
females and although odorless and
colorless it induces extreme sexual
arousal and pleasurable endorphins when
inhaled thus clouding the judgment of
any female and when mixed with any
standard men's cologne it becomes an
invaluable tool to our male agents to
distract and obtain information from
would be females acids mm-hmm God all
you freaks the same well thank you for
the chemistry lesson there doctor no
pants but I think I'll be going back
upstairs we're the same people work now
you don't really think that that's gonna
i I didn't mean to actually I'm not
really into so tell me do you think your
wife is actually murdering a me or just
beating there beyond recognition just a
thought
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
harder oh good shit fucking whore
Oh fuckin pussy
[Music]
yeah oh my god oh but your fingers my
anthemic um yes
[Music]
Oh
fucking corner
[Music]
test formula complete
subject reacted with optimal results
[Music]
hmm
Lassie she got to you too
[Music]
[Applause]
I can't believe it sir I've gotta pee
again I told you not to drink so much
tea this morning
[Music]
what's that got awful stench God sir
stepped in dog poop lose the shoes man
just quit those shoes hurry up
in remembrance of elfs given and
received and for outstanding service to
crown and country and on behalf of the
Commonwealth I hereby dub thee sir
Marcus Jax memorize
[Music]
agency agent D there's an important
satellite transmission for you in the
control room it's the president
go ahead mr. president this on I don't
get good reception in my office ah agent
Z&D I'd like to congratulate you on the
successful mission and in capturing that
really really bad guy hey who's that
dude's name dick and capturing that
really really bad guy who's seen I also
want to thank you on behalf of the
American public because they would have
been very sad to have been blown up it
was our pleasure sir
as a personal gesture I would like to
grant you to the use of my really big
boat and it's a fancy one too
to celebrate your anniversary oh my god
Thank You mr. president sir look at that
kick that's what I call him is
[Music]
oh my god you believe it I'm going on a
cruise on the president's boat I never
get to go anywhere
what well since you're an agent now
excess auditioning new assistants is
replacing me this is a top-secret
mission of the utmost importance I need
for you to take this phone answer it
whenever I call if you don't I could be
killed do you understand
he's replacing me
okay okay do you understand I understand
what what was the question again
okay you're perfect you're hired me me
no me no me he's talking about me okay
me okay both of you you're both hired
[Applause]
stop it fine so you guys are Asian axes
new administrative assistants huh
no silly respect Harry's unbelievable
[Music]
but it didn't happen to anyone
it happen to me I must have keep rubbing
it in like that
[Music]
so Jax sir Jax at your service
come look on the bright side it's not
every day you get into the Queen's
knickers now is it actually she wasn't
wearing any was she
come on tea biscuit let's go slay some
dragons
[Music]
we're not sure
I hate when they do that that's the
fourth one this week and I wanted Santos
tonight
[Applause]
no a Miller on the wall who's the
sexiest of all
any pardon supreme commander sir the
other hole is here to see you
Oh have a way to my office
I saw sexy she not resist me this time
ah
yong-ho what the pressure sorry for the
interruption commander I was sent to
informing a dr. Kwan has arrived safely
and is now working on your formula he is
guaranteed me she'll have results
shortly excellent
repeat emergency searching for nuclear
weapons they will never suspect this I
so smart I genius tell dr. Kwan he has
exactly 24 hours general so hyung will
be joining you to oversee completion of
the attack Oh Jung ho shall we make with
the sex and hope oh you play hard-to-get
alrighty I've been stretching
[Music]
from now on you're gonna be known as
agents T and you know it is a terrible
thing though to think that you may not
come back from these missions I'm sorry
I'm okay though because it's just
something that I CIA agents of the
Broadway if you know where I know
[Music]
hold it okay okay ladies there's enough
of agent acts and listen if you're gonna
be a team we're gonna see how you're
gonna work
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
ah
the supreme commander will not be
pleased with another failure I'm close
I'm close I just need more time
you are almost out of time doctor
[Applause]
[Music]
oh I'm the captain of the captain of the
captain of the ship and the captain of
the biggest ship the river state machine
and the captain of the captain of the
ship of the sea Oh Lucy
Wow happy and rich
beautiful it doesn't get any better than
this
[Music]
I can't think of anything
with me
you want to have sex with me
or do you want to have sex with the guy
that looks like Evan stuff
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
right there right this awesome
[Applause]
[Music]
fucking yeah fuck
are you
whoa captain you have worn me out I
think I'm gonna go have a nap before
dinner all right now what are you gonna
do with that this that dangerous seas
you got to be careful there's pirates
around I'm not a pirate
no they're monitoring that when I got
this baby it's the last of them so how's
it going well I'm using satellite
imaging to look for a bunker or
warehouse but I can't find any sort of
structures especially nothing large
enough to store weapons well keep
searching old chap so Jax is gonna take
her so Jax can kiss my ass
[Music]
this better be good
the Supreme Commander does not rank to
be interrupted during his mani-pedi the
tests have been successful the formula
yong-ho have you called to reconsider my
offer to make the suite rough
[Music]
hello hello hello
I'm so horny so horny is right Ryu
gorged that's just me on my throne our
wrong with my puppet I'm so horny I
don't want to be break virgin no more
there's no body for this pint-sized
dictator so much leave
[Music]
I'm so
- ooh come on
if you want
[Music]
Rachel Sam I fall it's not my fault
Rachel don't be mad don't be mad how can
I be mad you just saved the president's
yacht I fell asleep down my rocket
launcher you and that fucking rocket
launcher what I don't get is how the
doctors were able to fix your tiny
crooked little dick they couldn't do
anything for your pea brain yeah that's
right you have to be the stupidest
person alive actually wait a minute no
that would be me because I'm married
your dumbass but what you are definitely
the worst secret agent in history you
take that back no take that back Rachel
nope fuck you George
hate you I hate you more I hate you
forever in eternity time twenty
I should have let you drown that's
coming from a guy in water wings
you can't even swim George
unbelievable there goes my raise
[Applause]
I'm still not sure how you intend to get
the American public to just poison
themselves ha ha guys how about one
thing no redneck can resist this weekend
they're gonna have their silly 4th of
July they enjoy their last hot dog
cookout I know
I am sure
I know I mean I heard I'm in red
[Music]
[Applause]
you said you'd call you should you go to
anger management
obviously you
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
Oh
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
I'll be back
George always comes back
what if he doesn't come back
wouldn't be doesn't come back
[Music]
and together
big jungle big rivals important in a
jungle I'm a survivor food tough they
have some water
[Music]
maybe some coffee
Tommy be nice right hot