[Music]
[Applause]
congratulations on my coming in agent
Reichle I knew you had a didn't you
unfortunate about your husband oh yes
well I couldn't let my feelings for
George compromise the mission
[Music]
Sorry Sorry Sorry
does your husband preciate these no
husband doesn't appreciate anything dead
Oh George never does George you couldn't
even make coffee
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
Oh fuckin secret agent it feels like
yeah you can't teach that
anymore
[Music]
[Applause]
George never makes me come
[Music]
[Applause]
hmm complete Georgia scared the crap out
of me yeah you should see it from my
point of view dream about that damn fish
tank again yeah something like that
[Music]
[Applause]
oh I have my cereal
how are you think so yeah I do you
feeling lucky
would you try to come take it
oh I will you call yourself a secret
agent
no wonder they won't give you a
promotion
[Music]
[Applause]
take it that's a no ladies first age
before beauty brains before stupidity
[Music]
what I meant was you're the stupid one
okay
[Music]
thank you like a redheaded stepchild oh
no you did
can't believe you stake my spot oh
you're dirty here 30
[Music]
hi Rachel morning Alice
I made brownies
who wants some I had to park four blocks
away well now you've had your car yo
those are the last of the brownies isn't
it I didn't even get one oh you have to
watch your girlish figure
it's not fair Rachel you know I wanted a
brownie
George life's not fair that's one hell
one hell of a good cook yeah well you
try being married to her for six years
seven I'm sorry the lack of sex is
making my memory blurry sorry you got
remove all metal from your pockets
all metal so I'm gonna have to get a
little more thorough hey Sam it's time
for a good body cavity search so there I
was surrounded by the enemy deep in the
jungles of Bolivia unarmed and then
suddenly agency yes sir you're late
yes there was a malfunction at security
pella tracer function I'll tell you what
though I've got a big mission for you
yes sir go down to the break room and
give me a cup of coffee
[Music]
you know how I like it
as I was saying bullets buzzing over my
head I had no weapon suddenly from the
canopy above came the enemy oh sorry I
didn't mean to startle you
no it's okay it's a middle of on edge
too much caffeine
well I must compliment you on your
cat-like reflexes oh yeah comes as being
a secret agent I'll have to be a little
bit more careful around you I didn't
know you could be so dangerous
yeah that's that's me dangerous you know
good who's in I have to show you why
don't you tell me
[Music]
[Applause]
what does this do Oh be careful with
that I'm having a lot of problems with
it
it contains nerve gas a mini
supercomputer complete with wireless
internet digital camera mp3 player
cigarette lighter even an am/fm radio
should I have it
No
[Music]
what's this um that's that that's my
vibrator so you're planning on doing a
little fly-fishing oh that that is my
pride and joy
it's impenetrable what
Wow grazie okay I get it
this vest is specially designed to
increase the adrenaline and testosterone
of its we're giving him more strength
endurance even enabling him to run
faster well you think he could have made
it a little bit more fashionable I mean
it looks like a fishing vest do I look
like I know anything about fashion oh no
no no you know no the vest works it's
you know it's just got lots of
convenient pockets it has an internal
cooling system that regulates body
temperature and increases stamina
imagine what that could do for unifier
the sacred I could do for me in the
bedroom I already have is my latest
invention training goggles it can create
virtually any situation imaginable from
flying it's a combat try
[Music]
that's cool you do anything anything
anything anything
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh Oh
[Music]
Oh your
oh my god
[Music]
oh yes George take it you know you've
always one of that type
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
okay that was a little weird you don't
know how long I've waited for that you
tricked me you lured me down here to
take advantage of me you you gadget
siren so oh come on you know I like you
I'm married just leave it wasn't real
felt real don't
[Music]
where have you been huh what you've been
gone over an hour X was looking for you
he was yeah he needed his coffee oh yeah
right
so so what so where were you I was
taking care of business in the lab
business huh
and was this business wearing a white
lab coat and reeking a fake designer
perfume what are you talking about don't
play stupid with me George
that little trollop Amy what about her
George I'm serious I know that you know
that she knows that we're having marital
issues
she's like a vulture waiting in the
wings you're a crazy lady I'm crazy I'm
crazy I'm not the one was provoked by a
glass of milk this morning I'm not the
one that hassled the security guards and
we won't even discuss your bouts of
mourning road rage but I did not harass
those security guards you set me up
and for your information they proceeded
to get very intimate with me I guess I
should be grateful cuz it's the closest
thing I'm head to sex in months there
you go again always with the sex we know
what George maybe if you learn a little
technique instead of humping me like a
drunken Chihuahua I would be a little
more willing to participate really yeah
really is there a problem here no sir
good Rachel I'd like to see a one place
absolutely Zee yes where's my coffee
coming up sir
[Music]
Rachel we have a seat
I am sitting sir right
Rachel I need you
excuse me your help Oh
you're the only one that I can trust I
have to go on a secret mission no one
here even knows about it I can't help it
but I have a feeling it may be my last
really sir I don't think there's any
coming back from this one kid huh don't
cry it's the terrorists the Middle
Eastern ones you know those guys mm-hmm
they've developed a plan to destroy the
world and I have to go and steal the
magic ingredients to the weapon weapons
[Music]
Rachel yes sir I need you to help me
save the world huh the whole world can
you do that can you be a hero yes sir
[Music]
good
here's what I need for you to do take
this cellphone guard it with your life
I'm going to be meeting my contacts and
they are very dangerous men and they are
going to want to know that I am who I
say I am do you understand
not really sir they're gonna take me
into custody they're gonna dial that
phone for a code if you don't give him
that code or you don't answer that phone
I'll be killed Oh doc do you understand
I think so sir protect that with your
life
from now on you shall be known as agent
D D any questions what's the code word
Cuthbert right hmm
peppermint peppermint peppermint
now go I have to prepare for this kind
of a mission but Sir please go hmm
George what what are you doing here you
go sir
you know I like two sugars
you're dismissed what's so funny you
don't actually believe that secret
mission crap do you oh my god you do
that's the oldest trick in the book he
just wants to fuck you you're jealous
jealous that I got a mission your
secretary
no one's gonna give you a mission I am
an administrative assistant but I guess
you know a thing or two about not to
getting missions now wouldn't you well
except fetching coffee now why would you
have to go there okay I was just trying
to warn he's trying to get in your pants
why he does ass what did you say I said
don't be such an ass
[Music]
what is it with you in that fish tank
anyway this is going to be the perfect
underwater ecosystem and I hope it's God
you are not right yeah well at least I'm
not winning by a phone that's never
going to ring it will ring why don't you
have a little faith that he'll
accomplish the mission you just don't
get it he's not on a secret mission
nobody knows anything about a secret
mission that's because it's secret duh
honey you know nothing of protocol you
really think he would tell his secretary
about a secret mission I am an
administrative assistant let me see if I
get this straight the story is there's a
group of terrorists and they've built a
bomb and they've threatened to blow up
the planet Earth
but alas this will be his last call of
duty and his fate rests squarely and
palms of your hands you're the only one
he can trust his last hope
blah-blah-blah-blah-blah yeah listen
that's a story he gave his last
secretary Rachel listen don't get mad
just fast because you're fighting for
Agent X and felon certificate island
getting his dick sucked leg do not make
me tell you twice in the same night
okay I am an administrative assistant
she's crazy
[Music]
she's I think I just found it when I
think of this little swine isn't it cute
beautiful it's not to say say what we
swine it's just things with epson you
know it's so much fun to say isn't it
terrific would you like this little just
wine here do you like this wine this is
like the other other pink me but how
about some white meat excuse me no no
seriously let's just take a bite
[Music]
another one for a special agent man
thank you so how do you say your name
Lamy well if you insist
yeah like I haven't heard that one beep
wait a minute you're not gay no so you
didn't know that this is a gay and
lesbian bisexual transgender luau no up
to that name you know the offer still
stands but you might want to hurry
because my country could call me into
service at any moment
as a matter of fact I'm expecting a call
from the President of the United States
there he is
yes mr. president yes sir it's me sir
that top-secret of course sir you know
you can count on me yes sir goodbye sir
so uh just um yeah everything okay
yeah ship out an hour Wow then I guess
we have better hurry
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
okay yes
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
well guess I should be going are you
okay
oh shit idiots me you don't wanna tackle
me you should have gone there my
opponent firstly it was my secret
mission but now you've upset my pristine
ecosystem did you shut up about your
ecosystem check it out here Thank You
captain obvious oh oh my god do you
think he's dead Oh
[Music]
good morning everyone
I am agent J from the Washington field
office I'm afraid I have some terrible
news one of ours is missing agent X has
disappeared all we know is he left for
an unknown destination and has not been
heard of since Friday afternoon all
communication attempts have failed and
we are forced to use all of our
resources at hands the search and rescue
[Music]
need to get yourself together they bomb
the United States Rachel listen anybody
else hear your conversation that you had
with X no okay good now we're gonna
march back in there and we're gonna act
as if we know nothing okay hey you want
to be brought up in treason charges have
you ever been to prison
okay now we're gonna go back in there
and we're gonna act as if we know
nothing until I come up with a plan you
got that shake your head yes that you
got it good now let's go Rachel
right this way yeah so this is where the
best place to catch crab is
yeah Rachel isn't it maybe may have a
word with you in private
hey you bring me a cup of coffee
so I understand that your agent ex is
secretary administrative assistant right
well since you worked so closely with
him I'm just a little curious you've you
overheard anything strange the last few
days maybe you notice anything out of
the ordinary
he didn't discuss anything with you
mentioned taking a trip think hard
[Music]
well British intelligence have informed
us of a possible terrorist threat this
is not what we need right now with our
biggest agent missing you're still
waiting for more information to come in
from the Brits I'm gonna go check on
some possible leads on agent X in the
meantime I want you to sit next to the
fax and call me the instant something
comes in I'm depending on you yes sir I
mean ma'am
yes ma'am not again
[Music]
hey hey
what are you doing still here we didn't
actually think I was gonna leave you now
did you
we have our problems and everything but
in six years of marriage if I ever let
you down
seven we've been married seven years
seven years four months two days
[Music]
no come on in here you know you don't
have to wait with me I know that
everybody's gone home for the day and I
figured keep you some company
[Music]
that feels good
what are you doing what I tell you to
troll around at a time like this
human sensitive prick what's wrong with
you
great now I'm a prick well you know what
you are a frigid bitch
fuck you no fuck you
[Music]
you can't really be serious about this
oh I'm serious George wait shouldn't we
call someone you know for backup you saw
the report there's no time the
terrorists are gonna bomb the US in a
couple of days
the British agents are already enroute
exactly why we should call for backup
why so they could pass the assignment
under somebody else so I can get
overlooked again Rachel I'm fucking
tired of getting coffee and dry-cleaning
so this is about you know maybe you
selfish jerk
I don't think risking my life for my
government is selfish it's patriotic
besides if you hadn't killed our top
operative I wouldn't be forced to do
this fine
well I'm going with you no no no you're
not
you said it yourself I'm responsible so
I'm going no way
feet on the gong telling
[Music]
fine
yes my first mission as an agent you're
not an agent you're a secretary I am an
administrative assistant
just rear that terrorist I gotta call
Washington you're not calling anyone my
dear it's me we've got a problem
[Music]
Oh like it's gonna work for you honey
you forget in addition to being able to
type 87 words a minute I can hack into
anything I'm impressed
as you should be
grab the bag oh yeah you're mine now
[Music]
George I really don't think there's
gonna be time for fishing this isn't a
fishing rest this is a hi-tech fight
enhancing super boost all right you know
you don't have to make shit up George
follow me
[Music]
that's what I'm talking about that one
of those penis extension things what
feeling a little inferior are you George
I'm surprised you even remember that I
have a penis
[Music]
touch no back away from the weaponry I
want gun no George I want a gun no how
the hell did you expect me to defend
myself satisfied you've got to be
kidding me
listen go to the house pack a few things
essentials only I'm gonna go try and
secure it right in here before something
inconspicuous try not to shoot yourself
[Music]
what is all this
essentials okay do you understand we're
going undercover yeah that's why I need
somebody to disguise this duh
okay you know fine have it your way
I don't care if I am NOT carrying its
luggage not one single piece wait
this is our conspicuous ride no one's
ever gonna guess where we're going I'm
just getting it fair fine get the bags
getting George bags there George hit the
fucking bags
[Music]
the Falcon has left the nest
the Fox is in the henhouse what the two
idiots their other radio Oh
what if it's faithful for God's sake
[Music]
okay okay here we go capital of Finland
Helsinki no no no how many times do I
have to tell you form it as a question
what is Helsinki Effendi please excuse
the introduction but the British are
coming
I know this one who is Paul Revere no no
sir
the British are coming now here English
agents they're on to us
why don't you tell me this okay
scout the area find out where the
infidels keep their camp and destroy
them
yes Effendi well my plan to take over
the world does not work I always have
plan B Plan B sir
[Music]
Oh
I like that
survey says I like
[Music]
really hot out here
she put some sunscreen on baby okay
pac-man up doing I just here durka durka
Martinez jr. are you comfy Bob
I'm your contact
I'm gonna take your base camp go get
hurry up will receive I work with you
guys an agent extra all that from the
states all the time
[Music]
[Applause]
I've located the British agents send
three men to cut them off at the pass
take no prison meet me back at the
palace
[Music]
what a shithole yes Watson I don't see
our bloody contact anywhere we're gonna
have to move fast
hostiles are everywhere we need some
transport Watson get us a ride should I
contact HQ sir nonsense we move in as
plan ah
now just get us a ride would you what
what what the bloody what the bloody has
he gone Watson what the bloody hell are
you doing over there hello there do you
speak English okay alrighty then um I
will take the brandade double mocha with
extra cream and do you have any muffins
guess not you take credit cards Watson
yes sir
what nerd are you doing having a clue
sir
it's sandbox sandbox good lord
Watson it's a goat it's indigenous
species sir
Watson yes sir where's the ride sir yes
if you look very close I don't think
there's any taxis Watson just get us our
bloody ride would you can I take my
coffee sir
no quick
got it all nuts
Lahaina Mexican nasi do not touch
[Music]
what stop wait guys my instincts they
tell me there's danger your instincts
huh I don't see anything I think your
instincts are wrong
[Music]
virgins sweetie oh my that's awesome
Oh dirty
[Music]
here we go now yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
thanks sweetie
haha this had better be good
Efendi I have located the agent south of
the palace but these are different from
the rest they want us to know they are
here it's like they are taunting us and
I think they have the American agent
with them only he would be so bold I
think his name is X hold on a second
agent X is here and you're sure he took
out some of our best men it's got to be
him but we've captured a prisoner find
Abdul tell him to double the guard watch
and get out there I want to know
everything they're doing they take a
shit I want to know about it okay if we
take a crap I don't need to know about
that but anything else I want to know
about you understand and you interrogate
the prisoner okay yes
[Music]
this room is very beautiful it most
certainly is but not as beautiful as you
your beauty is as expansive as the
desert
you are like an oasis Oh
me
[Music]
do not fear my power
what
oh the maid must have left this never
mind
oh look into my eyes
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
ha
[Music]
Oh
oh geez
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
hey I want to hit her
I'm sick of eating my own
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
a dual I've written all over the powers
for you what are you doing in my room
and what is Teddy doing on the floor
Oh hmm
let me explain explain what that you
have one of Hussein's concubines in my
bed if he finds out I'll cut off both
our balls I will not tell you know what
begone with yourself be out of here
before someone sees you I should kick
your ass but I have no time the same
needs us dress quickly huh wait a minute
some of my cases are missing
and where's Muffy has anybody seen Muffy
what's a Muffy nothing's my baby we have
to go find Muffy Rachel get ahold of
yourself we cannot go back all right
there's no way she'd survive the heat of
the desert it's a casualty of war hey
look is this your shoe bag these are the
new summer collection see see how easily
she forgot about Muffy you know that
could be me out there and that you'd
know the difference the merge six years
seven seven years seven long years
[Music]
what's up this is not what I had in mind
you've been on that dancing all night
sir surely it's my turn to ride soon
Watson soon remember those hostiles
everywhere I must keep a lookout oh I
think I see something in the distance
where look a light southeast of our
position possibly my lens what do you
see what is it
[Music]
don't quite know Watson I can't make it
out good god I think that he's gotten to
me man
[Music]
[Applause]
it's really tight hold on
[Music]
stop identify yourself agent Jackson
Watson British intelligence now where
the hell were you today
you could have cost us the mission man
what I made my pickup I to understand
what the agents are yeah who the hell am
i you what oh I like your camel are you
guys on a mission to identify yourself
rankin agency field agent Z had a
command a CIA you liar
I'm sorry this is my husband George he
watches the mission files in our
building and I am the directors
administrative assistant Rachel you guys
must be the British fellows who sent me
the facts pleased to meet you boss good
god what are you both doing here this is
a Code Red top-secret mission no
sightseeing tour okay we'll take it from
here you two back in the camp while
we'll do recon of the area and own 500
hours okay yes stay close to your tents
oh and don't get in our way
hey I think we can be of service yeah
yes I think you might very good man ago
Russ me up a nice cup of tea
well the poached honey your reputation
precedes you
shut up Rachel so not really gonna stay
in our tent to let them have all the fun
are we yeah those limey bastards who
they think they are secret agents or
something they are oh I have an idea you
know what we should do we should get
that nerve gas but you had and put it in
their tent and then after they're asleep
we can go to the palace is still the map
to the warehouse that's a great idea why
do I have to go gas him in the tent I
thought you were the leader and if I was
leader that's what I would do yes of
course I knew that I was just testing
you and you did well I'm gonna go
prepare the equipment
[Music]
who do you work for tell me who sent you
where is the camp your silence only
anglish me oh look at the will dog
little dog
don't leave the prisoner with me thank
you
dismissed look at the will puppy wuppy
you're so sweet I think I'll name you
jihad wanna dance so that's the way
uh-huh uh-huh
which Ted do you think they're in I
think it's that one that one what the
Union Jack yeah that's a good good guess
[Music]
[Applause]
guys remember the only way inside the
palace office without setting off the
alarm is gonna be through the roof once
you're inside the map it's gonna be
inside the desk
[Music]
front door it's a lot I'm gonna find the
office right away
[Music]
that was amazing
did you forget how flexible my body is
well considering the fact that you never
let me see it anymore I've forgotten
quite a few things about your body not
now George really
[Music]
oh yeah what's an eyeful of my head's
been bashed in I think it was this uh
those damned Americans they're gonna get
us killed Watson I think they're Cowboys
or something
too much television I'd say
what the hell's you thinking you're
gonna get us all killed this is a game
you do anything like that again I know
your what I'll be forced to kill you I
would like to see you try that smarts
doesn't it oh you gotta watch her with
that she's like a ninja
Oh anything you'd like to add
we got the map here what done
so we're team now right you want our
help you want our help
good say it say it yes yes we need your
help
oh and I also got you this on here
you'll find all the reconnaissance
photos to get you safely into the house
excellent work my dear what the hell
happened to you man oh well I had to
take out a couple guards too in fact I
killed them with my bare hands I got rid
of the bodies that I dragged them far
away they'll never be found so you know
you don't have to worry won't come back
on you yes quite the hero he was oh good
job man I was wrong about you I thought
you were just a pen butcher well we got
lots of training to do we have to go
over the Intel reports that Rachel
gather Poulsen oh that's one crafty bird
Elton I should say nice
okay
no okay oh yeah broke up T
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
I'm okay
[Applause]
[Music]
okay now listen up
me and Watson to take out the palace
guards here and here moving forward to
the throne room and take our Husein
Rachel George Tate Bob's Jeep go to the
warehouse go to the warehouse and disarm
the weapon by removing the uranium
warhead now don't mess this up
is everyone clear yes sir good Watson
what are you doing something to remember
our trip together good god man this is
not a bloody lads holiday this is a
mission now move out that's it cheap
it's almost paying off
[Music]
we have the admin supports on this idea
we don't going guns blazing
so they have your silencer and fight
then you go up one and give anyone you
come across yeah crystal follow me
[Music]
oh my god I've died and gone to heaven
don't worry I'll take care of this are
you doing man
never good your training hostile sir
your anyone I see it's them or me that's
what you've said
goodness me if you forgot what is to be
a British agent fine country sir but no
no no to be licensed to kill a license
to fuck the finest women the world has
to offer ours this is not the time to
kill no no no this is time to
[Music]
what's he doing in these chambers it is
forbidden scream I just know it
don't worry we would not alert the
guards to the presence of our rescuers
rescues you are here to rescue us aren't
you
of course we are yes yes we're here to
rescue were just glad you're all in one
piece we have not seen men like you
before we only see one man oh that's
nice I guess
nice have you seen him holy jesus oh
nasty you see well yes I do
oh well we must be off we're gonna clear
the palace to rescue you of course wait
you must do one thing for us before you
leave
you must pleasure us before you leave
this place what all of you oh god I did
die go to heaven
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
god damn it
hostiles on the road we're gonna do you
know I have an idea I want to use the
big gun
Rachel this is not a big gun this is a
rocket launcher whatever it is I want to
use it my turn no yes wait no yes No
you don't let me use it you never gonna
see my make up buddy again oh and that's
any different from now how I'll kill you
looking to desert cantle outfit
ya know how much hot touch you
[Music]
hey George that's the problem with you
always premature oh shut up come on get
outta here
[Music]
on the way
I think you should try to make it to the
door
maybe it's unlocked come on hop with me
ready what are you doing I think we
should go by the window and yell for
help okay
George that's a stupid idea come on this
way can't believe you blew Bob's Jeep me
me I can't fucking believe I brought you
on this mission after six years of
marriage you think I've learned my
lesson but no my dumb ass brings your
dumb ass halfway around the world so you
can make me look like a bigger dumbass
unbelievable Wow
little pent-up aren't you yeah big can't
a man just get a little head just a
little just a little suckie suckie a
blow job here and there
have you lost your mind are you crazy
we're in this mess because you blow up
the Jeep this was your fault my fault
how the fuck is this my fault
are you so 16 a uniform blah blah blah
if you weren't busy molesting the rocket
launcher I wouldn't have accidentally
set it off are you kidding me
Rachel do you have any idea how hard it
is to be married to a beautiful woman
like you and having guys constantly
vying for your attention trying to
impress you I know you want to be with a
successful man like like Agent X and on
top of that you know every day I still
want you just as bad and just as
passionately there's the first day I
laid eyes on you and you don't seem to
want me to for me at all
that's not true George you just you're
obsessed with your job and
[Music]
getting a mission it's it's like I'm not
important to you anymore
don't you get it
it's because you're important to me that
I want a mission that I want to keep my
head buried in the work I want you to be
proud of me I want you to watch it be
proud walking around with me Vivek I am
proud of you I love you I love you too
[Applause]
[Music]
how very touching hmm Asian em don't
look so shocked and it's Miranda
but why money why else come I've brought
the coordinates to the White House I'll
deal with these lovebirds later always
thought she was kind of a bitch yeah she
big monstrous feet - I hope the Brits
are having better luck than us
[Applause]
[Music]
hmm sir why is it Watson we're gonna
need a damn good plan to get past his
guards yes Watson I'm on it
I have an idea
[Music]
are you fidgeting just me I know that
sound
what is that yeah did you mean what you
said of course I did still gonna stop
them no all right I'm going to strum the
Bob
you create a diversion okay okay
Rachel good I thank you
no I will
[Music]
oh shit looking for that I tell you gosh
donkey fucking will become a sport but I
think it will never become a sport who
in the right mind would pay good money
to see such a thing when you know that
horses are so much more entertaining
horses are agitating
she's never gonna work some faith man
absent faith honey become an agent run
around lady's Underpants what do we have
here
I have two new concubines for His
Highness I'm thinking I like this one
strong like us how dare you touch the
Saints property he would cut our hands
off for showing such disrespect
now step aside me for you what are you
talking about you look like every other
guard here I am a very handsome man I
have a nice physique maybe you are right
oh it gives you let's go back to our
post okay who's my little jihad who's my
little jihad come on a kiss to Papa come
on don't be shy
there you go Oh cutie hello
what's this I have brought two new lives
for you Oh too wise for me Jade you
shouldn't have
is this an honor of my birthday next
week
[Music]
that's what you so long
gather the girls made me out for me
[Music]
what do you go
silly American fish
I am mr. stern hello to you sexy lady
come to Jafar come on so here we've been
a better day huh you do not scare me
really I am Jafar really little little
oh are you gonna do what I tell you to
yes I hope so I have to punish you let's
see what we got here
mmm sounds like fun for me
[Applause]
[Music]
yes absolutely but I'll see you start
bathing my pussy show me what you can do
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
that's come on teacher that's right oh
you like that you like that
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah
[Applause]
[Laughter]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
you ask for distraction I'd say the
proof fucking distractive yeah I'll give
you that
so I found the bomb I diffused it and I
found a room full of cheap so we get
that hell out of here let's go what I
left the pack anointed George Rachel get
down
Rachel my mother kicks harder than that
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm sorry but I don't think it's such a
good time for fishing my friend are you
okay I'm okay you okay
[Music]
you wouldn't shoot an unarmed woman
would you I would never do that use my
bare hands so I can feel it you bitch
[Music]
the sexiest thing I've ever seen and
scariest - can't wait
[Music]
oh now I'm an idiot mister I gotta have
you now wait I did a ticaboo 20 I'm out
it'll still launch it just won't
detonate on impact well it's big enough
to do some serious fucking damage it's
aimed right for the White House god damn
it
Oh God you can't call it back now it's
too late no but I can change the
coordinates
[Applause]
please tell me that it's gonna land in
the middle of the ocean nope better
I said Moorhead not warhead hey boy come
on G hi come on
[Music]
okay thanks getting anywhere sir Thank
You Watson end of the road for you her
side that's all right I got it in here
boy it's time to be left professionals
this guy is mine
this guy belongs to a mutt the Bounty
Hunter who the hell are you
I told you I'm not the bounty hunter
hell no
[Music]
[Applause]
congratulations on becoming an agent
Reichle I always knew you had it in you
sir we thought you were dead
nonsense oh it was very scary really
then without warning a coconut hits him
in the head out of nowhere he was
unconscious for four days and when he
came to he couldn't remember a thing
oh I was so worried for him and coconut
sir
[Applause]
cheers Cheers oh and congratulations
ages 8 Thank You agent 8 hey no hard
feelings okay let's get this party
started I'm gonna get out of here I
thought you'd never ask
god
[Music]
[Applause]
present desert stop
[Music]
rosetta stone
[Applause]
you