[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
you
congratulations on me coming agent
Reichle I knew you had it in you
unfortunate about your husband oh yes
well I could let my feelings for George
compromise the mission
oh sorry sorry sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
did you possibly appreciate this you
know husband doesn't appreciate anything
dead ah George never does
George couldn't even make coffee
[Music]
[Applause]
I worked up
music oh god fucking secret-agent it
feels like yeah you can't teach that
trap I need that anymore
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
oh yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
George never makes me come
[Music]
[Applause]
mission complete George you scared the
crap out of me yeah you should see it
from my point of view dream about that
damn fish tank again
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
oh I have my cereal oh you think so yeah
I do you feeling lucky
and to try to come take it
oh I will you call yourself a secret
agent no wonder they won't give you a
promotion
[Music]
[Applause]
take it that's a no ladies first age
before beauty brains before stupidity
[Applause]
[Music]
what I meant was you're the stupid one
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you like a redheaded stepchild oh
no you did
[Applause]
can't believe mistake my spot Oh mister
you're 30 here 30
[Music]
[Applause]
hi Rachel
I made brownies
who wants some you have to do that I had
to park four blocks away well now you've
had your cardio those are the last of
the brownies isn't it I didn't even get
one oh honey you have to watch your
girlish figure
it's not fair Rachel you know I wanted a
brownie
George life's not fair that's one hell
one hell of a good cook yeah well you
tried being married to her for six years
seven I'm sorry the lack of sex is
making my memory blurry
sorry you got primitive all metal from
your pockets all metal
so we're gonna do a more thorough ha Sam
it's time for a game body cavity search
[Applause]
[Music]
so there I was surrounded by the enemy
deep in the jungles of Bolivia unarmed
and then suddenly I agency pisser you're
late
yes there was a malfunction at security
pella dresser function I'll tell you
what though I've got a big mission for
you what
yes sir go down to the break room and
give me a cup of coffee
[Music]
you know how I like it
as I was saying bullets buzzing over my
head I had no weapon suddenly from the
canopy above came the enemy ha ha oh hi
Amy
ah sorry I didn't mean to startle you
no it's okay it's a middle of on edge in
too much caffeine
well I must compliment you on your
cat-like reflexes
oh yeah
comes with being a secret agent I'll
have to be a little bit more careful
around you I didn't know you could be so
dangerous yeah that's that's me
dangerous you know you could lose an eye
[Applause]
I'm speaking of danger I have to show
you once you tell me
[Music]
[Applause]
cool what does this do
Oh be careful with that I'm having a lot
of problems with it it contains nerve
gas keeps leaking
[Music]
[Applause]
a mini supercomputer complete with
wireless internet digital camera mp3
player cigarette lighter even an am/fm
radio oh should I have it
no what's this um that's that's that's
my vibrator so you're planning on doing
a little fly-fishing oh that that is my
pride and joy it's impenetrable what
[Music]
Wow you're crazy okay
I get it this vest is specially designed
to increase the adrenaline and
testosterone of its we're giving him
more strength endurance even enabling
him to run faster well you think he
could have made it a little bit more
fashionable I mean it looks like a
fishing vest do I look like I know
anything about fashion oh no no you know
no the vest works it's um you know it's
just got lots of convenient pockets it
has an internal cooling system that
regulates body temperature and increases
stamina imagine what that could do for
unify the cigarette could do for me in
the bedroom I already have is my latest
invention training goggles it can create
virtually any situation imaginable from
flying to combat try
[Music]
[Applause]
that's cool you do anything anything
anything anything
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
oh god you're naughty Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Chloe
[Music]
oh my god
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yes George take it you know you've
always wanted that type
[Music]
all right and I'll type fucking there
yes oh yes joy to you you know you boys
[Music]
[Applause]
okay that was a little weird you don't
know how long I've waited for that you
tricked me you lured me down here to
take advantage of me you you gadget
siren oh so oh come on you know I like
you I'm married just my leaf it wasn't
real
felt real don't don't
frightening
[Music]
where've you been huh what you've been
gone over an hour X was looking for you
he was yeah
he needed his coffee oh yeah right
so so what so where were you I was
taking care of business in the lab
business huh and was this business
wearing a white lab coat and reeking a
fake designer perfume are you talking
about don't play stupid with me George
that little trollop Amy what about her
George I'm serious I know that you know
that she knows that we're having marital
issues
she's like a vulture waiting in the
wings you're a crazy lady ha ha I'm
crazy I'm crazy I'm not the one was
provoked by a glass of milk this morning
I'm not the one that hassled the
security guards and we won't even
discuss your bouts of mourning road rage
what I did not harass those security
guards
you set me up and for your information
they proceeded to get very intimate with
me I guess I should be grateful cuz it's
the closest thing I'm head to sex in
months there you go again always with
the sex we know what George maybe if you
learn a little technique instead of
humping me like a drunken Chihuahua I
would be a little more willing to
participate really yeah really is there
a problem here no sir
good Rachel would like to see a loan
place absolutely see yes
where's my coffee coming up sir
[Music]
Rachele fantasy
I am sitting sir right
Rachel I need you
excuse me your help Oh
you're the only one that I can trust I
have to go on a secret mission no one
here even knows about it I can't help it
but I have a feeling it may be my last
really sir I don't think there's any
coming back from this one again huh
don't cry it's the terrorists the Middle
Eastern ones you know those guys mm-hmm
they've developed a plan to destroy the
world and I have to go and steal the
magic ingredients to the weapon Rachel
yes sir I need you to help me save the
world huh the whole world can you do
that can you be a hero yes sir
Kurt
here's what I need for you to do
take this sulfone guard it with your
life I'm going to be meeting my contacts
and they are very dangerous men and they
are going to want to know that I am who
I say I am do you understand
not really sir
gonna take me into custody they're gonna
dial that phone for a code if you don't
give him that code or you don't answer
that phone I'll be killed doc do you
understand
I think so sir protect that with your
life
from now on you shall be known as agent
e d any questions what's the code word
Cuthbert right hmm peppermint peppermint
peppermint
now go I have to prepare for this kind
of a mission but Sir please go hmm
George what-what are you doing here you
go sir
you know I like two sugars
you're dismissed what's so funny you
don't actually believe that secret
mission crap do you oh my god you do
that's the oldest trick in the book he
just wants to fuck you
you're jealous jealous that I got a
mission your secretary
no one's gonna give you a mission I am
an administrative assistant but I guess
you know a thing or two about not
getting missions now wouldn't you well
except fetching coffee now why would you
have to go there okay
I was just trying to warn he's trying to
get in your pants oh I never do that
what did you say I said don't be such an
ass
[Music]
what is there with you in that fish tank
anyway this is going to be the perfect
underwater ecosystem and I will be its
God you are not right yeah well at least
I'm not waiting by a phone that's never
going to ring it will ring why don't you
have a little faith that he'll
accomplish the mission you just don't
get it he's not on a secret mission
nobody knows anything about a secret
mission that's because it's secret duh
honey you know nothing of protocol you
really think he would tell a secretary
about a secret mission I am an
administrative assistant let me see if I
get this straight the story is there's a
group of terrorists and they've built a
bomb and they've threatened to blow up
the planet Earth but alas this will be
his last call of duty and his fate rests
squarely in palms of your hands you're
the only one he can trust his last hope
bla bla bla bla bla bla yeah listen
that's a story gave his last secretary
Ritchie listen don't get mad that was
totally unnecessary you just passed
because you're fighting for Agent X and
file your certificate Island Cantonese
dick sucked leg and you go do not make
me tell you twice in the same night
okay I am a minister assistant
[Applause]
she's crazy
you
is it who are you Oh God Hey
I think I just found happen when I think
of this little swine isn't it cute
beautiful it's fun to say say what we
swine it's just things with absence you
know it's so much fun say isn't it
terrific you like this little swine here
do you like no swine this is like the
other other pink me but how about some
white bean
excuse me no seriously let's just take a
bite let me just roll on let me lick
your own come on
[Music]
[Applause]
another one for Special Agent man thank
you
so how do you say your name Lamy
well if you insist
yeah like I haven't heard that one beep
wait a minute you're not gay no so you
didn't know that this is a gay lesbian
bisexual transgender luau ah no I didn't
[Applause]
um
after that name you know the offer still
stands but you might want to hurry
because my country could call me into
service at any moment as a matter of
fact I'm expecting a call from the
President of the United States there he
is oh yes mr. president yes sir it's me
sir
that top-secret of course sir you know
you can count on me
yes sir goodbye sir
so uh to some yeah everything okay yeah
bag ship out an hour Wow then I guess
guess we better hurry
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
that's good whoa
Oh
good yes
[Music]
oh yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah oh yes yes yes yes oh
I am the secret needs administrator at
cockman yeah well guess I should be
going
you bitch are you okay are you okay
[Music]
don't you
oh shit idiots me you want to tackle me
you should gone there my phone and
firstly it was my secret mission
well now you upset my pristine ecosystem
did you shut up about your ecosystem she
came out here Thank You captain obvious
Oh oh my god do you think he's dead
No
[Music]
good morning everyone
I am agent Jay from the Washington field
office I'm afraid I have some terrible
news one of ours is missing
agent X has disappeared all we know is
he left for an unknown destination
and has not been heard of since Friday
afternoon all communication attempts
have failed and we are forced to use all
of our resources at hand the search and
rescue and I was really upset shut your
hole okay Rick I need to get yourself
together
didn't you hear that word terrorist
Wesley bomb the United States what I put
on responsible Oh shop together oh wow
Rachel listen anybody else hear your
conversation that you had with X No okay
good now we're gonna march back in there
and we're gonna act as if we know
nothing okay good hey you want to be
brought up in treason charges have you
ever been to prison okay now we're gonna
go back in there and we're gonna act as
if we know nothing until I come up with
a plan you got that shake your head yes
that you got it good now let's go Rachel
right this way yeah so this is where the
best place to catch crab is
yeah Rachel isn't it maybe may I have a
word with you in private
hey you bring me a cup of coffee
[Applause]
so I understand that your agent ex is
secretary administrative assistant right
well since you worked so closely with
him I'm just a little curious who've you
overheard anything strange the last few
days maybe notice anything out of the
ordinary
he didn't discuss anything with you
mentioned taking a trip
think hard well British intelligence
have informed us of a possible terrorist
threat this is not what we need right
now with our biggest agent missing
you're still waiting for more
information to come in from the Brits
I'm gonna go check on some possible
leads on agent X in the meantime I want
you to sit next to the fax and call me
the instant something comes in I'm
depending on you yes sir I mean ma'am
yes ma'am not again
[Music]
hey hey
what are you doing still here we didn't
actually think I was gonna leave you now
did you
[Music]
we have our problems and everything in
six years marriage I ever let you down
seven we've been married seven years
seven years four months two days
[Music]
come on in here you know you don't have
to wait with me
I know but everybody's gone home for the
day I figured keep you some company
um
that feels good
[Music]
what are you doing alright I tell you
could fool around at a time like this
human sensitive prick what's wrong with
you
great now I'm a prick well you know what
you are a frigid bitch fuck you no fuck
you you can't really be serious about
this
oh I'm serious George wait shouldn't we
call someone you know for backup
you saw the report there's no time the
terrorists are gonna bomb the US in a
couple of days the British agents are
already in route exactly why we should
call for backup
why so they could pass the assignment
under somebody else so I can get
overlooked again Rachel I'm fucking
tired of getting coffee and dry-cleaning
so this is about you know well maybe you
selfish Turk I don't think risking my
life for my government is selfish it's
patriotic besides the end killed our top
operative I wouldn't be forced to do
this fine well I'm going with you no no
no you're not
you said it yourself I'm responsible so
I'm going no way beyond the gong telling
[Music]
fine
yes my first mission as an agent you're
not an agent you're a secretary I am an
administrative assistant
[Music]
did you hear that terrorists I gotta
call Washington you're not calling
anyone my dear it's me we've got a
problem
[Music]
Oh like it's gonna work for you you
don't even know code honey
you forget in addition to being able to
type 87 words a minute I can hack into
anything impressed
as you should be grab the bag
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah you're mine now
[Applause]
[Music]
George I really don't think there's
gonna be time for fishing yeah this
isn't a fishing rest this is a high-tech
fight enhancing super list right you
know you don't have to make shit up
George follow me
[Music]
that's what I'm talking about that one
of those penis extension things
what been a little inferior are you
George
I'm surprised you even remember that I
have a penis
[Applause]
[Music]
touch me nice huh
no it back away from the weaponry
I want gun no George I want a gun no how
the hell do you expect me to defend
myself satisfied you've got to be
kidding me
listen go to the house pack a few things
essentials only I'm gonna go try and
secure it right in here for something
conspicuous try not to shoot yourself
[Music]
what is all this essential Kate do you
understand we're going undercover yeah
that's why I need somebody disguises duh
okay you know fine have it your way
I don't care if I am NOT carrying its
luggage not one single piece wait
[Music]
this is our inconspicuous ride no one's
ever gonna guess where we're going I'm
just getting fair fine get the bags
getting the best Jorge bag marry or get
the fucking bag
[Music]
[Applause]
the Falcon has left the net losses the
Fox is in the henhouse what the two
idiots our other video ah what if this
base of a rustic
[Music]
[Applause]
okay okay here we go capital of Finland
Helsinki no no no how many times do I
have to tell you form it as a question
what is health sync
yeah Efendi please excuse the
introduction but the British are coming
I know this one funder who is Paul
Revere no no sir the British are coming
now here English agents their own to us
why don't you tell me this uh okay
scout the area find out where the
infidels keep their camp and destroy
them yes Effendi well my plan to take
over the world does not work I always
have plan B Plan B sir
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
how much I like that I think it it
survey says I like this is why I'm gonna
be a bigger star yeah okay camera angle
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
really hot out here she put some
sunscreen on baby
okay agent yeah I am hack med up to it I
just here durka durka Martinez jr. but
he's cookie Bob
I'm your contact I'm gonna take your
base camp
go ahead hurry up for Racine I work with
you guys an Asian extra malls it from
the states all the time
[Applause]
[Music]
I've located the British agents send
three men to cut them off at the pass
take no prisoners meet me back at the
palace
[Music]
what a shithole yes Watson I don't see
our bloody contact anywhere we're gonna
have to move fast
hostiles are everywhere we need some
transport Watson get us a ride should I
contact HQ sir nonsense we move in as
planned huh
now just get us a ride would you what
what what the bloody would the bloody
has he gone Watson what the bloody are
you doing over there hello there do you
speak English okay alrighty then um I
will take a brand a double mocha with
extra cream and do you have any muffins
home excellent
guess not you take credit cards Watson
yes sir what nerves are you doing having
a Chrysler its sandbox fur bucks this
floor Watson it's a goat
it's an indigenous species sir Watson
yes sir
where's the ride sir yes if you look
very close I don't think there's any
taxis Watson just get us our bloody ride
would you can I take my coffee sir
no quick
don't eat all nuts the helm Africa
Norfolk do not
[Music]
well we stop wait guys my instincts they
tell me there's danger your instinct huh
I don't see anything I think your
instincts are wrong
[Music]
[Applause]
merchants here I come sweetie oh that's
awesome
ha
oh that's dirty
I don't know yeah
honey hello
she's back sweetie
[Music]
[Applause]
haha this had better be good
Efendi I have located the agent south of
the palace but these are different from
the rest they want us to know they are
here it's like they are taunting us and
I think they have the American agent
with them only he would be so bold I
think his name is X hold on a second
[Applause]
agent X is here and you're sure he took
out some of our best men it's got to be
him
but we've captured a prisoner find Abdul
tell him to double the guard watch and
get out there I want to know everything
they're doing they take a shit I want to
know about it okay they take a crap I
don't need to know about that but
anything else I'm gonna know about you
understand and you interrogate the
prisoner okay yes go
[Music]
this room is very beautiful it most
certainly is but not as beautiful as you
your beauty is as expansive as the
desert
[Music]
you are like an oasis Oh
do not fear my power
[Music]
what Oh my maid must have left this
never mind
oh look into my eyes
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
ha
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
you
Oh me I want to him
[Music]
yes
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
yes I do oh boy huh Abdul I've broken
all over the powers for you what are you
doing in my room
not Charo and what is Teddy doing on the
floor
hmm let me explain it explain what that
you have one of Hussein's concubines in
my bed if he finds out he'll cut off
both our balls I will not tell you know
what begone with yourself be out of here
before someone sees you I should think
of ah I sneaked up AHA I should kick
your ass but I have no time the same
needs us dress quickly
[Music]
[Applause]
huh wait a minute
some of my cases are missing
and where's Muffy has anybody seen Muffy
what's a Muffy nothing's my baby we have
to go find Muffy Rachel
get a hold of yourself we cannot go back
all right there's no way she'd survive
the heat of the desert the casualty of
war Hey look is this your shoe bag these
are the new summer collection see see
how easily she forgot about Muffy you
know that could be me out there and that
you'd know the difference good married
six years seven seven years
seven long years
[Music]
Oh
what huh this is not what I had in mind
you've been on that dancing all night
sir surely it's my turn to ride soon
Watson soon remember those hostiles
everywhere I must keep a lookout Oh
close ink I see something in the
distance where look alike southeast of
our position possibly my lens what do
you see what is it don't quite know
Watson I can't make it out
good god I think that he's gotten to me
man
[Music]
that's horses York it's really tight
high-five and gently hold on
[Music]
oh stop but any by yourself agent
Jackson Watson British intelligence now
where the hell were you today
you could have cost us the mission man
what I'm a might pick up I to understand
what the agents are yeah who the hell
annoy you what hmm
I like your camel are you guys on a
mission to identify yourself Franken
agency field agent Z had a command a CIA
you water I'm sorry this is my husband
George he watches the mission files in
our building and I am the directors
administrative assistant Rachel you guys
must be the British fellows who sent me
the facts pleased to meet you all good
god what are you both doing here this is
a Code Red top-secret mission Oh
sightseeing tour okay we'll take it from
here
you two back in the camp while we'll do
recon of the area and Oh 500 hours okay
yes stay close to your tents oh and
don't get in our way
hey I think we can be of service yeah
yes I think you might very good man ago
rusty have a nice cup of tea
well poached honey your reputation
precedes you
shut up Virgil so not really understand
our tensile mmm hell on the fuck are we
yeah those limey bastards who they think
they are secret agents or something they
are oh I have an idea you know what we
should do we should get that nerve gas
but you had and put it in their tent and
then after they're asleep we can go to
the palace until the map to the
warehouse that's a great why do I have
to go gas him in the tent I thought he
was a leader and if I was a leader
that's what I would do
yes of course I knew that I was just
testing you and you did well I want to
go prepare the equipment
[Music]
who do you work for tell me who sent you
where is the camp your silence only
angers me
oh look at the will dog little dog
I'm leave the prisoner with me thank you
dismissed
we'll get the will puppy wuppy
you're so sweet I think I'll name you
jihad wanna dance Sadat's the way uh ha
ha ha I like it
[Applause]
which tent do you think they're in I
think it's that one that one what the
Union Jack yeah that's good yes
[Music]
[Applause]
guys remember the only way inside the
palace office without setting off the
alarm is going to be through the roof
once you're inside the map is going to
be inside the desk guys
[Music]
front door somewhat I'm gonna find the
office right away
[Music]
that was amazing
did you forget how flexible my body is
well considering the fact that you never
let me see it anymore I've forgotten
quite a few things about your body not
now George really
[Music]
Oh Oh what's not full of my head's been
bashed in I think it was this uh those
damned Americans they're gonna get us
killed Watson I think they're Cowboys or
something too much television I'd say
[Applause]
[Music]
what the hell was you thinking you're
gonna get us all killed this is a game
you do anything like that again I know
your what I'll be forced to kill you I
would like to see you try oh ha ha ha
that smarts doesn't it oh you gotta
watch her with that she's like a ninja
Oh
anything you'd like to add
[Music]
we got the map here what done
so we're team now right you want our
help you want our help
good sit sit yes yes we need your help
oh and I also got you yes on here you'll
find all the reconnaissance photos to
get you safely into the house excellent
work my dear what the hell happened do
you mad
oh well I had to take out a couple
guards to fact I killed them with my
bare hands I got rid of the bodies I
dragged them far away
they'll never be found so you know you
don't have to worry we'll come back on
him yes quite the hero he was
oh good job man I was wrong about you
I thought you were just a pen butcher
well we got lots of training to do we
have to go over the hill reports there
Rachel gather Monsen oh that's one
coffee Bertelsen I should say
nice Oh No okay Oh
kevrah come t zue sugars
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
you
[Applause]
I'm okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay now listen up me and Watson to take
out the palace guards here and here
moving forward to the throne room and
take out the Seine Rachel
George take Bob's Jeep go to the
warehouse go to the warehouse and disarm
the weapon by removing the uranium
warhead now don't mess this up is
everyone clear yes sir
good what's in what are you doing
something to remember our trip together
good god man this is not a bloody lads
holiday this is a mission now move out
now dead sheep it's almost paid off
[Music]
[Applause]
take a look take cancer take this one we
have to end the surprise on this idea we
don't go dance place so they have your
silencer and fire
then you go on fire and kill anyone you
come across anyone yes 81 man you can
miss a life cycle yeah where's don't
follow me
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god I've died and gone to heaven
Dorie I'll take out this what are you
doing man never good your training I'll
style sir kill anyone I see it's them or
me that's what you've said conduce me up
you forgot what is to be a British agent
but I find country sir no no no to be
licensed to kill and license to fuck the
finest women the world has to offer
ours is not the time to kill no no no
this is time to what are you doing in
these chambers it is forbidden good
scream I'll just know it don't worry
we would not alert the guards to the
presence of our rescuers rescues you are
here to rescue us aren't you of course
we are yes yes we're here to rescue
we're just glad you're all in one piece
we have not seen men like you before we
only see one man oh that's nice I guess
nice have you seen him holy jesus
Oh nasty you see well yes I do
oh well we must be awful we're gonna
clear the palace to rescue you of course
wait you must do one thing for us before
you leave
you must pleasure us before you leave
this place what all of you oh my god I
did die go to heaven
three
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
British something
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
god damn it
hostiles on the road Oregon do you know
I have an idea I want to use the big gun
Rachel this is not a big gun this is a
rocket launcher whatever it is I want to
use it my turn no yes wait no yes
no you don't let me use it you never
gonna see my make up buddy again oh and
that's any different from now how hot
out here
you how cute you look new
does it camel outfit yeah you know how
much hot touch
[Music]
hey George that's the problem with you
always premature Rachel shut up coming
off good earlier
[Music]
[Applause]
on the way
[Music]
are fired
I think you should try to make it to the
door
maybe it's unlocked come on hop with me
ready
[Applause]
what are you doing I think we should go
by the window and yell for help okay
George that's a stupid idea come on this
way this way go to play don't worry this
way can't believe you blue Bob cheap me
me I can't fucking believe I brought you
on this mission after six years of
marriage you think I've learned my
lesson but no my dumb ass brings your
dumb ass halfway around the world so you
can make me look like a bigger dumbass
unbelievable Wow
little pent-up aren't you yes big cat
man just get a little head just a little
just a little sucky sucky a blow job
here and there have you lost your mind
are you crazy
we're in this mess because you bought
the Jeep this was your fault my fault
how the fuck is my fault are you so sick
seeing a uniform bah bah blah you aren't
busy molesting a rocket launcher I
wouldn't have accidentally set it off
are you kidding me
Rachel give any idea how hard it is to
be married to a beautiful woman like you
and having guys constantly vying for
your attention trying to impress you I
[Music]
know you want to be a successful man
like like Agent X and on top of that you
know every day I still want you just as
bad and just as passionately there's the
first day I laid eyes on you and you
don't seem to want me to to want me at
all
let's hop to short you just you're
obsessed with your job and
[Music]
get a mission it's it's like I'm not
important to you anymore
don't you get it it's because you're
important to me that I want a mission
that I want to keep my head buried in
the work I want you to be proud of me I
want you to what you'd be proud walking
around pity I am proud of you course I
love you
love you too
[Applause]
[Music]
how very touching agent em don't have
shot and it's Miranda why money why else
come I've brought the coordinates to the
White House I'll deal with these
lovebirds later always thought she was
kind of a bitch yeah she big monstrous
feet - I hope the Brits are better luck
than us
[Applause]
[Music]
so why is it Watson we're gonna need a
damn good plan to get past his own
guards yes Hudson I'm on it I have an
idea
[Music]
are you fidgeting just me I know that
sound
what is that did you mean what you said
of course I did
[Music]
[Applause]
still gonna stop them now I don't
all right I'm going to strum the Bob you
create a diversion
okay okay Rachel okay thank you
no I will
[Music]
jean-bob that way oh shit hi looking for
that I tell you gosh donkey fucking will
become a sport bubbly it was never
become a sport who in the right mind
would pay good money to see such a thing
when you know that horses are so much
more entertaining
horses are edited
[Music]
she's never gonna work some faith man
some faith honey become an agent around
lady's Underpants what do we have here
I have two new combatants for His
Highness ah very very nice
I'm thinking I like this one strong my
god how dare you touch with Saints
property he would cut your hand off for
showing such disrespect
now step aside and laugh mm father just
open Farber your pinky oh that was for
me for you what are you talking about
you look like every other guard here I'm
a very handsome man I have a nice
physique maybe you are right
oh I can see you let's go back to our
post okay who's my little jihad who's my
little jihad come on a kiss to Papa come
on don't be shy
there you go Oh jokey hello what's this
I have brought two new wise for you to
wise for me Jade you shouldn't have is
this in honor of my birthday next week
[Applause]
[Music]
wait
[Applause]
[Music]
I took you so long
gather the girls made me out fun okay
got what
well you go
[Music]
[Applause]
ah silly American fashion
[Music]
I am mistress Joan
well hello to you sexy lady
come to Jafar come on my way so here
you've been a bad boy huh
you do not scare me all realized you far
really
little little oh are you gonna do what I
tell you to do
yes I hope so I have to punish you
let's see what we got here
Oh sounds like fun for me
[Applause]
[Music]
yes absolutely
but don't you start bathing my casino
hey show me when you came dinner
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
oh that's cuz meet you
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
and
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
that's right
[Applause]
[Music]
come on teacher that's right
oh you like that you like that
[Music]
[Applause]
yes Oh
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
oh yeah
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
yes yes yes
[Music]
[Applause]
you ask me deception I'd say that a
fucking distracted yeah I'll give you
that
so I found the bomb I diffused it and
about a room full of tape so we get that
hell out of here let's go what I left
the back you enjoyed it short
perhaps you looking for this you know
Rachel get down
[Music]
some Rachel
fibula possess please my mother kicks
harder than that
oh dish how about I'm sorry but I don't
think it's such a good time for fishing
my god told you it's faster cool are you
okay I'm okay you okay okay
you would shoot it on on one would you I
would never do that
use my bare hand so I can feel it ah
you bet
[Music]
[Applause]
sexiest thing I've ever seen and
scariest to
[Music]
can't wait
Oh
oh oh now I'm an idiot miss I gotta have
you now wait I thought you said you are
that thing I did a ticaboo 20 I'm out
it'll still launch it just won't
detonate on impact
well it's big enough to do some serious
fucking damage and right for the White
House
Oh God you can't call it back now it's
too late no but I can change the
coordinates
please tell me that's gonna land in the
middle of the ocean nope better
[Music]
I said Moorhead not warhead one come on
G hive come on faith where am i right
girl let's okay ladies getting any
myself Thank You Wilson end on the road
for you her side that's right I got it
in here boys times we've left
professionals this guy is mine
this guy belongs to a mutt the body
hunter who the hell are you
I told you I must a bounty hunter hell
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
my foot congratulations on becoming an
agent Reichle I always knew you had it
in you sir we thought you were dead not
judge oh it was very scary
really then without warning a coconut
hits him in the head out of nowhere he
was unconscious for four days and when
he came to he couldn't remember a thing
Oh I was so worried for him
coconut sir
[Applause]
cheers Cheers oh and congratulations
ages eight Thank You agent a hey no hard
feelings okay let's get this party
started
[Music]
you ready get out of here I thought you
never asked god
[Music]
[Applause]
huh
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
because a powerful
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
hi
[Music]
Oh
ah
that's
well
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
with the
to
go in
not
faster morning
yes
[Music]
when the gentleman
everybody
Parisian desert stopped me
you
[Music]
Operation Desert Storm
break7
[Music]