[Music]
congratulations on my coming in agent
Reichle I knew you had it didn't you
unfortunate about your husband oh yes
well I couldn't let my feelings for
George compromise the mission
[Music]
Sorry Sorry Sorry
does your husband create these no
husband doesn't appreciate anything
dead Oh George never does George you
couldn't even make coffee
Oh
[Music]
fuckin secret agents those like yeah
you can't teach that
think I need that anymore
[Music]
[Applause]
George never makes me come
[Music]
[Applause]
giorgia scared the crap out of me yeah
you should see it from my point of view
dream about that damn fish tank again
yeah something like that
[Music]
[Applause]
oh I have my cereal
how are you think so yeah I do you feel
unlucky
would you try to come take it
oh I will you call yourself a secret
agent
no wonder they won't give you a
promotion
[Applause]
I take it that's a no ladies first age
before beauty brains before stupidity
[Music]
what I meant was you're the stupid one
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you like a redheaded stepchild oh
no you did
can't believe you stake my spot oh
you're dirty here 30
[Music]
hi Rachel I made brownies
who wants some I had to park four blocks
away well now you've had your cardio
those are the last of the brownies isn't
it I didn't even get one oh you have to
watch your girlish figure
it's not fair Rachel you know I wanted a
brownie
George life's not fair that's one hell
one hell of a good cook
yeah well you tried being married to her
for six years seven I'm sorry the lack
of sex is making my memory blurry sorry
you got the remove all metal from your
pockets
all metal so gonna have to get a little
more thorough Sam it's time for a dead
body cavity search so there I was
surrounded by the enemy deep in the
jungles of Bolivia unarmed and then
suddenly agency yes sir you're late
yes there was a malfunction at security
pella day sir function I'll tell you
what though I've got a big mission for
you
yes sir go down to the break room and
give me a cup of coffee
you know how I like it
as I was saying bullets buzzing over my
head I had no weapon suddenly from the
canopy above came the enemy oh sorry I
didn't mean to startle you
no it's okay it's a middle of on edge
too much caffeine
well I must compliment you on your
cat-like reflexes oh yeah
comes with being a secret agent I'll
have to be a little bit more careful
around you I didn't know you could be so
dangerous yeah that's that's me
dangerous you know good
[Music]
[Applause]
what does this do Oh be careful with
that I'm having a lot of problems with
it
it contains nerve gas a mini
supercomputer complete with wireless
internet digital camera mp3 player
cigarette lighter even an am/fm radio oh
should I have it
No
[Music]
that's just that's death that's my
vibrator so you're planning on doing a
little fly-fishing oh that that is my
pride and joy it's impenetrable what
[Music]
okay I get it
this vest is specially designed to
increase the adrenaline and testosterone
of its we're giving him more strength
endurance even enabling him to run
faster well you think he could have made
it a little bit more fashionable I mean
it looks like a fishing vest do I look
like I know anything about fashion oh no
no you know no the vest works it's you
know it's just got lots of convenient
pockets it has an internal cooling
system that regulates body temperature
and increases stamina imagine what that
could do for unifier just think what I
could do for me in the bedroom I already
have is my latest invention training
goggles it can create virtually any
situation imaginable from flying it's a
combat try
[Applause]
[Music]
anything anything anything
Oh
oh you're
[Music]
oh my god
oh yes George take it you know you've
always one of that type
[Music]
fucking you know you've always one of
that type
[Music]
okay that was a little weird you don't
know how long I've waited for that you
tricked me you lured me down here to
take advantage of me you you gadget
siren so oh come on you know I like you
I'm married it wasn't real felt real
[Music]
where have you been huh what you've been
gone over an hour X was looking for you
he was yeah he needed his coffee oh yeah
right so so what so where were you I was
taking care of business in the lab
business huh and was this business
wearing a white lab coat and reeking a
fake designer perfume what are you
talking about don't play stupid with me
George
that little trollop Amy what about her
George I'm serious I know that you know
that she knows that we're having marital
issues
she's like a vulture waiting in the
wings you're a crazy lady I'm crazy I'm
crazy I'm not the one was provoked by a
glass of milk this morning I'm not the
one that hassled the security guards and
we won't even discuss your bouts of
mourning road rage but I did not harass
those security guards you set me up
and for your information they proceeded
to get very intimate with me I guess I
should be grateful cuz it's the closest
thing I'm head to sex in months there
you go again always with the sex we know
what George maybe if you learn a little
technique instead of humping me like a
drunken Chihuahua I would be a little
more willing to participate really yeah
really is there a problem here no sir
good Rachel I'd like to see you alone
please absolutely see yes where's my
coffee coming up sir
Rachel have a seat
I am sitting sir right
Rachel I need you
excuse me your help
Oh
you're the only one that I can trust I
have to go on a secret mission no one
here even knows about it I can't help it
but I have a feeling it may be my last
really sir I don't think there's any
coming back from this one kid huh don't
cry it's the terrorists the Middle
Eastern ones you know those guys mm-hmm
they've developed a plan to destroy the
world and I have to go and steal the
magic ingredients to the weapon weapons
[Music]
Rachel yes sir I need you to help me
save the world huh the whole world can
you do that can you be a hero yes sir
[Music]
good
here's what I need for you to do take
this cellphone guard it with your life
I'm going to be meeting my contacts and
they are very dangerous men and they are
going to want to know that I am who I
say I am do you understand
[Music]
not really sir they're gonna take me
into custody they're gonna dial that
phone for a code if you don't give him
that code or you don't answer the phone
I'll be killed Oh doc do you understand
I think so sir protect that with your
life from now on you shall be known as
agent dee dee
any questions what's the code word
good word great
hmm peppermint
peppermint peppermint now go
I have to prepare for this kind of a
mission but sir please go mmm
George what what are you doing here you
go sir
you know I like two sugars you're
dismissed
what's so funny you don't actually
believe that secret mission crap do you
oh my god you do that's the oldest trick
in the book he just wants to fuck you
you're jealous jealous that I got a
mission
your secretary no one's gonna give you a
mission I am an administrative assistant
but I guess you know a thing or two
about not to getting missions now
wouldn't you well except fetching coffee
no why would you have to go there okay I
was just trying to warn he's trying to
get in your pants Oh what did you say I
said don't be such an ass
[Music]
what is it with you in that fish tank
anyway this is going to be the perfect
underwater ecosystem you are not right
yeah but at least I'm not waiting by a
phone that's never going to ring it will
ring why don't you have a little faith
that he'll accomplish the mission you
just don't get it he's not on a secret
mission nobody knows anything about a
secret mission that's because it's
secret duh
honey you know nothing of protocol you
really think he would tell his secretary
about a secret mission I am an
administrative assistant let me see if I
get this straight the story is there's a
group of terrorists and they've built a
bomb and they threaten to blow up the
planet Earth
but alas this will be his last call of
duty and his fate rests squarely and
palms of your hands you're the only one
he can trust his last hope blah blah
blah blah blah yeah listen that's a
story he gave his last secretary Richie
listen don't get mad because you're
fighting for Agent X and felon
certificate island getting his dick
sucked leg there you go do not make me
tears you twice in the same night okay I
am an administrative assistant
[Music]
she's crazy
I think I just found when I think of
this little swine isn't it cute
beautiful it's not to say say what we
swine it's just things with Epson you
know it's so much fun to say isn't it
terrific you like this little just wine
here do you like this wine this is like
the other other pink me but how about
some white meat
excuse me no no seriously let's just
take a bite
[Music]
another one for a special agent man so
how do you say your name Lamy well if
you insist
yeah like I haven't heard that one beep
wait a minute you're not gay no so you
didn't know that this is a gay lesbian
bisexual transgender luau
no I didn't up to that name you know the
offer still stands
but you might want to hurry because my
country could call me into service at
any moment
as a matter of fact I'm expecting a call
from the President of the United States
oh there he is
yes mr. president yes sir
it's me sir
that top-secret of course sir you know
you can count on me yes sir goodbye sir
so uh just um yeah everything okay yeah
ship out in an hour
Wow then I got guess we have better
hurry
[Music]
yeah
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
well guess I should be going okay are
you okay
[Music]
don't you
oh shit idiots me you tackle me you
should have gone there my phone and
firstly it was my secret mission but now
you've upset my pristine ecosystem would
you shut up about your ecosystem check
it out here Thank You captain obvious
Oh oh my god do you think he's dead Oh
[Music]
good morning everyone
I am agent J from Washington field
office I'm afraid I have some terrible
news one of ours is missing agent X has
disappeared all we know is he left for
an unknown destination and has not been
heard of since Friday afternoon all
communication attempts have failed and
we are forced to use all of our
resources at hand the search and rescue
[Music]
get yourself together Rachel listen
anybody else hear your conversation that
you had with X no okay good
now we're gonna march back in there and
we're gonna act as if we know nothing
hey you want to be brought up in treason
charges have you ever been to prison
okay now we're gonna go back in there
and we're gonna act as if we know
nothing until I come up with a plan you
got that shake your head yes that you
got it good now let's go Rachel
right this way this place to catch crab
is
Rachel isn't it maybe may I have a word
with you in private
hey you bring me a cup of coffee
so I understand that your agent ex is
secretary administrative assistant right
well since you worked so closely with
him I'm just a little curious who've you
overheard anything strange the last few
days maybe notice anything out of the
ordinary
he didn't discuss anything with you
mentioned taking a trip think hard
well British intelligence have informed
us of a possible terrorist threat this
is not what we need right now with our
biggest agent missing you're still
waiting for more information to come in
from the Brits I'm gonna go check on
some possible leads on agent X in the
meantime I want you to sit next to the
fax and call me the instant something
comes in I'm depending on you yes sir I
mean ma'am yes ma'am not again
Hey Hey
what are you doing still here we didn't
actually think I was gonna leave you now
did you
we have our problems and everything but
in six years of marriage if I ever let
you down
seven we've been married seven years
seven years four months two days
come on in here you know you don't have
to wait with me
I know but everybody's gone home for the
day and I figure keep you some company
[Music]
that feels good
what are you doing around at a time like
this cue insensitive prick what's wrong
with you
great now I'm a prick well you know what
you are a frigid bitch
fuck you no fuck you
you can't really be serious about this
oh I'm serious George wait shouldn't we
call someone you know for backup you saw
the report there's no time the
terrorists are gonna bomb the u.s. in a
couple of days the British agents are
already enroute exactly why we should
call for backup
why so they could pass the assignment
under somebody else so I can get
overlooked again Rachel I'm fuckin tired
of getting coffee and dry-cleaning so
this is about you know maybe you selfish
jerk
I don't think risking my life for my
government is selfish it's patriotic
besides if you hadn't killed our top
operative I wouldn't be forced to do
this fine well I'm going with you
no no no you're not you said it yourself
I'm responsible so I'm going no way
pila metalli
fine yes my first mission as an agent
you're not an agent you're a secretary I
am an administrative assistant
just rear that terrorist I gotta call
Washington you're not calling anyone my
dear it's me we've got a problem
Oh like it's gonna work for you honey
you forget in addition to being able to
type 87 words a minute I can hack into
anything I'm impressed
as you should be
[Music]
George I really don't think there's
gonna be time for fishing this isn't a
fishing dress this is a high-tech fight
enhancing super boost all right you know
you don't have to make shit up George
follow me
that's what I'm talking about that one
of those penis extension things what
feeling a little inferior are you George
I'm surprised you even remember that I
have a penis
touch no back away from the weaponry gun
no George I want a gun no how the hell
did you expect me to defend myself
[Music]
satisfied you've got to be kidding me
go to the house pack a few things
essentials only I'm gonna go try and
secure it right in here before something
inconspicuous try not to shoot yourself
[Music]
what is all this
essentials okay do you understand we're
going undercover yeah that's why I need
somebody to disguise this duh okay you
know fine have it your way
I don't care if I am NOT carrying ass
luggage not one single piece wait this
is our inconspicuous ride no one's ever
gonna guess where we're going I'm just
getting fair fine get the bags getting
the back George
bags Mary George hit the fucking bags
[Music]
the Falcon has left the nest the Fox is
in the henhouse what the two idiots
their other radio oh for God's sake
[Music]
okay okay here we go capital of Finland
Helsinki no no no how many times do I
have to tell you form it as a question
what is Helsinki Effendi please excuse
the introduction but the British are
coming
I know this one who is Paul Revere no no
sir
the British are coming now here English
agents they're on to us why don't you
tell me this okay
scout the area find out where the
infidels keep their camp and destroy
them
yes Effendi well my plan to take over
the world does not work I always have
plan B Plan B sir
[Music]
survey says
really hot out here she put some
sunscreen on baby okay pac-man up to it
I just here
durka durka Martinez jr. but you call me
Bob
I'm your contact
I'm gonna take your base camp go Gator
hurry up before we're seen I work with
you guys an Asian Eckstrom all that from
the states all the time
[Music]
I've located the British agents send
three men to cut them off at the pass
take no prisoners meet me back in the
palace
[Music]
what a shithole yes Watson I don't see
our bloody contact anywhere we're gonna
have to move fast
hostiles are everywhere we need some
transport Watson give us a ride should I
contact HQ sir nonsense we move in as
plan ah
now just get us a ride would you what
what what the bloody what the bloody has
he gone Watson what the bloody are you
doing over there hello there do you
speak English alrighty then um I will
take four and a double mocha with extra
cream do you have any muffins
guess not you take credit cards Watson
yes sir
what nerves are you doing having a
Chrysler its sandbox sandbox good lord
Watson it's a goat it's an indigenous
species sir Watson yes sir
where's the right sir yes if you look
very close I don't think there's any
taxis Watson just get us our bloody ride
would you can I take my coffee sir
no quick
don't eat all nuts
Lahaina Mexican no sir do not touch
[Music]
well what stop wait guys my instincts
they tell me there's danger your
instincts huh I don't see anything I
think your instincts are wrong
[Music]
Oh sweetie oh my that's awesome
dirty
[Music]
we go now yeah
sweetie
[Music]
haha this had better be good Efendi I
have located the agent south of the
palace but these are different from the
rest they want us to know they are here
it's like they are taunting us and I
think they have the American agent with
them hold on a second agent X is here
and you're sure he took out some of our
best men it's got to be him
but we've captured a prisoner find Abdul
tell him to double the guard watch and
get out there I want to know everything
they're doing they take a shit I want to
know about it okay they take a crap I
don't need to know about that but
anything else I want to know about you
understand and you interrogate the
prisoner okay yes go
this room is very beautiful it most
certainly is but not as beautiful as you
your beauty is as expansive as the
desert
you are like an oasis Oh
do not fear my power
what
the maid must have left this never mind
oh look into my eyes
[Music]
ha
[Applause]
[Music]
hey I want to hit sick of eating my own
[Laughter]
[Music]
yes yes
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm looking all over the powers for you
what are you doing in my room
[Music]
what is Teddy doing on the floor
let me explain explain what that you
have one of Hussein's concubines in my
bed if he finds out I'll cut off both
our balls I will not tell you know what
begone with yourself be out of here
before someone sees you I should kick
your ass but I have no time the same
needs us dress quickly
[Music]
huh wait a minute
some of my cases are missing
and where's Muffy has an amazing Muffy
what's a Muffy nothing's my baby we have
to go find Muffy Rachel get ahold of
yourself we cannot go back all right
there's no way she'd survive the heat of
the desert the casualty of war Hey look
is this your shoe bag these are the new
summer collection see see how easily she
forgot about Muffy you know that could
be me out there I thought you'd know the
difference the merge six years seven
seven years
[Music]
what's up this is not what I had in mind
you've been on that dancing all night
sir surely it's my turn to ride soon
Watson soon remember those hostiles
everywhere I must keep a lookout oh I
think I see something in the distance
where look a light south east of our
position possibly Mullens
what do you see what is it don't quite
know what to like can't make it out good
god I think that he's gotten to me man
[Music]
it's really tight hold on
stop identify yourself agent Jackson
Watson British intelligence now where
the hell were you today
you could have cost us the mission man
what I made my pickup I don't understand
what the agents are who the hell am i
you what oh I like your camel are you
guys on a mission to identify yourself
rankin agency field agent Z had a
command a CIA you liar
I'm sorry this is my husband George he
watches the mission files in our
building and I'm the directors
administrative assistant Rachel you guys
must be the British fellows who sent me
the facts pleased to meet you both good
god what are you both doing here this is
a Code Red top-secret mission Oh
sightseeing tour okay we'll take it from
here you two back in the camp while
we'll do recon of the area and own 500
hours okay yes stay close to your tents
oh and don't get in our way
hey I think we can be of service yeah
yes I think you might
very good man ago Russ me up a nice cup
of tea
well the poached honey your reputation
precedes you shut up Rachel so not
really gonna stay in our tent to let
them have all the fun
barley yeah those limey bastards
who they think they are secret agents or
something
they are oh yeah I have an idea you know
what we should do we should get that
nerve gas
but you had and put it in their tent and
then after they're asleep we can go to
the palace until the map to the
warehouse that's a great idea why do I
have to go gas him in the tent
I thought you were the leader and if I
was leader that's what I would do
yes of course I knew that I was just
testing you and you did well I'm gonna
go prepare the equipment who do you work
for tell me who sent you
where is the camp
your silence only angers me
oh look at the will dog little dog
don't leave the prisoner with me thank
you
dismissed look at the will puppy wuppy
you're so sweet I think I'll name you
jihad when a dance Sadat's the way
uh-huh uh-huh
where's Ted do you think they're in I
think that one that one what the Union
Jack yeah that's good
[Music]
[Applause]
guys remember the only way inside the
palace office without setting off the
alarm is gonna be through the roof once
you're inside the map is gonna be inside
the desk
[Music]
front door it's a lot I'm gonna find the
office right away
[Music]
that was amazing
did you forget how flexible my body is
well considering the fact that you never
let me see it anymore I've forgotten
quite a few things about your body not
now George really
[Music]
oh yeah what's an eyeful of my head's
been bashed in I think it was this uh
those damned Americans they're gonna get
us killed Watson I think they're Cowboys
or something too much television I'd say
what the hell's you thinking you're
gonna get us all killed this is a game
you do anything like that again I know
you're what I'll be forced to kill you I
would like to see you try that smarts
doesn't it oh you gotta watch her with
that she's like a ninja anything you'd
like to add
we got the map here what done
so we're team now right you are help you
honor help good say Sam yes yes we need
your help
oh and I also got you this on here
you'll find all the reconnaissance
photos to get you safely into the palace
excellent work my dear what the hell
happened to you man
oh I had to take out a couple guards too
in fact I killed him with my bare hands
I got rid of the bodies that I dragged
him far away they'll never be found so
you know you don't have to worry won't
come back on you yes quite the hero he
was oh good job man I was wrong about
you I thought you were just a pen
butcher well we got lots of training to
do we have to go over the Intel reports
that Rachel gather Poulsen oh that's one
crafty bird Elton I should say nice
you know okay oh yeah broke up t zue
sugars yeah
[Music]
I'm okay
okay now listen up me and Watson to take
out the palace guards here and here
moving forward to the throne room and
take out the Seine Rachel
George take Bob's Jeep go to the
warehouse go to the warehouse and disarm
the weapon by removing the uranium
warhead now don't mess this up is
everyone clear yes sir good Watson what
are you doing just let me tell him of
our trip together good god man this is
not a bloody lads holiday this is a
mission now move out that's it sheep
it's almost paying off
[Music]
oh my god I've died and gone to heaven
don't worry I'll take care of this
what are you doing man you forgot your
training hostile sir kill anyone I see
it's them or me that's what you've said
good news me if you forgot what it is to
be a British agent fine country sir but
no no no to be licensed to kill and
licensed to fuck the finest women the
world has to offer us this is not the
time to kill no no no this is time to
[Music]
what's you doing in these chambers it is
forbidden scream don't worry we would
not alert the guards to the presence of
our rescuers rescues you are here to
rescue us aren't you
of course we are yes yes we're here to
rescue we're just glad you're all in one
piece we have not seen men like you
before we only see one man oh that's
nice I guess
nice have you seen him holy jesus oh
nasty you see well yes I do well we must
be awful we're gonna clear the palace to
rescue you of course wait you must do
one thing for us before you leave you
must pleasure us before you leave this
place what all of you oh god I did die
go to heaven
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
god damnit hostiles on the road you know
I have an idea I want to use the big gun
Rachel this is not a big gun this is a
rocket launcher whatever it is I want to
use it my turn
no yes wait no no you don't let me use
it
you never gonna see my make a buddy
again oh and that's any different from
now how cute you look a new desert camel
outfit ya know how much hot touch you
see George that's the problem with you
always premature Rachel shut up come on
get outta here
[Music]
on the way
I think you should try to make it to the
door
maybe it's unlocked come on hop with me
ready what are you doing I think we
should go by the window and yell for
help okay
George that's a stupid idea come on this
way can't believe you blew Bob's Jeep me
me I can't fucking believe I brought you
on this mission after six years of
marriage you think I've learned my
lesson but no my dumb ass brings your
dumb ass halfway around the world so you
can make me look like a bigger dumbass
unbelievable Wow little pent-up aren't
you yeah big can't a man just get a
little head just a little just a little
suckie suckie a blow job here and there
[Music]
have you lost your mind are you crazy
we're in this mess because you blew up
the Jeep this was your fault my fault
how the fuck is this my fault are you so
16 a uniform blah blah blah if you
weren't busy molesting a rocket launcher
I wouldn't have accidentally set it off
are you kidding me
Rachel do you have any idea how hard it
is to be married to a beautiful woman
like you and having guys constantly
vying for your attention trying to
impress you I know you want to be with a
successful man like like Agent X and on
top of that you know every day I still
want you just as bad and just as
passionately there's the first day I
laid eyes on you and you don't seem to
want me to come why me at all
that's not true George you just you're
obsessed with your job and
getting a mission it's it's like I'm not
important to you anymore
don't you get it it's because you're
important to me that I want a mission
that I want to keep my head buried in
the work I want you to be proud of me I
want you to watch it be proud walking
around with me Vivek I am proud of you
I love you I love you too
how very touching agent em don't look so
shocked and it's Miranda
but why money why else come I've brought
the coordinates to the White House I'll
deal with these lovebirds later always
thought she was kind of a bitch yeah she
big monstrous feet - I hope the Brits
are having better luck than us
sir what is it Watson we're gonna need a
damn good plan to get past his veins
guards yes what sir
I'm on it I have an idea
[Music]
how are you feeling
I know that sound
what is that yeah did you mean what you
said still gonna stop them no all right
I'm gonna just armed the bomb you create
a diversion
okay okay Rachel good I thank you
no I will
[Music]
oh okay further I tell you gosh
donkey fucking will become a sport
bubbly
it will never become a sport who in the
right mind would pay good money to see
such a thing when you know that horses
are so much more entertaining horses are
agitating
she's never gonna work some faith man
absent faith fighting become an agent
one ready ladies underpants
what do we have here I have two new
concubines for His Highness I'm thinking
I like this one strong like ox how dare
you touch with Saints property he would
cut your hand off for showing such
disrespect
now step aside are you what are you
talking about you look like every other
guard here I am a very handsome man I
have a nice physique maybe you are right
what gives you let's go back to our post
okay
who's my little jihad who's my little
jihad come on a kiss to Papa come on
don't be shy
there you go Oh cutie hello what's this
I have brought two new lives for you to
wise for me Jade you shouldn't have
is this an honor of my birthday next
week
[Music]
[Applause]
let's took you so long
gather the girls made me out fun
what do you go
silly American fish
I am mr. stern
[Music]
hello to you sexy lady come to Jafar
come on so here we've been about today
you do not scare me really I am Jafar
really little little Oh
are you gonna do what I tell you to yes
I hope so I have to punish you I did see
what we got here
Oh sounds like fun for me
but don't start bathing right Missy
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
come on
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
you asked for a distraction I'd say
they're pretty fucking distracted yeah
I'll give you that
so I found the bomb I diffused it man
about a roomful of jeep so we get that
hell out of here let's go
[Music]
what I left it back Rachel get down
Rachele my mother kicks harder than that
Oh does she
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'm sorry but I don't think it's such a
good time for fishing are you okay I'm
okay you okay you would shoot an unarmed
woman would you I would never do that
use my bare hands
so I can feel it
[Music]
you bitch
[Applause]
[Music]
the sexiest thing I've ever seen and
scariest to
[Music]
oh now I'm an idiot mister I gotta have
you now wait I did a tickler 20 I'm out
it'll still launch it just won't
detonate on impact
well they're gonna have to do some
serious fucking damage as in right for
the White House
Oh God you can't call it back now it's
too late no but I can change the
coordinates
please tell me that it's gonna land in
the middle of the ocean
no better
I said Moorhead not warhead 1 come on G
hi come on
thanks getting anywhere sir Thank You
Watson end of the road for you her side
that's alright I got it in here boy it's
time to be left professionals this guy
is mine this guy belongs to a mutt the
Bounty Hunter who the hell are you I
told you I'm not the Bounty Hunter he'll
know
[Music]
[Applause]
congratulations on becoming an agent
Reichle I always knew you had it in you
sir we thought you were dead
absent oh it was very scary really then
without warning a coconut hits him in
the head out of nowhere he was
unconscious for four days and when he
came to he couldn't remember a thing oh
I was so worried for him and coconut sir
[Applause]
cheers Cheers
oh and congratulations ages eight Thank
You agent agent hey no hard feelings
okay let's get this party started
[Applause]
I thought you'd never ask
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
you