Congratulations on becoming agent Rachel
I knew you had it in you
Unfortunate about your husband
Yes
Well, I could not let my feelings for George
compromise the mission
Oh... Sorry
Sorry!
Sorry...
Nice tits
Does your husband appreciate this?
No... Husband doesn't appreciate anything
Bull(***?)
Dead fool(***?)
Ah, George never does that
George couldn't even make coffee
*** fucking secret-agent *** feels like
Yeah
- You can't teach that on training
- No
I don't need that anymore
George never makes me come
George is a fool
No evidence
Mission complete
- Ah!
(- Ah)
Jesus Christ
George you scared the crap out of me
Yeah? You should see it from my point of view
Dreamed about that damn fish tank again?
Yeah. Things like that.
Thank you
Oh I have my cereal
Oh you think so?
Yeah. I do.
You feeling lucky?
Would you try to come take it?
Oh, I will
You call yourself a secret agent,
no wonder they won't give you a promotion
Argh
Holly bitch
Hey, *** together
I take it as a "no"
Ladies first
Age before beauty
Brains before stupidity
What I meant was you're the stupid one, ok?
(- Idiot)
(I'm the smart one.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT)
I ***
Everybody knows that
No
Oh...
Oh no
Oh yeah, you want some of this
[composing phone number]
[phone rings]
I *** you like a readheaded stepchild
Oh no you didn't!
Can't believe you stick my spot
Oh, is this your spot?
You're dirty. You're dirty. Damn it.
(Hi Rachel)
Morning fellows
(Good morning)
I made brownies!
Who wnats some?
You don't have to do that I had
I had to park 4 blocks away
Well. Now you've had your cardio.
Those are the last of the brownies, isn't it?
I didn't even get one
Oh, honey... you have to watch your girlish figure
It's not fair Rachel
You know I wanted a brownie
George: life's not fair
That's one hell of a woman
One hell of a good cook yeah well you
Yeah, well,
you try being married to her for 6 years
(SEVEN!)
I'm sorry the lack of sex is making my memory blurry
[beep]
Sorry you got to remove all metal from your pockets
All metal
[beep]
So we're gonna do a more thorough
Ah!
Sam, it's time for a deep body cavity search
(So there I was...)
...surrounded by the enemy...
...deep in the jungles of Bolivia...
...unarmed and then suddenly I...
Agent Z?
Yes Sir
You're late
Yes Sir, there was a malfunction at security
*** Sir.
- Malfunction...?
- Yeah
I'll tell you what...
I've got a big mission for you
What?
(Yes Sir)
Go down to the break room
and give me a cup of coffee
[laughs]
You know how I like it
As I was saying, bullets buzzing over my head
I had no weapon
Suddenly, from the canopy above,
came the enemy: *zeeee*
- Hi!
- Argh!
Oh... Hi Amy
Ah, sorry, I didn't mean to startle you
No, it's okay, it's a middle of on edge(***?)
Too much caffeine
Well, I must compliment you on your cat-like reflexes
Oh...
Yeah, I was... uh...
Comes with being a secret agent
I'll have to be a little bit more careful around you
I didn't know you could be so... dangerous
Yeah, that's... that's me: dangerous
You know you could lose an eye
[laughs]
Hmm... Speaking of danger,
I have something to show you
Won't you come in?
How... cool!
(Wow)
[amazed laughs]
This is cool!
What does this do?
Oh, be careful with that,
I'm having a lot of problems with it
[George's smelling]
It contains nerve gas, but it keeps leaking
A mini supercomputer
Complete. With wireless internet
Digital camera
MP3 player
Cigarette lighter. Even an AM/FM radio
Can I have it?
No
What's this?
Um...
That's...
That's... That's my vibrator
So you're planning on doing a little fly-fishing?
Oh that?
That is my pride and joy
It's impenetrable
Watch
[gunshot]
Wow!
You're crazy
Watch this
[sound of arrow]
Okay, I get it.
This vest is specially designed
to increase the adrenaline and
testosterone of its wearer
giving him more strength, endurance
even enabling him to run faster
Well you think he could have made it
a little bit more fashionable
I mean it looks like a fishing vest
Do I look like I know anything about fashion?
Oh..! No no no, you know...
No, the vest works. It's um...
You know it's just got lots of...
...convenient pockets
It has an internal cooling system
that regulates body temperature
and increases stamina
Imagine what that could do for you under fire
Just think what it could do for me in the bedroom
I already have
George: [um-um]
This is my latest invention:
Training goggles
It can create virtually any situation imaginable
Really?
From flying to combat. Try.
(Okay)
Wow
That's cool. You do anything?
Anything
- Anything?
- Anything.
You want to ***?
You don't know how long it's been
Oh god you're naughty
Oh yes George take it
You know you've always wanted that type
of fucking ass of mine
Alright in that tight fucking ass?
Okay, that was a little weird
You don't know how long I've waited for that
You tricked me!?
You lured me down here to take advantage of me
you... you gadget siren
Oh... So...?
Oh come on you know I like you
I'm married! ***
It wasn't real
Felt real!
Don't! Don't touch me!
Predator
[Rachel's smelling]
Where have you been?
Huh? What?
You've been gone over an hour
X was looking for you
He was?
Yeah. He needed his coffee
Oh, yeah, right
So?
So what?
So where were you?
I was taking care of business in the lab
Business, huh?
And was this "business" wearing a white lab coat
and reeking a fake designer perfume?
What are you talking about?
Don't play stupid with me, George
That little trollop: Amy
What about her?
George I'm serious, I know that you know
that she knows that we're having marital issues
She's like a vulture waiting on the wings
You're a crazy Lady
Haha. I'm crazy?
I'M CRAZY?
I'm not the one was provoked by
a glass of milk this morning
I'm not the one that hassled
the security guards,
and we won't even discuss your bouts
of mourning road rage
WHAT??
I did not harass those security guards
you set me up, and for your information
they proceeded to get very intimate with me
I guess I should be grateful
because it's the closest thing I'm
head to sex in months
There you go again: always with the sex
We know what George?
Maybe if you learn a little technique
instead of humping me like a drunken Chihuahua
I would be a little more willing to participate
- Really?
- Yeah!
Really?
Is there a problem here?
Together: NO SIR
Good
Rachel, I would like to see you alone, please
Absolutely
- Z?
- Yes?
- Where's my coffee?
- Coming up, Sir
"Where's my coffee?"
Rachel, have a seat
I am sitting, Sir
Right
Rachel, I need you
Excuse me?
Your help.
Oh
You're the only one that I can trust I
I have to go on a secret mission
No one here even knows about it
I can't help it, but I have a
feeling it may be my last
Really, Sir?
I don't think there's any coming back
from this one, kid
Sir...
Don't cry
It's the terrorists
The Middle Eastern ones
You know... those guys...
mm-hmm
They've developed a plan to destroy the world
and I have to go and steal the magic
ingredients to the weapon
(Ah... weapons)
- Rachel?
- Yes, Sir?
X: I need you to help me save the world
Rachel: Huh... The whole world?
Can you do that? Can you be a hero?
Yes, Sir
Good
Here's what I need for you to do
Take this cellphone, guard it with your life
I'm going to be meeting my contacts
and they are very dangerous men and they
are going to want to know
that I am who I say I am
Do you understand?
Not really, Sir
Gonna take me into custody
They're gonna dial that phone for a code
If you don't give him that code,
or you don't answer that phone
I'll be killed
Now you understand?
Rachel: Huh... I think so, Sir
X: Protect that with your life
From now on, you shall be known
as agent...
..."D"
Rachel: "D"?
Any questions?
What's the code word?
Right
Huh...
Hmm... "Peppermint"
"Peppermint"?
X: "Peppermint"
Now go.
I have to prepare for this kind of mission
But Sir...
[X: tears in voice] Please. Go.
Hmm?
Uh! George!
What... What are you doing?
Here you go, Sir
You know I like two sugars
You're dismissed
[George is laughing slowly]
What's so funny?
You don't actually believe that
secret mission crap, do you?
Rachel: hmm
Oh my god, you do!
That's the oldest trick in the book
He just wants to fuck you
You're jealous
Jealous that I got a mission
You are a secretary
No one's gonna give you a mission
I am an administrative assistant
but I guess you know a thing or two
about not getting missions now, wouldn't you?
Well, except fetching coffee
Now why would you have to go there, okay?
I was just trying to warn he's trying to
get in your pants
Oh ***
What did you say?
I said don't be such an ass
[sigh]
What is there with you in that fish tank anyway?
This is going to be the perfect underwater ecosystem
And I will be its God
You are not right
Yeah
Well at least I'm not waiting by
a phone that's never going to ring
It will ring
Why don't you have a little faith that
he'll accomplish the mission?
You just don't get it
He's not on a secret mission
Nobody knows anything about a secret mission
That's because it's secret, duh!
Honey, you know nothing of protocol
You really think he would tell a secretary
about a secret mission?
I am an administrative assistant!
Let me see if I get this straight:
The story is there's a group of terrorists
and they've built a bomb
and they've threatened to
blow up the planet Earth
But alas this will be his last call of duty
And his fate rests squarely in palms of your hands
You're the only one he can trust
His last hope
Bla bla bla bla bla bla
Rachel: - Huh
George: - Yeah
Listen: that's a story he gave his last secretary
Rachel, listen, don't get mad
[tazzer sound]
George: Aargh!
[Breathes]
That was totally unnecessary
You just tazzed because you're fighting for Agent X
and [indistinct speech]... ***
...getting his dick sucked... *** [indistinct speech]
Do not make me tazz you twice in the same night
Okay
[tazzer sound]
I am an administrative assistant!
[George cries]
She's crazy
Jesus, who are you, for God sake
I think I just found ***
What do you think of this little swine?
Isn't it cute?
Beautiful
It's not to say say what we swine (?)
it's just things with asses you know
it's so much fun say
Isn't it terrific?
You like this little swine here?
Do you like more swine?
This is like the other other pink meat,
but how about some white meat?
Excuse me
No no, seriously let's just take a bite together
Let me, let me lick your hole (?)
Nah, seriously. Oh come one...
Another one for "special agent man"
Thank you
So how do you say your name?
"Lei Mi" (lay me)
[smiling]
Well, if you insist...
Yeah... like I haven't heard that one bi...
Wait a minute, you're not gay?
No
So, you didn't know that this is a gay,
lesbian, bisexual, transgender luau?
Ah... No. I didn't.
Um.
After that name, you know the offer still stands
But you might want to hurry because my country
could call me into service at any moment
As a matter of fact...
I'm expecting a call from the
President of the United States
[phone rings]
Oh... There he is
Hold that.
[phone rings]
Yes, Mr President.
Yes Sir, it's me Sir.
That's top-secret
Of course, Sir
You know you can count on me
Yes Sir. Goodbye Sir
So uh... to some... yeah... everything ok?
Yeah
I'll ship out in an hour
Wow... Then I guess...
Guess we... Better hurry
Call me Mr Secret Agent
Yeah Mr Secret Agent, *** cock in my pussy
Well uh...
... I guess I should be going
Yeah, that thing...
- Yeah the... President...
- Yeah
Jesus Christ...
You bitch!
Oh my god
Are you okay?
[2001, Space Odyssey's theme]
[phone rings]
Don't you *** ?
Oh shit!
Oh shit! Idiot!
Me?
You want to tackle me!
You should've gone *** my
phone at first place
It was my secret mission
But now you've upset my pristine ecosystem
Would you shut up about your ecosystem?
Check it out
Here
***
Thank you captain Obvious
Oh oh my god do you think he's dead
Oh! Oh my god
Do you think he's dead?
No
[Indistinct chatting]
Good morning everyone,
I am agent J from the Washington field office
I'm afraid I have some terrible news
One of ours is missing.
Agent X has disappeared
All we know is he left for an unknown destination
(and has not been heard of since Friday afternoon)
[Rachel's speaking to George]
All communication attempts have failed
and we are forced to use all
of our resources at hand
[Rachel starts crying]
(The search and rescue...)
She's really upset, sorry
You ***
***
Okay!
Rachel, you need to get yourself together
Did you hear them?
- Shhh!
- Terrorist!
What if they bomb the United States?
What if they find out I'm responsible?
- I DON'T WANT TO ***!
- Rachel! Rachel!
- Get yourself together
- Ouch
Ouch!
Rachel, listen!
Did anybody else hear your
conversation that you had with X?
- No
- Okay, good
Now we're gonna march back in there
and we're gonna act as
if we know nothing, okay?
I don't want to go back...
Hey hey hey, you want to be
brought up in treason charges?
No? Have you ever been to prison?
Okay
Now we're gonna go back in there and
we're gonna act as if we know nothing
until I come up with a plan
You got that?
Shake your head yes that you got it.
Good. Now let's go.
Rachel!
This way!
Rachel.
[Indistinct chatting]
(Get yourself together...)
No no no
Yes, this is where the best
place to catch crab is.
[Indistinct chatting]
Yeah, give that
[Rachel coughs]
...toast.
You need to get yourself together.
You understand?
Sit down. Sit
- ***, get yourself together
- Yes
- You undersand?
- Rachel isn't it?
- Maybe
May I have a word with you in private
Hey you!
Bring me a cup of coffee
(Help... help... help...)
So... I understand that your agent X's secretary
Administrative a...ssistant
Right
Well since you worked so closely with him,
(I'm just a little curious who've you overheard)
(anything strange the last few days)
(Maybe notice anything out of the ordinary)
(He didn't discuss anything with you?)
(Mentioned taking a trip?)
(Think hard)
Well, British intelligence have informed
us of a possible terrorist threat
This is not what we need right now
with our biggest agent missing
We're still waiting for more information
to come in from the Brits
I'm gonna go check on some possible
leads on agent X
In the meantime I want you to sit next to the fax
I'm depending on you
Yes Sir
I mean Ma'am
Yes... Ma'am
Not again
[sound of door]
- Hey
What are you doing still here?
You didn't actually think I was
gonna leave you now, did you?
We have our problems and everything
But in 6 years marriage, I ever let you down
Seven. We've been married 7 years
Seven years, four months, two days
Come here
Right here? ***
Come on, in here
You know you don't have to wait with me
I know, but everybody's gone home for the day
I figured keep you some company
Um
That feels good
You like that?
What are you doing?
What? There is no fool around
At a time like this? You're an insensitive prick(?).
What's wrong with you?
Great. Now I'm a prick
Well you know what?
You are a frigid bitch
Fuck you!
No. Fuck you!
[Fax's noise]
You can't really be serious about this
Oh I'm serious
George, wait, shouldn't we
call someone, you know, for backup?
You saw the report: there's no time
The terrorists are gonna bomb
the US in a couple of days
The British agents are already in route
Exactly why we should call for backup
Why? so they could pass the
assignment under somebody else?
So I can get overlooked. Again.
Rachel, I'm fucking tired of
getting coffee and dry-cleaning
So this is about you?
No!
(Well... maybe)
You selfish jerk
I don't think risking my life
for my government is selfish
It's patriotic
Besides,
if you hadn't killed our top operative
I wouldn't be forced to do this
Fine. Well I'm going with you
No. No, no. You're not
You said it yourself:
I'm responsible so I'm going
No way
*** [Beyond the gong telling]
Fine
Yes! My first mission as an agent
You're not an agent.
You're a secretary
I am an administrative assistant
Did you hear that? Terrorist
I gotta call Washington
You're not calling anyone my dear
[guy's screaming]
[phone dialing]
It's me. We've got a problem
[beep]
- Oh like it's gonna work for you
- Tsss
You don't even know code
Um
How did you do that?
Honey, you forget:
in addition to being able to type 87 words a minute
I can hack into anything
Impressed
As you should be
"As you should be"
Wow
Grab the bag
Oh yeah, you're mine now
George, I really don't think there's
gonna be time for fishing
This isn't a fishing vest
This is a high-tech fight enhancing super vest
Right. You know you don't have
to make shit up, George
Follow me
[George's laughing]
That's what I'm talking about
That one of those penis extension things
What?
Feeling a little "inferior"? Are you, George?
I'm surprised you even remember that I have a penis
- Ouch
- Don't touch
- Maybe a knife
(- Hey!)
- *** on that one
- Hey hey
Back away from the weaponry
- I want gun
- No
- George, I want a gun!
How the hell do you expect me to defend myself?
Satisfied?
You've got to be kidding me
Listen: go to the house pack a few things.
Essentials only
I'm gonna go try and secure it right
in here for something... inconspicuous(?)
Try not to shoot yourself
What is all this?
Essentials.
Do you understand we're going undercover?
Yeah
That's why I need some things to disguise us. Duh!
Okay. You know, fine. Have it your way
I don't care if I am not carrying this luggage
Not one single piece
Wait!
This is our inconspicuous ride?
No one's ever gonna guess where we're going
I'm just getting fair
Fine. Get the bags
- I ain't getting the bags!
- George, bags!
- *** bags
- George get the fucking bags
The Falcon has left the nest
Who is it?
The fox is in the henhouse
What?
The 2 idiots are on their way to you!
Ah, what the *** for the god's sake
Okay okay, here we go: capital of Finland
Helsinki
No no no.
How many times do I have to tell you:
Form it as a question
What is Helsinki?
Yes!
Efendi, please excuse the interruption,
but the British are coming
I know this one:
Who is Paul Revere (?)
No, no, Sir
The British are coming now
Here, English agents, they're on to us
Why don't you tell me this?
Uh... Okay...
Scout the area, find out where the
infidels keep their camp
and destroy them
Yes, Effendi
Well, my plan to take over
the world doesn't work
I always have plan B
"Plan B", Sir?
Right, ***
Want to know how much I like that?
Look at this:
Survey says I like it
That's it, fuck my asshole
This is why I'm gonna be a bigger star
Yeah, okay
Love this concept ***
You like it?
This is good camera angle?
Really hot out here
You should put some sunscreen on, baby
(Okay)
- Agents?
- Argh!
Shhhh!
I am Ahmed Abdul Al-ahjeer
Durka-durka Martinez Junior
But you can call me Bob
I'm your contact!
I'm gonna take you to your base camp
Go, get hurry up before we're seen
I work with you guys as an Asian expert
*** from the states all the time
Honey, ***
I've located the British agents
Send 3 men to cut them off at the path
Take no prisoners
Meet me back at the palace
[goat and camel noises]
What a shithole
Yes Watson, I don't see our
bloody contact anywhere
We're gonna have to move fast
Hostiles are everywhere
We need some transport Watson.
Get us a ride
Should I contact HQ sir?
- Nonsense we move in as planned
- Ah!
Now just get us a ride, would you?
What? What the bloody?
What the bloody has he gone?
Watson? What the bloody are
you doing over there?
Hello there, do you speak english?
- Okay
- Alrighty then, um...
- I will take the...
[waiter is spitting]
...brand a double mocha with extra cream
And do you have any muffins?
[waiter's speaking arab]
Hmm... Guess not.
Do you take credit cards?
- Watson?
- Yes Sir
What nerves(?) are you doing?
Having a *** Sir, it's sandbox
Sandbox?
[waiter's speaking arabic]
- Uh, Good Lord
[goat is yelling]
Watson, it's a goat!
It's an indigenous species, Sir
- Watson!
- Yes Sir
Where's the ride?
where's the ride sir yes if you look
IIIIIIIIICIIIIIIIII
very close I don't think there's any
taxis Watson just get us our bloody ride
would you can I take my coffee sir
no quick
don't eat all nuts the helm Africa
Norfolk do not
[Music]
well we stop wait guys my instincts they
tell me there's danger your instinct huh
I don't see anything I think your
instincts are wrong
[Music]
[Applause]
merchants here I come sweetie oh that's
awesome
ha
oh that's dirty
I don't know yeah
honey hello
she's back sweetie
[Music]
[Applause]
haha this had better be good
Efendi I have located the agent south of
the palace but these are different from
the rest they want us to know they are
here it's like they are taunting us and
I think they have the American agent
with them only he would be so bold I
think his name is X hold on a second
[Applause]
agent X is here and you're sure he took
out some of our best men it's got to be
him
but we've captured a prisoner find Abdul
tell him to double the guard watch and
get out there I want to know everything
they're doing they take a shit I want to
know about it okay they take a crap I
don't need to know about that but
anything else I'm gonna know about you
understand and you interrogate the
prisoner okay yes go
[Music]
this room is very beautiful it most
certainly is but not as beautiful as you
your beauty is as expansive as the
desert
[Music]
you are like an oasis Oh
do not fear my power
[Music]
what Oh my maid must have left this
never mind
oh look into my eyes
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
ha
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
you
Oh me I want to him
[Music]
yes
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
yes I do oh boy huh Abdul I've broken
all over the powers for you what are you
doing in my room
not Charo and what is Teddy doing on the
floor
hmm let me explain it explain what that
you have one of Hussein's concubines in
my bed if he finds out he'll cut off
both our balls I will not tell you know
what begone with yourself be out of here
before someone sees you I should think
of ah I sneaked up AHA I should kick
your ass but I have no time the same
needs us dress quickly
[Music]
[Applause]
huh wait a minute
some of my cases are missing
and where's Muffy has anybody seen Muffy
what's a Muffy nothing's my baby we have
to go find Muffy Rachel
get a hold of yourself we cannot go back
all right there's no way she'd survive
the heat of the desert the casualty of
war Hey look is this your shoe bag these
are the new summer collection see see
how easily she forgot about Muffy you
know that could be me out there and that
you'd know the difference good married
six years seven seven years
seven long years
[Music]
Oh
what huh this is not what I had in mind
you've been on that dancing all night
sir surely it's my turn to ride soon
Watson soon remember those hostiles
everywhere I must keep a lookout Oh
close ink I see something in the
distance where look alike southeast of
our position possibly my lens what do
you see what is it don't quite know
Watson I can't make it out
good god I think that he's gotten to me
man
[Music]
that's horses York it's really tight
high-five and gently hold on
[Music]
oh stop but any by yourself agent
Jackson Watson British intelligence now
where the hell were you today
you could have cost us the mission man
what I'm a might pick up I to understand
what the agents are yeah who the hell
annoy you what hmm
I like your camel are you guys on a
mission to identify yourself Franken
agency field agent Z had a command a CIA
you water I'm sorry this is my husband
George he watches the mission files in
our building and I am the directors
administrative assistant Rachel you guys
must be the British fellows who sent me
the facts pleased to meet you all good
god what are you both doing here this is
a Code Red top-secret mission Oh
sightseeing tour okay we'll take it from
here
you two back in the camp while we'll do
recon of the area and Oh 500 hours okay
yes stay close to your tents oh and
don't get in our way
hey I think we can be of service yeah
yes I think you might very good man ago
rusty have a nice cup of tea
well poached honey your reputation
precedes you
shut up Virgil so not really understand
our tensile mmm hell on the fuck are we
yeah those limey bastards who they think
they are secret agents or something they
are oh I have an idea you know what we
should do we should get that nerve gas
but you had and put it in their tent and
then after they're asleep we can go to
the palace until the map to the
warehouse that's a great why do I have
to go gas him in the tent I thought he
was a leader and if I was a leader
that's what I would do
yes of course I knew that I was just
testing you and you did well I want to
go prepare the equipment
[Music]
who do you work for tell me who sent you
where is the camp your silence only
angers me
oh look at the will dog little dog
I'm leave the prisoner with me thank you
dismissed
we'll get the will puppy wuppy
you're so sweet I think I'll name you
jihad wanna dance Sadat's the way uh ha
ha ha I like it
[Applause]
which tent do you think they're in I
think it's that one that one what the
Union Jack yeah that's good yes
[Music]
[Applause]
guys remember the only way inside the
palace office without setting off the
alarm is going to be through the roof
once you're inside the map is going to
be inside the desk guys
[Music]
front door somewhat I'm gonna find the
office right away
[Music]
that was amazing
did you forget how flexible my body is
well considering the fact that you never
let me see it anymore I've forgotten
quite a few things about your body not
now George really
[Music]
Oh Oh what's not full of my head's been
bashed in I think it was this uh those
damned Americans they're gonna get us
killed Watson I think they're Cowboys or
something too much television I'd say
[Applause]
[Music]
what the hell was you thinking you're
gonna get us all killed this is a game
you do anything like that again I know
your what I'll be forced to kill you I
would like to see you try oh ha ha ha
that smarts doesn't it oh you gotta
watch her with that she's like a ninja
Oh
anything you'd like to add
[Music]
we got the map here what done
so we're team now right you want our
help you want our help
good sit sit yes yes we need your help
oh and I also got you yes on here you'll
find all the reconnaissance photos to
get you safely into the house excellent
work my dear what the hell happened do
you mad
oh well I had to take out a couple
guards to fact I killed them with my
bare hands I got rid of the bodies I
dragged them far away
they'll never be found so you know you
don't have to worry we'll come back on
him yes quite the hero he was
oh good job man I was wrong about you
I thought you were just a pen butcher
well we got lots of training to do we
have to go over the hill reports there
Rachel gather Monsen oh that's one
coffee Bertelsen I should say
nice Oh No okay Oh
kevrah come t zue sugars
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
you
[Applause]
I'm okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay now listen up me and Watson to take
out the palace guards here and here
moving forward to the throne room and
take out the Seine Rachel
George take Bob's Jeep go to the
warehouse go to the warehouse and disarm
the weapon by removing the uranium
warhead now don't mess this up is
everyone clear yes sir
good what's in what are you doing
something to remember our trip together
good god man this is not a bloody lads
holiday this is a mission now move out
now dead sheep it's almost paid off
[Music]
[Applause]
take a look take cancer take this one we
have to end the surprise on this idea we
don't go dance place so they have your
silencer and fire
then you go on fire and kill anyone you
come across anyone yes 81 man you can
miss a life cycle yeah where's don't
follow me
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god I've died and gone to heaven
Dorie I'll take out this what are you
doing man never good your training I'll
style sir kill anyone I see it's them or
me that's what you've said conduce me up
you forgot what is to be a British agent
but I find country sir no no no to be
licensed to kill and license to fuck the
finest women the world has to offer
ours is not the time to kill no no no
this is time to what are you doing in
these chambers it is forbidden good
scream I'll just know it don't worry
we would not alert the guards to the
presence of our rescuers rescues you are
here to rescue us aren't you of course
we are yes yes we're here to rescue
we're just glad you're all in one piece
we have not seen men like you before we
only see one man oh that's nice I guess
nice have you seen him holy jesus
Oh nasty you see well yes I do
oh well we must be awful we're gonna
clear the palace to rescue you of course
wait you must do one thing for us before
you leave
you must pleasure us before you leave
this place what all of you oh my god I
did die go to heaven
three
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
British something
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
god damn it
hostiles on the road Oregon do you know
I have an idea I want to use the big gun
Rachel this is not a big gun this is a
rocket launcher whatever it is I want to
use it my turn no yes wait no yes
no you don't let me use it you never
gonna see my make up buddy again oh and
that's any different from now how hot
out here
you how cute you look new
does it camel outfit yeah you know how
much hot touch
[Music]
hey George that's the problem with you
always premature Rachel shut up coming
off good earlier
[Music]
[Applause]
on the way
[Music]
are fired
I think you should try to make it to the
door
maybe it's unlocked come on hop with me
ready
[Applause]
what are you doing I think we should go
by the window and yell for help okay
George that's a stupid idea come on this
way this way go to play don't worry this
way can't believe you blue Bob cheap me
me I can't fucking believe I brought you
on this mission after six years of
marriage you think I've learned my
lesson but no my dumb ass brings your
dumb ass halfway around the world so you
can make me look like a bigger dumbass
unbelievable Wow
little pent-up aren't you yes big cat
man just get a little head just a little
just a little sucky sucky a blow job
here and there have you lost your mind
are you crazy
we're in this mess because you bought
the Jeep this was your fault my fault
how the fuck is my fault are you so sick
seeing a uniform bah bah blah you aren't
busy molesting a rocket launcher I
wouldn't have accidentally set it off
are you kidding me
Rachel give any idea how hard it is to
be married to a beautiful woman like you
and having guys constantly vying for
your attention trying to impress you I
[Music]
know you want to be a successful man
like like Agent X and on top of that you
know every day I still want you just as
bad and just as passionately there's the
first day I laid eyes on you and you
don't seem to want me to to want me at
all
let's hop to short you just you're
obsessed with your job and
[Music]
get a mission it's it's like I'm not
important to you anymore
don't you get it it's because you're
important to me that I want a mission
that I want to keep my head buried in
the work I want you to be proud of me I
want you to what you'd be proud walking
around pity I am proud of you course I
love you
love you too
[Applause]
[Music]
how very touching agent em don't have
shot and it's Miranda why money why else
come I've brought the coordinates to the
White House I'll deal with these
lovebirds later always thought she was
kind of a bitch yeah she big monstrous
feet - I hope the Brits are better luck
than us
[Applause]
[Music]
so why is it Watson we're gonna need a
damn good plan to get past his own
guards yes Hudson I'm on it I have an
idea
[Music]
are you fidgeting just me I know that
sound
what is that did you mean what you said
of course I did
[Music]
[Applause]
still gonna stop them now I don't
all right I'm going to strum the Bob you
create a diversion
okay okay Rachel okay thank you
no I will
[Music]
jean-bob that way oh shit hi looking for
that I tell you gosh donkey fucking will
become a sport bubbly it was never
become a sport who in the right mind
would pay good money to see such a thing
when you know that horses are so much
more entertaining
horses are edited
[Music]
she's never gonna work some faith man
some faith honey become an agent around
lady's Underpants what do we have here
I have two new combatants for His
Highness ah very very nice
I'm thinking I like this one strong my
god how dare you touch with Saints
property he would cut your hand off for
showing such disrespect
now step aside and laugh mm father just
open Farber your pinky oh that was for
me for you what are you talking about
you look like every other guard here I'm
a very handsome man I have a nice
physique maybe you are right
oh I can see you let's go back to our
post okay who's my little jihad who's my
little jihad come on a kiss to Papa come
on don't be shy
there you go Oh jokey hello what's this
I have brought two new wise for you to
wise for me Jade you shouldn't have is
this in honor of my birthday next week
[Applause]
[Music]
wait
[Applause]
[Music]
I took you so long
gather the girls made me out fun okay
got what
well you go
[Music]
[Applause]
ah silly American fashion
[Music]
I am mistress Joan
well hello to you sexy lady
come to Jafar come on my way so here
you've been a bad boy huh
you do not scare me all realized you far
really
little little oh are you gonna do what I
tell you to do
yes I hope so I have to punish you
let's see what we got here
Oh sounds like fun for me
[Applause]
[Music]
yes absolutely
but don't you start bathing my casino
hey show me when you came dinner
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
oh that's cuz meet you
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
and
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
that's right
[Applause]
[Music]
come on teacher that's right
oh you like that you like that
[Music]
[Applause]
yes Oh
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
oh yeah
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
yes yes yes
[Music]
[Applause]
you ask me deception I'd say that a
fucking distracted yeah I'll give you
that
so I found the bomb I diffused it and
about a room full of tape so we get that
hell out of here let's go what I left
the back you enjoyed it short
perhaps you looking for this you know
Rachel get down
[Music]
some Rachel
fibula possess please my mother kicks
harder than that
oh dish how about I'm sorry but I don't
think it's such a good time for fishing
my god told you it's faster cool are you
okay I'm okay you okay okay
you would shoot it on on one would you I
would never do that
use my bare hand so I can feel it ah
you bet
[Music]
[Applause]
sexiest thing I've ever seen and
scariest to
[Music]
can't wait
Oh
oh oh now I'm an idiot miss I gotta have
you now wait I thought you said you are
that thing I did a ticaboo 20 I'm out
it'll still launch it just won't
detonate on impact
well it's big enough to do some serious
fucking damage and right for the White
House
Oh God you can't call it back now it's
too late no but I can change the
coordinates
please tell me that's gonna land in the
middle of the ocean nope better
[Music]
I said Moorhead not warhead one come on
G hive come on faith where am i right
girl let's okay ladies getting any
myself Thank You Wilson end on the road
for you her side that's right I got it
in here boys times we've left
professionals this guy is mine
this guy belongs to a mutt the body
hunter who the hell are you
I told you I must a bounty hunter hell
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
my foot congratulations on becoming an
agent Reichle I always knew you had it
in you sir we thought you were dead not
judge oh it was very scary
really then without warning a coconut
hits him in the head out of nowhere he
was unconscious for four days and when
he came to he couldn't remember a thing
Oh I was so worried for him
coconut sir
[Applause]
cheers Cheers oh and congratulations
ages eight Thank You agent a hey no hard
feelings okay let's get this party
started
[Music]
you ready get out of here I thought you
never asked god
[Music]
[Applause]
huh
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
because a powerful
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
hi
[Music]
Oh
ah
that's
well
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
with the
to
go in
not
faster morning
yes
[Music]
when the gentleman
everybody
Parisian desert stopped me
you
[Music]
Operation Desert Storm
break7
[Music]