Don't worry.
Dr Harper is more-than-capable.
I'm just so scared for George.
Was this really necessary?
Absolutely.
Without a complete identity change your
husband's life was in grave danger.
We received intel that after the capture of Hussein,
and angered four terrorist factions,
they put a price on his head.
I understand.
Yeah. It looks like he's almost done.
Do you want to go in and take a peek?
Yes.
Sir? How much was it? What the price on George's head?
Ah. Four dollars.
$4? Four dollars?
Oh!
Excellent work, Doctor.
That's quite a transformation.
Yeah, this is incredible.
Who is this anyway?
Some famous porn star: Evan Stone.
Agent Z was quite insistent on his new face.
He also thought you'd appreciate... this.
Oh
Holy shit.What is that?
A penis implant.
We had this special order, the extra huge size he requested.
Look at the size of those testicles.
Oh yeah.
Yes. A curious side-effect I'm afraid.
After performing a facelift at this magnitude,
we had so much extra skin.
Frankly we didn't know where else to put it so...
Hmmm.
Oh no waste, he's finally got some balls.
And he will be fully functional in about 3 days.
Yes!
Yeah, while you're at it, Doc, can you laser off those stupid tattoos?
Sure. Easy enough.
Woo.
Three days. Three days.
*Across the pond, British agents Jacks and Watson
have safely returned to England where they continue
to celebrate the success of their mission
the way dashing British agents often do...*
Just as we thought we were done for it,
was to be the end of us,
there was a loud crashing sound...
BANG, missile come bursting through the palace room,
just missing us by inches.
Do you have any idea how difficult is to
operate a successful mission while
dressing with this garments?
What we was wearing is inconsequential Watson.
I'd have to disagree, sir.
It's quite difficult to outrun the hostiles in a skirt.
Enough Watson.
So there we were:
Battling our way through the palace guards,
heavily outnumbered.
The bear in mind. We never expected to make it out alive,
but still we battled on.
We fought away for the flames and the falling debris.
Until we caught up with the evil: terrorist Hussein.
To save the world from impending doom.
- And rescue the harem girls!
- Quite.
Now her Majesty the Queen has decided to Mr. Jacks and I
with the utmost honor.
Yes we ought to be knighted tomorrow morning.
Can you believe that, man?
IIIIIIIIICIIIIIIII
believe that man sir Jack's it sir what
yes
now if you wouldn't excuse us ladies we
need to get our rest for tomorrow
ceremonies slipper sir Thank You Watson
are you sure we can't stay just a bit
longer perhaps we can help you relax
before the big event
yes I've never made it with a night
before well technically we're not quite
know it yet what
Oh
rise to the occasion
George it's after 7:00 you better be up
George if you make me late on my first
day as an agent I'll kill you myself
George George George
what the fuck is wrong with you George
you almost killed me thought you were
hostile hostile or shown hostile if you
don't get up
idiot
what much
yeah back in the day I was was quite the
athlete it's pole vaulting or L or only
but after the sex well that's when she
actually knighted me it was quite an
unique agency got a mission for you go
down and get me a cup of coffee
[Laughter]
that just never gets over
take these authorization forms down to
the labs we can finalize testing on
formula 69
I will take that ever mean to have a
little chat with Amy down in the lab
it's me to do it now you remember what
happened last time we ventured down to
her little den of iniquity I'm thinking
about it your king that's gonna be a
catfight
where are you Amy you little slut
that's right you better hide you know
was gonna come down here kick some ass
yeah
that's interesting hi you're not Amy
no uh Amy's out in the field she's
collecting samples she won't be back
until next week I'm her sister Martha
where are your pants
oh I'm working at a top-secret project
called formula 69 a formula 69 all right
you people are into some seriously kinky
shit down here mm-hmm well you see we've
managed to isolate a pheromone that's
only detectable to females and although
odorless and colorless it induces
extreme sexual arousal and pleasurable
endorphins when inhaled thus clouding
the judgment of any female and when
mixed with any standard men's cologne it
becomes an invaluable tool to our male
agents to stracke and obtain information
from would be females acids mmm God all
you freaks the same well thank you for
the chemistry lesson there doctor no
pants but I think I'll be going back
upstairs we're the same people work now
you don't really think that that's gonna
III didn't mean to actually I'm not
really into huh
so tell me do you think your wife is
actually murdering a me or just beating
her beyond recognition just a thought
Oh harder oh that was a good shit oh
yeah fucking lab whore
Oh fuckin face in my pussy
yeah oh my god oh but your fingers my
ass make you cum yes
[Laughter]
for me
Oh
fucking wet
oh oh you're my favorite
Oh
fucking corner that's me oh my god oh my
god
test formula complete
subject reacted with optimal results
mmm
blast you she got to you too
I can't believe it sir I've got me again
I told you not to drink so much tea this
morning
what's that got awful stench God sir
stepped in dog poop lose the shoes man
just quick those shoes hurry up in
remembrance of elfs given and received
and for outstanding service to crown and
country and on behalf of the
Commonwealth I hereby dub thee sir
Marcus Jack you may rise
agent Z agent D there's an important
satellite transmission for you in the
control room it's the president
go here mr. president this on I don't
get good reception in my office ah agent
Z&D I'd like to congratulate you on the
successful mission and in capturing that
really really bad guy who's that dudes
named dick and capturing that really
really bad guy Hussein I also want to
thank you on behalf of the American
public because they would have been very
sad to have been blown up it was our
pleasure sir
as a personal gesture I would like to
grant you to the use of my really big
boat and it's a fancy one too
to celebrate your anniversary oh my god
Thank You mr. president sir
look at that dick now that's what I call
him is
oh my god you believe it
I'm going on a cruise on the presidents
of both I never get to go anywhere
what well since you're an agent now
excess auditioning new assistants is
replacing me this is a top-secret
mission of the utmost importance I need
for you to take this phone answer it
whenever I call if you don't I could be
killed
do you understand
he's replacing me
okay okay do you understand I understand
what what was the question again
okay you're perfect yeah you're hired me
me no me no me he's talking about me
okay me okay both of you you're both
hired okay stop it
fine so you guys are Asian axes new
administrative assistants huh
no silly respect Harry's unbelievable
but it didn't happen to anyone
it happened to me I must have keep
rubbing it in like that
so Jax sir Jax at your service come look
on the bright side it's not every day
you get into the Queen's knickers now is
it actually she wasn't wearing any was
she come on tea biscuit
let's go slay some dragons agent Jax
this is Walton we have just intercepted
a coded transmission seems that North
Korean leader Joe Hill has hit by large
quantities unknown substance for use in
a weapon mo noobs we are not sure let
the message lose to an impending
large-scale attack we proceed
immediately to weaken keep air force
base your women is already in route and
intelligence waiting to further greet
you be more your halo jump this message
will self-destruct
I hate when they do that that's the
fourth one this week and I wanted some
toast tonight no a mill on the wall
who's the sexiest of them all
any pardon supreme commander sure the
other hole is here to see you
Oh have a wait in my office
and I saw sexy she not resist me this
time ah Jung ho what the pressure
sorry for the interruption commander I
was sent to informing a dr. Kwan has
arrived safely and is now working on
your formula
he was guaranteeing me she'll have
results shortly excellent
repeat emergency searching for nuclear
weapons they will never suspect this I
so smart I genius tell dr. Kwan he has
exactly 24 hours general so hyung will
be joining you to oversee completion of
the attack Oh Jung ho shall we make with
the sex
I hope oh you play hard-to-get alrighty
I've been stretching No
from now on you're gonna be known as
agents T and day you know it is a
terrible thing though to think that you
may not come back from one of these
missions I'm sorry I'm okay though cuz
it's just something that I CIA agents
have to put up with you know wear it
like a badge of honor still the thought
of never and I don't let them touch you
again alright No
hold it okay okay ladies there is enough
of agent axe and listen if you're gonna
be a team we're gonna see how you're
gonna work together
Oh
[Laughter]
ah
the supreme commander will not be
pleased with another failure I'm close
I'm close I just need more time
you are almost out of time doctor
oh I'm the captain of the captain of the
captain of the ship and the captain of
the biggest ship never save the singing
and the captain of the captain of the
ship of the sea
oh mercy
Wow happy and rich
beautiful it doesn't get any better than
this
I can't think of anything to say sir
with me
you want to have stick with me
or do you want to have sex with the guy
that looks like Evan still
what
Oh
oh yes
right there right this awesome
Oh
but gonna fuckin come yeah yeah fuck god
are you
whoa captain you have worn me out I
think I'm gonna go have a nap before
dinner all right you do that now what
are you gonna do with that this that
dangerous seas you got to be careful
there's pirates around I'm not afraid of
pirates
no they're marking that one I got this
baby it's the last of them
so how's it going well I'm using
satellite imaging to look for a bunker
or warehouse but I can't find any sort
of structures especially nothing large
enough to store weapons
well cube searching on chap so Jax is
gonna take her
so Jax can kiss my house this better be
good
the Supreme Commander does not like to
be interrupted during his mani-pedi the
tests have been successful
the formula is now complete
Yoho have you called to reconsider my
offer to make the sweet rough
hello hello hello
I'm so horny so horny as right really
gorged that's just me on my throne our
wrong with my puppet
I'm so horny I don't want to be ranked
virgin no moon there's no body for this
pint-sized dictator so much just leave
it go
I'm so horny
very soon this shit
come on it if you want to live
Rachel Sam I fall it's not my fault
Rachel don't be mad don't be mad how can
I lie be mad you just say the
president's yacht anyway I fell asleep
down my rocket launcher you and that
fucking rocket launcher what I don't get
is how the doctors were able to fix your
tiny crooked little dick they couldn't
do anything for your pea brain yeah
that's right you have to be the
stupidest person alive actually wait a
minute now
that would be me because I married your
dumb ass but but you are definitely the
worst secret agent in history you take
that back no take that back Rachel nope
fuck you George hate you I hate you more
I hate you forever in eternity time 20
I should have let you drown that's
coming from a guy in water wings
you can't even swim George
fucking idiot unbelievable there goes my
raise
I'm still not sure how you intend to get
the American public to just poison
themselves ha that's how that one Seng
no redneck and resist this weekend
they're gonna have their silly horses
you like they enjoy their last how to
cook out ha ha I know
I am so
and all
I mean I her I mean I read
you said you'd call
you should go to anger management
obviously you
[Laughter]
ya fuckin ass
yeah yeah
he'll be back he'll be back
George always comes back
what if he doesn't come back
I don't attend together
well
here we go hey big jungle oh babe
Randall's important in a jungle I'm a
smile let's have food they have the
water water
[Laughter]
maybe copy copy be nice nice hot
you must be the jungle to survive the
jungle I'm never gonna get out of here
alive
[Laughter]
and it's mine
well
I don't need no return you know that I
hate you
I am the kings of the jungle and the
king of the waterfall
stupid idiot he'll be back
ma
George Oh George is that you
George
George's is so not funny
oh that's my favorite
Jax Rachel what what are you doing here
are you on the mission
yeah mister I don't know he doesn't tell
me anything
oh okay I think it's clear
let's move quick let's move
you uh don't likely be needing these
Thanks
so you're really sir Jack's now huh I
can't believe you guys got knighted
oh well well one of us did things didn't
go quite as planned for Watson really
what happened I want to talk about it
okay but Sir are talking rubbing it in
my face that was so sensitive man let's
just brief Rachel now would you
well as you know this island is the
smallest of the group belonging to North
Korean leader Jong Il
now a British intel has informed us that
he has hidden some sort of weapon here
in preparing for attack we've been using
select imagery to scan the terrain for
any photographic element of anything
man-made existing out here so we began
searching the island on for two days ago
thinking perhaps jong-il had stashed the
weapons in a cave that's so far we've
had no luck hmm have you guys consider
the possibility that maybe it's
underground no yes okay here I'll hack
into one of the USS heat-seeking
satellites reposition it to scan this
island see what we can find
Wow
he really did and your top secret
clearance now didn't you could you doubt
me sir Jack's never again my dear never
again look it's working good god it's
been right beneath us the whole time it
appears to be about a mouse some of us
oh my god what we have to tell George
George look Jesus where is the old chap
oh nice yeah very nice statues in Hudson
Derek nice wonderful please
oh look at fire oh oh that was painful
oh thank you No thank you very much I
could have won that was hey oh hey whoa
time out time out
hold on time out time out whoa secret
wedding ring
I know it's means something to some
people but to other people it means
nothing but to me I love Rachel
whoa Rachel Rachel nothing Rachel loving
Rachel whoa something else is up beside
Rachel hello hello okay whoa skip some
it and stop it
I'm getting wood hi I'm getting good
whoa getting wood skinny wood oh okay
okay just a little bit just a little all
right just a little bit ah okay okay
okay all right I wouldn't want to be
rude
[Laughter]
yes oh yeah Oh
one of the security details found an
intruder on the beach would eliminate
she escaped from a bitch she have my
name - DG bruh
George don't move slowly
my job coming Rachel what the agent Jax
meet my new friend Rachel Wow top secret
pheromone spray formula 69 females find
it irresistible obviously the species is
not a factor No
so what are you doing no time for a
siesta Watson come on get up
what happened fainted that's what
happened yes twice
that's one crafty burned
I don't get it what could it be hey
anyway it's George he couldn't have gone
that far
who knows have you seen the shape he's
in
look this is his floaties he couldn't
have gone far
so so what I think it is cannibals
cannibals there's cannibals here what
does that mean for Jorge number one
buying you prep horseshoes check number
to update my my appraised page yeah
check number two II brought something up
okay
check number four
father Moore originally children
about to be check jung-ho I need you we
consider my offer
we can make beautiful evil offspring
together intruders were discovered in
the island commander don't just stand
there looking cute with your dragon
faith in your big cans go get them and
it's Twitter oh wait
tell me I sex Rachel I'm sure he knew
how you really felt
I know what I'm afraid of you see the
last time I saw George I hit it with
to George a gentleman spy and a great
soldier
well Rachel many comrades fall in
Spearman's
it is the nature of our business George
died saving his country you should be
very proud
hmm you're cute
you sound like that little insurance
lizard on the TV huh we should make out
huh
Oh
I do love a natural
nazy Tiger think you're doing you
touching my leg put your leg neck what
my user what sir don't don't move what
is it doctor was it yours
No
guys I think somebody's out there how do
you know I don't know I just I don't
know I I can sense it
oh you can sense it can you I think my
highly-trained instincts would have
alerted me to anything is going on out
there
right so how'd you know that
Oh
got the big gun now sorry I'll be over
here
oh good job buzzin
yes sir bangs huh or the other
here's a
can we better get it ready there could
be more coming so sure
Hamels it's the sign of the sacrificial
drums you don't think George
could be
wait a minute that's not George looks
like that porno shopping yes it does
what's his name Evan Stone sir ah well
that might look like Evan Stone but
that's my George new-and-improved and
all the right spots on my dad
oh how are we gonna save him well sir
Jack's great instincts tell you know
we're gonna need a distraction what kind
of distraction there's so many of them
I think I have just the thing
hey Rachel
what are you doing here I'm rescuing you
now come on let's go rescue I don't need
to rescue not from someone like you
these these are my people and they they
love me unlike you right well your
people are going to eat you
yeah somebody's jealous
no you jackass look around they're going
to eat you they're cannibals yeah
[Laughter]
fantastic
ladies oh come on what he's good enough
to eat it I'm not what a bloody hell
with you I think we should get out of
here I'm trying to come back yes good
idea
Oh George have you heard I'm so jacked
now hey does anybody see Watson okay I
think we should split up
Watson I will head to the mainland and
take out jong-il Rachel George you stay
here look for the underground bunker
corner the sunlight images directly
beneath us entrance has to be around
here somewhere
nobody's waiting offshore - again again
the hell did he mean by that what I mean
what the hell do you mean by that
you were fantastic don't start with me
George I know what the cannibals do to
people before they eat them that's right
I watch the Discovery Channel I know
what cannibal do before they eat there
don't worry I watch the Discovery
Channel I don't get it Jack said the
hatch is here can't find it
are you looking in the right place I
don't think Jax knows well what Jax is
talking about oh really
and you do let me get this straight you
who st. the president's yacht got us
stranded on an island almost got
yourself eating by cannibals Wow
why would I think you know how to find
it oh my god honey you found it like on
what the hatch oh yeah
I found the hatch you dipshit look what
oh the hatch huh yeah what open it yeah
all right not like that try the handle
go after you sir
down there down there from there down
there down there down there
what watch it just if we don't make it
out I'm gonna tell you I'm sorry I said
I hated you I don't hate you I'm sorry -
I'm sorry about everything I'm sorry
about ruining our anniversary I'm sorry
you didn't write it and hey this is a
memorable right right I think I see
something up ahead
what are you doing
I'm gonna call headquarters they have no
idea where we are or what's going on
that's right
it's weird no spots
Oh
oh yes call for distress Karthik what is
all this stuff anyway barbecue sauce
that's kind of weird Georgia still the
vast of a poison has been mixing to the
sauce all other bothers are packaged
ready to be shipped the supreme
commander shall reward you for your
dedication to this cause by this time
tomorrow these bottles will be on their
way to every American grocery store
[Laughter]
not if I can help are you go ahead Nick
would you just army and hit me the nose
at the same time Jordan let's see how
you do with flying grasshopper alright
men to Messer let's see how well you do
with a broken back
bitch
[Laughter]
- a machine gun
George what are you doing I just killed
the most deadly midnight assassin ninja
Shah and master of the world has ever
known
he's right over there you don't have to
lie
I quit fucking around let's go let's go
on the chopper let's go let's go men and
women excuse me mr. president there's a
very important call for you on line one
I told you I'm doing important
president's stuff and I don't want to be
disturbed tell that dick to take a
message okay
will there be anything else yes
what's the capital of Florida
uh-huh it's Tallahassee but that's Texas
sir that's Texas yeah you know your home
state yeah yeah t e x ma thanks clean go
got figure out a way around like God
loading the bloody entire army oh my
dear you do what take out so good idea
I'm bloody stop
take out ain't talking about take out
I'll be thinking about our stomachs it's
kind of time hello do you speak English
this flood but no idiot its barbecue
sauce mmm
god damn it Wilma it's the third time
this week I've had to come looking for
you and where did I find you where did I
find you on the other side of the other
words like goddamn coconuts again I
can't take it anymore please Wilma I'm
sorry
I'm sorry it won't happen again I'll
take you to the mall I'll buy you those
shoes you've always wanted well got a
couples therapy I'll do what do you
think I guess so
a volleyball or something like that a
lot of work shit on this island yeah
let's get out of here
what is that takeout sucks
the special
Oh complement or for mr. the Supreme Kim
Oh me
good job man come on good job
Mesa I don't know just check every door
honey
Rachel what are you doing my first kill
you can't
it'll cost too much commotion we gotta
rescue the Brits
[Laughter]
Oh
now that was a sire was it not good god
man what are you doing
don't worry sir I know what to do
mutton no no agent II take an axe
choppers on route me just on the roof in
half an hour
John gage Nets rooftop and happy
it's over here sure that this way you go
ahead have an idea there are other ways
many ways to make you talk
No
[Laughter]
Watson don't do it man get all yourself
and after my parents divorced I went to
live in the English countryside with my
Nana she made the most rubbish carpet I
tell you and I storms they would have
died for about auntie Gertrude
sure Oh wrong with you man huh
spare anything cause for the animals
what about your training all right
no wonder they didn't make you a knight
get out of my sight going gonna have
training comets with your fucking Nana
god I never want to see your sorry face
around here again
enter who are you but the temp agency
sent me
oh I bring you midnight snack Oh
most excellent I starving
what this is damnation just right tell
you that's right the taste of your own
medicine yes my first kill right well
done my dear thank you well looks like
the missions country is dead
where's Watson don't ask who cares
well looks like the missions complete
then I'll guess I'll be off come in
Pegasus
this is agent Jack's requesting
transport out o diligently
what was that about some kind of lover's
quarrel
right well let's get to the roof
agent X should be here any minute
well well I had in this way Rachel too
bad really
Hey then just stay up
poor dumb secretary huh huh I'm a double
agent
no I don't believe you you are evil
Rachel good
come in headquarters necesita Knox
mission aborted
I repeat mission
damnit who's there
you