[Music]
[Applause]
hi Linda hi Marie
you'll never guess what just happened
well my boyfriend um my hair I see the
carrot was bothering him you know you
put it up the ass yeah yeah oh God well
first I was really into it
for this video I gave my chance for real
yeah loved it
oh she was into it
oh god was great
would you like it that way so what I did
was I took my old Dylan yeah shut that
up
yeah
oh god when they were both going put oh
let me try that on
I'm still on prom serious it's just
something very essential another place
is do enough well do you have an answer
are you playing with yours I'll wear
them going to get back to some other
business one does so on I'll see you
later okay
listen forward okay bye-bye
mark I just heard a message I'm sorry
oh yeah uh-huh my girlfriend Marie her
boyfriend fucked her up as doesn't melt
down a good sliding yeah I guess
oh it's just like you really turned me
on
um you know my girlfriend Amy she's
coming over later I thinking like maybe
you and her you know can like take turns
like me out the house I have a dildo she
could you okay good night father
why yeah that'd be great women just
imagine ooh do so Oh God it gets me
really hot anytime