-Subtitle production and distribution
KUKUDAS.COM
Shoko Akiyama
Good morning
It's a little cold today
I know, right
I'm always sorry
The hallway cleaning was originally done by a janitor ...
No, I love cleaning.
Besides, I'm a full-time housewife, so I have a lot of time.
is that so
I'm sorry, sir
You are an angel.
Oh, what is that?
If you have such a beautiful wife
Will your husband be happy too?
Because you're speaking like that
I'm a little shy
Then I saw
A truck arrived at the entrance to the apartment a few days ago.
It looked busy
Who moved?
Then I saw
Someone has moved in.
I think I'm a single man
Oh, I see
I was forgotten.
What is it for?
this
It's a circular
-I forgot to give.
Although this is an internet world,
Would it be outdated
You bother
If you see all
Give it to the next person
I know
Thank you always
Then I'll ask you
-Yes, good work.
That's right, honey
There is a place I want to go on this holiday
Where do you want to go?
Home center that is said to be new
I really want to go
Is there anything you want to buy?
Not particularly
I think I haven't been out with two guys recently
How about sometimes?
Yes
I'm sorry, I can't do it on the next holiday.
The manager asked me to go golf.
How can I not?
No
It looks like there are a few people coming from
It's like entertainment.
like that...
The next holiday
I will somehow make excuses.
Sorry
Ok
Who is it? this time
It's different
Yeah
Good morning
Who are you?
I moved in next door
This is Yoshida
I bought it as a commemoration
It doesn't matter if you don't care.
No, no
Get
Then thank you
Honey
It's the new Yoshida statue.
Thank you, for your concern
thank you
No, no
You're busy, excuse me.
No, we are
then
-Yes, Thank you
To celebrate the move,
Isn't it rare these days?
Yeah
I ate well, I'll wash and come
The married woman who committed her husband while she was away
I had a bad temper because of the need for dissatisfaction.
Hello, Yoshida Sang
Good morning
You're home at this time.
Yeah
What is going on?
Yes
I just moved in.
I think there is a problem with the capital
I called a contractor now.
i See
Didn't you check?
No, I was going to be inspected.
Due to the delay in moving,
So I thought I'd do it over here
So this is what it is
like that
Stop the company I worked for so far
What to say
Because I am unemployed
i See
If there is a karma,
Are you saying you can't use the bathroom?
I said it was over soon.
I rarely finished
-Oh my goodness
there
Would you like to use my bathroom if you like?
It's okay?
What
I'm the only one at this time
still...
I want to repay you for yesterday.
Not specification
Okay
Then I will do that.
Mrs
I lived
It was breathtaking.
-Breathtaking
That ’s good.
How about a car if you like?
no...
My wife
Married
That's a little ...
Tea is fine.
no
I was really trying to rent a bathroom
thank you
is that so...
Thank you very much
Yeah
Then see you later
Honey
Huh?
Tonight
I met Yoshida who just moved in
Huh
I think the capital is broken
I rented a bathroom
Are you listening?
uh
so?
Because
I told you to drink tea and go.
I refused to say sorry
He was a very good person
like that
Honey
Sorry, tired
still
I haven't done it recently
No?
Honey
Is it over already?
Sorry
I have to go to work early tomorrow.
I want to do more ...
Next,
Let's
good night
Hi, Yoshida
Yeah
Hello
Why do you do that? Yoshida statue
Then I see, Madam
The circular is back.
Can I carry it later?
Ah yes
What are you doing? Yoshida statue
What are you doing
Do you do it recently?
Daily
Excuse me?
What do you mean
Madam
Are you seducing?
I have no idea what I mean.
there
now
I got the circular
Would you please leave?
Weird
Last time
Drink some tea and go
You told me
desire
Complaint?
This apartment
The wall is thin
All clear
Yesterday
Earlier
alone
Did you do it?
My husband
Aren't you playing opponents?
What are you talking about?
I'll call someone!
Go out!
In fact, me
I've been interested in my wife since
I lived nearby
Yeah!?
before
When passing this complex
I saw my wife by accident
I think it would be nice if we moved here.
continue
I was watching
To my wife
More
I want to go closer
I moved here.
Yeah!?
I am complaining about my wife's needs
I'll solve it
Than masturbation
I will make you feel much better
What are you talking about
I have a husband
Don't come any closer
My wife is bad.
Font to hear strange sounds from daylight
Think about this position.
I can't stand it
Do not
Do not touch
Let's enjoy it
Hate
I'll call someone
Nobody at this time
Hate
Every day making a weird sound
You're comfortable, right?
No, don't.
Let's enjoy it, Madam.
Do you want to run away?
I like it quite a bit
Run away
Put this
Hate
Do not
Isn't this good for you, too?
Hate
Force being forced
You can't like it
It's good?
I kept watching
That hated look is awesome.
The nipple is already five?
Hate
It's five nipples
Don't you hate it?
-Hate!
I know everything
Hate
what
Do you want to kiss?
Hate
Let's enjoy it
Sam's sweat
delicious
Hate...
more
Let's do something good
Do not come
Do not
Mrs
If you make so much noise
Can you hear me?
Because the wall is thin
Good
A body like this
Let's look back
Want to do more?
-Hate
like this
Hate
Didn't you masturbate like this?
Rubbing her pussy
no?
If you don't tell me, you don't know, madam
No
Is it wet?
I'm not wet
Show me
It's wet
T back
what is this
Do not
Why are you so wet?
If you ever want to touch
-That's ...
Did you think?
I never thought about it
Do not lie
Then what is this
Nice ass
Hate
It smells good
That's a really nice ass.
Awesome, ma'am
Can't you run away?
I'm just touching
look
Hate
It's getting wetter
Are you a married woman with a need?
No
Hate
Awesome
Boast
What cup?
What cup? this
let me know
Good expression
It's a look that I want to suffer
Mrs
Hate?
I want to do
Almost want to suffer
Isn't it an exquisite harmony?
Hate
Below?
No
Sexy
You said you can't stand it
No
Didn't you touch it here?
Hate
It's so wet
Why are you wet?
let me know
It looks good
Show me
I'm biting
Because it's noisy
It's getting wetter
Your body reacts, right?
tiring?
I'll play with you
Kill
Dissatisfaction
Dissatisfaction? you
Dissatisfaction?
Look at my horny cock
I'll put it
No
That's not enough
what?
-No
No
While getting wet like this
Pussy wants it.
No...
It's killing too
As expected
I'll put it deep
Hate
Awesome
No
Quiet
Do you like to put it deep?
No
stop
I'll do it
Aren't you shaking your back yourself?
Isn't it a pervert?
Then I will do this
Open your anus
Show me
Hate
Do you feel good?
Have you ever gone?
I'm done
Come on
I'll put you in more
Feel good?
Come on
wait
Wait
Where are you going
Do you like this?
Is this good?
this
Good mood?
Do you like my cock?
Do you feel good about my cock?
Mrs?
Are you moving your waist at will?
Good mood?
This makes it an agreement.
If you feel like that
It's an agreement.
You are moving directly.
A weird woman
really
It's weird
Yes, okay
bite!
Make it clean
I'm here
Come on, honey
What's up? I don't even light
Anywhere bad?
Huh?
Nothing
Ah...
I forgot Bob.
I'll make it right
OK
Then, shall I wash it first
My body is
I recently moved
By the neighbor
It has become dirty.
Even if you resist
Inevitably
I
I forgave his intrusion
Why ...
But
Unfortunately
The more I remember, the more I remember
My place is
I'm getting wet ...
Congratulations
T-bag or
What is this?
Don't do it
Why is it so wet
For sex life with my husband
Some things were not satisfied, but
What happened during the day
Without leaving your head
It's getting hotter ...
My husband has a body, but
Because I have not forgotten what has been done to others
Within
Another I want
No ...
Maybe
I ...
You may have wanted this kind of meeting.
Honey
Honey, I'm sorry
I ...
Madam
You are moving your waist freely?
Good mood?
No
Don't do this
After all, Madam is the best.
Do not
Mrs
Days before
Did you tell your husband?
How can you say
Right?
I didn't tell you
Our relationship
Does that mean it's okay?
-no
It can't be.
In addition
I want you to do that
Wasn't that what you were expecting?
no
No
After then
Didn't you have sex with your husband?
So wet
Don't touch any more
Didn't you want this?
turn around
No
I'll drive you from behind
I...
-Extrude
No
I got wet like this
I'll drive you deeply
Do you like it?
Feel good?
No
Are you there? I'm a manager
Mrs?
Madam, aren't you there?
I'm a manager
Yeah
Mrs
You were
-Yes, what are you doing?
The mail arrived
Mailbox on the ground floor
Sorry
-I wonder if you are there.
Thank you on purpose
Today is hot
It's hot and cold, and the intersection is getting worse.
Iknow, right
Am I like this?
I am worried about what to wear at this time.
I'm from the Northeast, so it's okay to be cold
Weak in the heat
Is your wife the same as your husband?
I heard that my husband was from Hokkaido last time.
there...
I am from Kanagawa
Oh, is that so?
Then, do you go to your family on holidays?
Because my wife is so young
Father, you must be young.
How about ...
-perhaps
Aren't you younger than me?
How about ...
Oh right
The other day
I sent salmon from my hometown
Salted
I have a lot of hands
My parents
I say I don't need it
every time
I'm sending a bunch
Thank you very much
Would you mind if I liked it?
I'm left alone
I'm giving out every time
Glamour
If left
Oh, is that so?
Then I'll bring it later
A little salty
If you use it as a side dish, the rice goes well
Then I know so
I'll bring it later
Sorry
By dragging a strange story
no
Thank you
then
Mrs
Why
Didn't you make a sound?
Huh?
Did you feel good?
When I always masturbate
To the subject making a loud sound
Mrs
If not
You can stop
no...
Please continue
I just became honest
You wanted to do it too
Then shall we continue?
I really like my body
Mrs
Madam's breasts, really awesome
Madam, it's already hardened
look
Good mood
Your body feels good no matter where you use it.
Best
Want more?
Good mood...
-It's getting tighter, Madam's pussy.
Chuckle
the best
Good mood?
Good mood...
Good mood
No, I think I'm going.
I think I'm going
Funny expression
Do you feel good?
I feel good ...
It's the best, Madam.
Like this, the beautiful wife
With my cock
I'm feeling
Awesome 2
Good mood
I'm so terrified
I feel good
Say you feel good
Please tell me you feel good
Cocks ...
I feel good ...
Good mood
Quiet
Would you like to move your waist?
It looks like rice
Did you feel good?
I felt good
Next
I will come
I
I knew
Only by thinking
To the whole body
The amount of current flowing
I noticed the pleasure
Marriage to be happy
But
Maybe I'm
More stable
Never should be caught by my husband
This thrill
You may have wanted it.
What is it
sorry
I don't feel like it today
like that...
What is it?
Yes, a little
Where to go?
Off
I'm going to buy some
like that
Ok
And I
Like a lie
I did
Mrs
What's up, this time
hug me
Is your husband okay?
please
hug me
Miss is also a wonderful woman
You want me more than your husband
I can't help it because my body is getting hot ...
Make it mess
me
Hold as much as you want
Are you really okay?
Awesome
I can't help it because I want to
like that
You want that
Would you like to go to bed?
Mrs
Touch it
Can I?
Can I do whatever I want?
Mine too
Is it really okay?
Even if it's okay
Madam, I feel good
To be so active
It must have been piled up
Touch me too
Please touch below
Good mood
I can't stand it anymore
Can I put it?
Good mood
Good mood...
Awesome
After all Yoshida's cock
It feels good to go deep
Feel good
Yoshida statue
Please drive as much as you can from behind
Good mood
Drive it in
Make it mess ...
Good mood
more
Drive me more
There, I feel good
It feels good to go deep inside ...
No, I think I'll go
I think I'm going, I'm going ...
Good mood...
Make it more messy
Awesome
After all I feel good
I feel much better than my husband's cock ...
Let me go
No
No, I think I'm going.
No no
I think I'm going, I'm going ...
I think I'm going ...
more
Let me go more
Ok there
Good mood
Do you think it will be rice?
Wrap it up a lot here
Wrap it up
No, I think I will go too
No, I think I'm going.
-Subtitles production, distribution kukudas.com-
Honey, hurry up
I'm sorry, the clock alarm broke ...
I can't help it
this
It's been a meeting since this morning ...
Oh yeah?
I'll buy a watch at the supermarket later
Then I will go
-Yeah, go.
Good morning
-Bye
Hello Madam
-Good morning
It's lively and looks good.
Iknow, right
It's not a little hot
Mr. Yoshida, I think I moved.
I think I got a job at a local company.
Yes, I think so
I am not sure what is what
You were a strange person.
Then I see, Madam
At home
I also sent ...
How about if you are okay?
are you okay?
I'm sorry, though.
I'm sorry I just got it
no
I can't eat it all by myself anyway.
Then I'll bring it
Please wait
From him
The Yoshida statue next door is moving out
I never met again
Of course
What happened then
Keep it secret to your husband
Looking back at it
I don't know how many times he had sex with him
I do not regret
And
A new resident
This is said to come to the jar
Next
Someone
Do you want to move?
Shoko Akiyama