Undress.
Now take off your skirt.
I understand, Miura Sakura.
You have a complex about those big breasts.
The boys in your class
tease you,
play pranks on you,
bully you.
You're so pitiful.
You can't even tell them to stop.
You're such a gentle, nice girl.
Undress.
Take off your underwear.
Let teacher take a good look at you.
You're a good girl.
I admit that your body is pure and beautiful.
You know what teacher wants
you to do, don't you?
What is it?
Do you usually sleep this long?
What about breakfast?
I'll get up now.
Wait. I'll prepare it for you.
Excuse me…
Father-in-law,
it's almost ready, so please sit down and wait.
My back hurts.
It's easier to stand up.
Ah, I see.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
How's your back?
Yeah, well... My back is okay
when I stand or lie down.
When I sit down or move around,
it's quite uncomfortable.
What did the doctor say to you?
I have a strained back, so he wants
me to rest for about a week.
Well, you should rest in our house from tomorrow.
Okay.
If you need anything, ask Sakura to help you.
I will.
I'm sorry for this.
It's okay.
Excuse me. Can you help me a bit?
Of course.
Ouch!
I'm sorry.
Let me do it
Thank you.
Did the doctor prescribe any medication?
Yeah, he gave me painkillers.
They don't work.
My father-in-law, who lives alone,
has been staying at our house since yesterday.
He has a back injury that makes
it difficult for him in his daily life.
I've let him have my room.
I know I have to get along with him,
but I just can't like my husband's father.
Maybe…
I'm… a little afraid of him.
My Son's Big-Tittied Bride Pushes Her Pussy Onto My Cock And Makes Herself Cum
I'm sorry, am I being too loud?
Don't mind me.
Go ahead.
I'm closing the door.
I'm sorry.
Dad, let me do it
It's okay.
I'll do it myself.
I made tea for you, too.
I'm sorry. I'll do it next time.
I'll clean up here.
How do you like this house?
Isn't it big for two people?
No, it's a great house.
Thank you.
Ever since my wife died,
I've been living on my own.
It's too big for one person.
So I'm renting it out for the time being.
But…
After Masato finished college,
he came back here
and said he was going to get married.
I was surprised.
I wondered what kind of daughter-in-law she would be.
I'm glad you're a gentle, nice girl.
You're such a gentle, nice girl.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I'm sorry.
Can you give me a back massage?
Of course.
You're not very good.
I'm sorry.
Should I do it like this?
I know, let's change places.
Go on.
Lie here.
Take this off.
Go on. Lie down on that.
This is how you do it.
But you have such a slender waist.
Like this.
Massaging your waist.
This area is very rigid. And so
are the muscles around it.
Also…
I need to massage the base of your legs, too.
Otherwise, your waist won't be able to relax.
Father-in-law!
I have to go.
What is this?
What's going on?
Say…
What is it?
I want to do it.
Since father's here,
it would be bad if he heard us.
I can't do it for two or three days.
Then…
Okay?
Mmm.
Take care.
Thank you.
I leave Dad in your care.
Okay.
I'll be on my way.
See you.
I made some tea.
Drink it.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Shall we change places?
Go on. Lie down.
Father-in-law… Eh?!
Stop…
It's okay, stay still.
This is…
Please stop, Father-in-law…
Don't…
Don't move.
Please stop.
Wait…
That's…
Please stop.
Please…
Be quiet!
Father-in-law…
What's this?
What…?
It's just a drug.
A drug?
You understand, don't you?
Men like me can see it right away.
You say no,
but you can't resist.
This behavior…
is irresistible to a man.
You've experienced it before, haven't you?
When you were in school,
you teased a man, didn't you?
I know.
Women like you…
are unconsciously tempting men.
Your back is moving involuntarily, isn't it?
It's getting hard.
It's getting really wet.
Aahh! Don't…
No?
Can you feel me touching your clitoris?
That's it.
You have a great waist.
There.
Don't…
No!
Huh?
- No!
- Why?
It's getting really hot.
Let's take a look at these.
- No…
- Hmm?
No…
You don't have to be polite.
You're sensitive, aren't you?
How is it?
Let me see this, too.
What is that? Ah!
I'll make you feel good.
That's amazing.
- Look, it's stiffened.
- No…
Here, too.
Ah, don't…
Amazing.
The nipples are so hard.
Can you come if I just play with your nipples?
Such a nice body.
It's hot inside your pussy, isn't it?
Yes.
Stop…
You don't have to hold back.
That's it.
Well?
How does it taste?
Ah, I'll come…
Look at this.
Don't…
You're soaking wet.
It's getting hotter and hotter.
Come on, spread your legs wider.
Yes.
No need to hold back.
Please.
Teacher, please stop.
Teacher?
So that's how it is.
Please stop, Teacher.
I'm scared, Teacher. Please stop.
It's okay.
Please stop, Teacher.
You'll feel really good, in a little while.
I'm scared.
You have to relax.
I'm putting it in.
Ah, Teacher…
Ah, Teach… Teacher!
That's it.
Oh, this isn't good. You're so tight.
There…
Say…
Did you cum?
Teacher…
Don't call me a teacher.
Call me father-in-law.
It's feels good, doesn't it?
My back hurts.
Move your hips yourself.
Now…
That's it.
That feels good.
Why do you…?
You want to sit on top?
Ah, amazing.
Hey, it slipped out.
Yes.
That's it.
Want more?
You want more?
Wonderful. Like this.
Amazing…
Put your head here.
Yes, that's it.
That's it.
Now…
Look here.
Ah, that's amazing.
Yes.
Ah, that's it.
Amazing.
Yes, now move your hips closer.
Just make me feel good.
Come on. That's it.
Yeah, like that.
That's it.
Ah, I'm cumming!
What is it?
Father's here.
Understand?
Here I go.
How was it, having sex with Masato?
Did it satisfy you?
He's sweet to me.
Undress.
Show them to me properly.
Your ass, too.
Come closer and let me take a closer look.
Go on. Start cleaning up.
Hey.
It's dirty here, too.
Look, it's dirty on this side, too.
Hey. There, too.
Look.
It's dirty there, too.
Come on.
You know what I want you to do, don't you?
You know what the teacher
wants you to do, don't you?
Go on.
Take it in your mouth.
That's it.
Touch my balls and lick my glans.
Yes, that's it.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Now suck my cock.
Ah, that's it.
More intense.
Deeper.
Right.
Use lots of saliva.
Now spit on it.
Amazing.
How is it?
Show me your breasts.
Come closer.
Well? Does it feel good?
Okay.
Hold it between your breasts.
Yes.
Father-in-law.
Put your cock inside me.
Not yet.
Please…
I really want to put it in.
Make me feel even more pleasure.
Do it more intensely.
I'm standing up.
Put it in your mouth again.
More intense.
Open your mouth and stick out your tongue!
I'm cumming.
Father-in-law…
Please, I want your cock.
I'm getting old, you know.
I can't do it right away.
So…
All right.
Now, come here.
You're really wet.
Well?
Do you want it inside you?
I want it inside me.
Want me to push it deeper?
No.
W-wait…
You feel good, don't you?
Turn your ass this way.
Yes.
Does it feel good?
Amazing.
Ah, I'm cumming…
How do you like this?
Father-in-law.
I want your cock.
Then do it yourself.
- Myself?
- Yes.
Take them off.
Ah, that's it.
It's getting hard.
Now put it in yourself.
Ah, yes.
That's good.
You move by yourself.
This is nice.
This is great.
Moving your pussy by yourself.
Let me put it in.
Come on, move.
Yes, I will move.
Ah, this is great.
Amazing.
This is great.
Keep moving.
More.
Yes, more. More.
More like this.
Yes, like that. Make it more intense.
Oh yeah.
I'm going to shoot.
Ah, I'm cumming!
Yes!
Wait a minute.
Masato.
I'll be going home tomorrow.
Is that so?
Will that be all right?
I've been bothering you for too long.
That's no problem. It's okay with me.
I'm getting in the way of
you having a baby, aren't I?
Hurry up and give me a grandchild.
What's he talking about?
Saying such a strange thing.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Don't worry.
Let's do it when you my dad's gone home.
Don't you like having sex with me?
I'm sure he will hear us.
Mmm…
Hey, what's wrong?
It's been a long time since you
took the initiative yourself.
Let's do it another time.
Masato's asleep, isn't he?
What are you going to do if he wakes up?
Never mind that.
Back when I played pranks on you,
you didn't like having sex, did you?
That's now how I feel anymore.
I didn't think of you as anything but a toy.
It doesn't matter.
Your underwear is amazing.
I wore it for you, Father-in-law.
Does it feel good?
I want to feel even better.
Can I lick them?
You have such lewd breasts.
Yes, you can.
If we're too loud, Masato may wake up.
Yes.
It's hot in there.
It's so wet.
- You've become hard, too, Father-in-law.
- Yeah.
It's unbearable.
Can you help me?
It's amazing.
Father-in-law, can I suck it?
You want to suck it?
I want to suck it.
Then go on.
Ah, that's it.
Is it delicious?
It's delicious.
Will you let me lick your pussy, Sakura?
Lick it, please.
Amazing.
Your ass is so cute.
It's beautiful.
Ah, I'm cumming…
Hmm? What is it?
It feels great.
I'm cumming.
Yes.
It's so wet.
Am I making your pussy feel good, Sakura?
Yes.
I know.
So lewd.
Spread your ass with your hands.
Yeah.
- I'm putting it in.
- Yes.
Feels so good.
Feels good.
It feels so good.
And I feel good, too.
Ah, I'm cum… ming…
I've been waiting for you.
Feels so good.
Now put your hands here.
That's it.
This is amazing.
It feels good.
Ah, I'm cumming, cumming.
Your clitoris has gotten really hard.
It feels good.
That's so good.
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
I'm cumming.
Come on.
Let's move like this.
Yes.
I'm going to cum.
- You're cumming again?
- Yes.
I'm cumming.
It's inside me.
It feels great, doesn't it?
It feels really good.
Right.
It feels good from behind.
So you like it from behind?
I love it.
You have a wonderful waist.
I'm going to cum.
I'm cumming.
Come.
I can see your ass hole.
Move in a more lewd way.
That's it.
Oh, yes.
Do you like it?
It feels good.
Yes.
That's it!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
I'm cumming!
- That was intense. Did you cum?
- Yes.
- Well, want more?
- I want more, please.
You want more?
- More.
- What am I supposed to do?
Come.
Let's do it here.
That's it.
- Grab my cock and put it inside you.
- Yes.
Yes.
It feels amazing.
Amazing.
More.
It feels so good when you're deep inside me.
No…
No, you have stand up straight.
Yes.
Come on, stand up straight.
Oh, yes.
Like that.
Ah, it's amazing.
No…
You can't stand up properly, can you?
Come on. Let me see you spread your pussy.
Do you want it that badly?
Put it in here, please.
Oh, those hip moves are amazing.
I can't hold back any longer.
Show me more.
Your pussy is so small.
Yes.
- That's it.
- Ah, I'm cumming.
I'm cumming.
Like this. Yes, yes!
That's it.
Amazing…
I can't stop my hips from moving.
Do you want to come again?
More intense?
Do it more intensely.
Then I'll do it more intensely!
I'm cumming!
Yes, yes.
You're so tight.
It feels so good.
No, I can't hold back any longer.
- Is it okay if I cum in your mouth?
- Yes.
Ah, I'm cumming!
Now open your mouth and stick out your tongue!
Now, I want you to suck it clean.
The car is ready. Are you coming?
Yes.
I hope you'll come again.
Well, I'll come back another time, then.
Yes.
I'll give this to you.
What is it?
Well, it's like a tonic.
You have some, too.
It'll increase your vigour.
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
Yeah.