De Mimo Mumime
Subtitle production: Abja subtitles (Jamakav.com)
I'm back ~
Wow, it's very hot
Welcome ~
Hey!  Are you eating ice cream again?
I have two more.
I did not know
No matter how long the summer vacation is,
you still can't get enough to play?
"I'm glad you're home." - Yes?
The mother has to go to prepare for the village festival.
Go home to your Grandpa
to get him some food.
Eh...?  Why me?
Because you have nothing to do anyway,
your Grandpa is too old to handle himself.
I go to her every day to feed her.
Eh...?  Why me?
I don't want to go.  I can not walk.
Today, I made curry. If you don't go
eat with him, your mother will be upset
I don't want to go... Okay, I went to Grandpa
Don't I want to go so naked?
Grandpa Urano is a relative and I am not
ashamed of him, he is part of the family.
- That's right. - Then I'll go.
UnBaLanCE original
I'm Asahi (27 years old) and I came home for the summer vacation. I usually
work as an OL. At my mother's request, I'm going home to my Grandpa.
Umekichi (84 years old) is an elderly person living alone. I took care of
Asahi when he was just a kid. Now my body is weak and I have some dementia.
You will feel good with this grandfather...
Series of female body aches 01 『Asahi and Umekichi』
Wow, it's great... I haven't been here since I
was in elementary school, but nothing has changed.
Ooo!  Buniculee
It's been a long time since I've seen you.  That's right!
Do you remember me?
Grandma ~ I'm Asahira
I came to get you food.
Who, who, who, who, who... Who are you?
Don't you remember, Grandma?  It's been a long time
So... really... Ah... Asahi? Ah
... are you really in front of me?
Yes I am
Ah... I'm surprised
how big you got.
Because I'm 27 now.
Are you an adult !?
So now...
I work at OL
For?  For?  Lani ~
It is very good.
- That's right.
- Yes? But what are these?
Oh, nothing. Bar, Bob? Sorry
"I just asked..."
I can't believe it... Is that really Asahi?
She grew up really fast...
She's a real young woman.
OMG... No No By the way,
that breast... How beautiful is it ?!
Her breasts are huge...!
Besides, is OL...? It's similar
to what I saw on this DVD, right?
Do I think they're bigger than the
actress here? If they are so big...
Her body is very beautiful... She looks
better than the actress in the movie...?
Don't you watch TV?
Ah... that's right
Every time she moves a little,
her breasts shake!
Is it hard to refrain from clutching such a beautiful ass...?
I was trying to masturbate while watching
a porn DVD... I don't need that anymore.
-Grandmother ~ I don't know
where the shredder is. Chopper?
Where will it be...?
Wait?
Here?
Ah, was he here?  I think he was here...
OMG... They have a huge volume... I
want to touch them! I want to suck them!
-Here is!  -Uh, uh... ah...
Now it's okay.  You can leave.
Ah!  It's okay now ~
I wanted to ask if I needed anything else?
You can leave now,... watch TV.
What is it ;  Why do you keep standing aside?
My mother used to say that my grandfather
was ill, so I had to take care of him.
I said I would have... I
think that's the situation.
But he seems too insistent,
he stares too carefully...
Even though I said he could leave now...
I'm trying to tell you something
scary... Would you like to leave me...?
Oh, haha,
I've been in trouble since I had dementia
If you pretend to be insane,
most people will believe you.
I think it's okay if
I look elsewhere
However, the more I look at her,
the more excited I am...
When I see this slender posture
with that arched ass... naughty
I'm so eager now, I want to touch her...
Stop Grandma!  You are too close ~
Hey, it's dangerous to use a kitchen knife ~
Ah... I'm sorry
Stay!  Buniculee!
Kaneko when I looked at you, I fell in love...
Kaneko?  Isn't Kaneko a grandmother?
I'm Asahi. I'm not grandma.
Grandma died a few years ago!
Ah... I thought you were Kaneko,
she came back after a long time...
-Grandpa... What are you doing?
Watch TV until I'm done cooking !!
Ahh ~ What was that?
She has a very nice ass... she is very strong...
Now I have to touch her breasts...
Okay, it needs to boil a little more and the food will be ready
Grandma... If you wait a little longer, it'll be ready
Uh, ah?
Buniculee...
Are all those clothes unwashed?
What is it?  Ah... yes!  they are unwashed
It takes a little while to finish the
curry, and then I'll wash the clothes.
I'm so sorry you have to do this too...
It's okay, I'm in good shape
Grandpa just sits there and rests
Oh yeah... I'm sorry I can't help you.
I can handle!
-I'm so sorry... Kaneko
...- I'm not really Kaneko.
The weather is good and the laundry will dry soon
I'll serve you food right after.
Yes, I want to eat fast.
So you got it: I'm not my grandmother.
Kaneko... you have the most beautiful breasts.
- Stay!  -Oohho ~
-Yes, Kaneko's breasts are the best -No,
Grandma!
It's not Kaneko!
-Kaneko... You liked me to do this to you.
- I don't know what this is!
Kaneko...
-Do not do it! / -You're upset ..
-Your breasts... / -Grandma! Do not do it
I like.  Kaneko... Kaneko...
Buniculee!
-She's the best... -Leave!
-She's the best...
-Do you feel that?
-You're crazy!  -I'm not doing it!
Kaneko... Are you okay?
-Because I'm not Grandma Kaneko!
-Are you feeling alright? Are you okay Kaneko?
Haaa .. Kaneko
Grandma !!
Grandpa!  NOT!
-I'm not Kaneko... Grandma!
Kaneko is not here!
Off .. Grandpa...
I can not...!
Grandpa!
Oh... this bra won't
let me touch it properly
To the shadow... What
can this thin coat hide...
... can you take it down?
I can't get there!
Buniculee...!
I think you're sensitive here
-... The nipple is -No!
That's enough!  Stay!
Grandpa!  I said no...!
Uahh...!
They haven't hardened here yet...
Grandpa... Stop it!
-That's / -No...! -Here is..
Kaneko... Kaneko...
-Are you feeling well here?
-No, Grandpa!
Buniculee...
Now I'm going to do it right!
Stop!
Yes, they are sensitive... They are already strong now
-Ready! Grandpa, it's not fun what you're doing!
-You're so pretty Kaneko!
- Not!
-It's good to touch the nipples -Stop... opt!
Understand!  I'm not Kaneko
-I need to rotate the nipple slightly.
Grandma... Stop...
Grandma... ahh
-Grandpa...
-Kaneko... Kaneko...
Can I suck your nipple?
No, Grandma!
Grandpa!
I hate this...!
Buniculee...
It's not Kaneko.
Kaneko!  Kaneko!
Kaneko!
Stop Grandpa!
Buniculee...!
Stop...!
Stop... That's it
Grandma... I hate... ahhh
Stop Grandpa!
No... Hmm...
Grandma... ahhh
Stop Grandma...!
Ah... Now, Grandma... So hard... I can't
resist... I'm starting to like it...
I feel licked by my grandfather
who raised me since childhood...
Buniculee!  You really can't do this to me!
Stay...!  Buniculee...
And here... are you feeling well...?  It is not like that?
Grandma... Stop... I can't do this!
-Seriously... Wait!
-Kaneko... Open your legs.
Don't wait...!
Not...!
I want to touch Kaneko here too...
-I said no! Not really! Stay!
-Kaneko...
-Are you feeling alright?
-Stop, you are my Grandpa...!
your pussy is very wet...
What do you say about this ?!
I wanted to tell you that
... Kaneko... she's fine...
Grandma... I'm a virgin...
-I have to work harder.
- I hate this...!
Buniculee...
No no no...
Grandpa can't...
-Grandpa... No!
-Kaneko is fine here!
You're so wet Kaneko...
-Where are you going?
-I have to go to the kitchen...
Kaneko... don't leave.  Kaneko...
I can't anymore, Grandpa...!
Do you want to do it too, Kaneko?
Grandma... please!
Buniculee...!
Uahh...!
-You feel good
Kaneko -Grandpa...
Stop Grandpa !!
No... I feel good doing this...
I think it's weird...
Now it's very weird... !!
No no...!
Want?
Do you want Grandpa's dick?
-Ahhh... -Do you want...?
-Eh...?  -Do you want me to put it on?
-My dick... you wanted it!
-You really want it!
Would you like?
I'm not Kanako!
I know, Asahi
When I saw you in front of the house, I felt like I wanted you
You are so sensual...
You have such a beautiful body
So I felt like you were the first woman I would so much like to fuck...
Look, she's very up.
She's so upset that I feel
like I want to rape you, Asahi...
We only do it once
At least once...
Before dying
You could see how well an
experienced man can fuck you
How good is the old dick
Has his grandfather recovered?
Or... isn't he insane?
No... Grandma doesn't
Give me one last gift before I die
How do I persuade Asahi to let me fuck her?
I'm pretending to have dementia... from the beginning
Will you do this for me?
Good !  just one time...
Of course, only once
Now, turn your back
I can't get there, put your ass down.
Now I'll put it on you Asahi...
-Ahhh Grandma...
- I'm bleeding...
-Oh, no, it hurts! - Grandma...
-Do you feel it?  -It is good like this...
Oh, it's so good... In Asahi's pussy...
Sloppy ~
Your breasts are shaking... round and big breasts...
-Since I haven't done it before,
I think I'll let go quickly -No...
I can't... I'll have an orgasm...
I really can't...
Take it out, you'll ejaculate...
Take her out... Stop... I think I have an orgasm...
You are very good...
I take it out because you have an orgasm...
Come in here!
Stay here!
Let's see you... Asahi
Buniculee...
Do you want more now?
Lay on your back!
You don't need panties anymore
Now you want more...
-I need to suck more of these breasts.
- Not!
Do you like to suck your breasts?
-You're very horny now -No...
You are very hot...
Not ..!
I want you to tell me when you want me
No matter how much I suck, I don't get tired
Please...
Good!  So you want me to fuck you now?
-Do you want me to put it in?
-Not...
Then I can rub it more!  so..
-Tell me... that you want her -No,
no, stop Grandpa!
This very sensitive and beautiful
body... you are so good...
Want this...
Do I put it in, or not?
Put it in... don't fool me anymore...
Oh, you really want her
Even if you just rub your pussy, you'll have an
orgasm... I don't have to put it on anymore.
Ah... I have an orgasm!
You feel great! Kaneko... you're
very sensual when you're horny
-Kaneko you're really sexy...
-Grandpa, I'm not Kaneko ..
I know you're not Kaneko
But,
Asahi looks the same as Kaneko.
Asahi is... even better
I want to rub it again.
That's what Kaneko liked best
Can't stand it anymore?
Did the clitoris go crazy?
I have an orgasm...
I want to fuck you in the back
Show me your ass... You
don't even need a bra anymore!
Oooh .. You have such a good ass!
Before introducing it,
I want to make you feel as good as possible
You like it here?
You can moan more...
Ah, yes, that's it
No no no...
Cover me ..
It would be nice if I sucked here too...
Okay... Kaneko,
I feel you really liked it.
Now, we keep rubbing your pussy
-You can't stand it anymore? do you want me to put it on you?
-No... -I can't stand it anymore!
Fuck me!
We need to moisten it more
Do you want my old dick, Asahi?
Say: put it on me! You
should say you want it.
Can I finish otherwise, just rubbing your pussy?
I'm going to have to fuck
this beautiful body... get up.
I'm so excited...
Get in?  Are you feeling well?
Tell me if it's okay...
You're really good...
Is it so good to feel your
cock? Rub my pussy...
With your old dick...
Do you want to feel it?  It is not like that?
Do you want me to fuck her?
Grab it and rub it... to get it up as high as possible
She tried to grab it on her own and put it in her pussy
-No...
-Do you want to put it in now?
I have an orgasm...
I'll take your face
... I'll rub your face
Look at her and grab
her and rub her pussy
Even if I just rub her pussy.
This old man's dick makes me feel so good.
Grandma... is she okay here?
Very well...
I guess I can't just rub it anymore,
because this old man's dick wants to fuck me
Do you want me to fuck you?
Do you want your
Grandpa's cock fucked?...
Do you have to ask me to
fuck you? You have to say it...
Fuck me... please...
Turn your back, fuck your back.
-I have an orgasm... - Do you have an orgasm?
How about my dick, old woman?
It is really very good...
It's nice to see Asahi's satisfaction as he fucks her...
Grandma... come... come...
Fuck me, Grandma...
It's coming...
What a good ass you have!
I have an orgasm again...
Excellent...
Wonderful...
You feel it deep, don't you?
Grandpa... I'm going crazy...
You are great...
I can not take it anymore.
I will die.
-I'm ejaculating... - No.
Don't take it out!  No no
- Not! I can not!
-Now she's lying down...!
She became small and is lying inside...
By the way... I want to
keep touching these breasts...
You said you only wanted me once.
I have to be fully satisfied for once...
What are you doing?...
I'd like to... one more time before I die...
Let me touch these breasts even more...
You are killing me...
Stop now!
Please...
-You said you only wanted to fuck me once!
-And you did it...
You're upset?  Did I upset you?
This is...
There are only a few
days left... I'm sad...
Ah... Kaneko... Why did you
leave first? And you left me...
I'm alone... I want to meet you soon.  Kaneko...
Kaneha... Kaneko...
Grandpa, are you okay?
I'm sorry, Kaneko...
I missed Kaneko... Kaneko!
Grandpa!
You know she's not Grandma Kaneko!
I missed you Kaneko...
What are you doing, Grandma?
Ah... that's good, Kaneko.
Asahi?
Asahi... There are many similarities with Kaneko...
And Kaneko really liked that...
But I'm not Grandma Kaneko!
I know, I know... I know.
So I know...
But...
With Kaneko...
I did this before!
- Grandpa!
-You said you were not feeling well!
Stop!
I really did that...
No... Grandma!
Leave me...?  It is not like that?
Do you mind?
Buniculee...
Will you leave me?
-You mean?  - Not!
-It feels good... - Stop!
Kaneko liked that too...
Kaneko just left doing this...
I'm not Kaneko.
Asahi... Asahi likes this...
You got horny!
Are you embarrassed?
Stop!
Grandpa!
I can not!
I can't help it
You look so nice...
There are many things similar to
Kaneko when it comes to her nipples.
-Asahi... Asahi .. it's similar ..
-No!
Grandpa... Enough...
I'm going to wash... I want to go...
Wait... Wait...
Going?
I won't let you go...
You say you don't want to,
but your face says you want more...
Not...
Stop stop...
Asahi...
Just rubbing your nipples...
is this the first time i woke up ..?
It's probably the first time...
But did you feel good?
-Oh... Grandma!
-You have to make your Grandpa feel good too.
Grandpa, I'll make you feel good...
Ca Kaneko...
And I...
Make me feel good too
Kaneko did this...
Yes, help me live too
In order to let you go,
you should help me feel good too...
Stop Grandpa...
Is it okay to help each other... okay?
Not...
Come here ..
Yes, put it between my breasts.
You do it?
Yes, I do
Grandpa made Asahi feel good.
Now make Grandpa feel good too.
Do it... like this
So?
Ah, that's exactly what I want
Come here and do it...
Rub it between your tits
Good good
Yes Yes
Ah... are you okay?
So good..
Kaneko has always done that...
But, it's nice to see that Asahi does too...
I've never done anything like this...
But you are doing very well...
Ah okay
Ah... so good
Ah... I like it there
Grandpa, is it okay?
Ah... so good
Energy is growing...
It's starting to get up...
Do you feel it again?
Again...
I think she's getting up again.
It is not like that?
Ah... so good
Good...
Something is coming out...
Something is flowing
flow...
Grandpa ..
It's over now.
No, I have to do it to the end...
Yes!  You have to do it to the end...
Would you like me to do more?
It's over now.
Yes I know...
Are you feeling well now? ...
It's not good... what am I doing to you now?
I returned..
What are you doing?  You're late?
Did you cook?
Yes!  I cooked!
Did you have to wash clothes too?
Yes, I washed a lot of laundry
How was your grandfather?
Ah .. It was really invigorating for him... Kaneko
Kaneko, he's been looking for Grandma all day
You must have had a good relationship with your grandmother.
It is not like that?  Did he love her so much?
Oh yes !... look, tomorrow
You take this document to Grandma and you come back.
Well... I have something to talk
to your Grandpa about the festival.
I don't have anyone to
ask for advice this year.
Shall I go again?
You're free anyway
I cleaned the room while you were gone
Because you wasted a lot of time
Ah... I'm tired, I'm going to bed
Grandpa ..
Grandpa!
We came to talk about the festival.
Who are you?
Asahi
Don't say you don't remember.
Ah... now I know.
Yes... you grew up a lot...
The baby... grew up wonderfully...
I'm not Grandma Kaneko!
You were...
I'm sorry you have to do all this...
It's fine.
I'm confident in my fitness
By the way, I have a very lustful body...
I have to make him want me again...
More?  It is not like that?
Yesterday was so violent...
When Grandma Kaneko comes to mind...
My grandfather changes strangely...
I tried to get him out of the dream...
Why are you sad?
I'm sorry, Asahi...
Can you give me a pillow to sleep on your knees?
Kaneko often did...
I'm watching you...
Ha... I was thinking.
I'm sorry... I really asked for that...
Who was it?  Grandma Kaneko?
It is not like that?
You mean Kaneko?
Kaneko...
Grandpa!
Kaneko has always done that.
You said I'm not Grandma Kaneko!
Yes I know..
Are you here because you want to do it too?
Stop it, Grandma!
-Do you want too? -Not!
-You wanted to have an orgasm again.
-Not!
Stop!
I know everything... I know
I came because I wanted to have an orgasm again.
Did you come because you couldn't take it anymore?
Feel good ..
Is it okay to lick it for you?
I said no... Grandpa!
Are you okay here?
Wait... Wait...
No no no...
No no...
Stop!  I'm going to have an orgasm...!
I will lick it even more, to make you feel even better
Kaneko often had an orgasm... like that.
It's cute. Here it is
Grandpa!  Stop Stop...
No more...
Yes, yes... and the breasts
Want?  Do you want me to do it here too?
I know I know..
Buniculee...
-Do you want to have an orgasm by touching him again?
-I told you to stop!
I don't want here...
Asahi has sensitive breasts...
Oh,
I found Asahi's weakness... Here...
Here!
Here it is... here... haha
Correct?
The nipples are hard...
No nipples...
-I'm sensitive...
-Are I going to do this?
How do you feel like that?
I know how to get Asahi aroused
So and so..
So ..
You would be very happy...
To die like that
Doing so..
The nipples will rub and harden.
I need to do more
So... how about that?  How is it?
Grandpa... it's ugly...
I will only excite you with your nipples.
Come on, come on
Now it's Grandpa's turn...
Did you want my dick?
Look at this... it's already grown
He liked that a lot
Is she up?
Do you want to touch?
I want you to touch
Grandpa, it's too much...
Kaneko is...
Kaneko gave me her
breasts and it was wonderful...
And I really enjoyed sucking them.
You get very excited when I lick your nipples.
I can not take it anymore...
Is Asahi excited too? Hey,
you keep shaking
It's getting louder...
It's starting to get stronger...
Grandma... you're great...
Now...
Please suck it for me
I want to see you suck cock...
Yes, there...
put your hard cock in your mouth...
Why are you ashamed?
You wanted that too ..
-It is not like that?
-It's unpleasant to do it while you look at me
Do it while I watch ..
I need to see...
how do you do that...
Buniculee...
I feel good...
Are you okay, Grandpa?
Ah... well, but...
I should touch your breasts.
Do you think the semen will come out?
Do you think you will finish?
What would you want me to do?
Sprinkle them
Sprinkle me everywhere, Grandpa!
Keep doing it like this...!
Ah... get out!
Grandpa, you're full of energy...
Asahi...
What do you want me to do next?
What do I do next?
Next time... What should I do?
Tell me!
What would you like me to do next?
I want to...
What do you want?  Tell me!
What do I want you to do? After I
put Grandma's cum on my chest...
Do you want me to make you feel more?
I want to feel more ..
I want the dick to feel in my Grandpa, in me...
Take this out ..
Take your clothes off!
You wanted it from the beginning...
You wanted your dick one last time.
I'll tell you how to do it
Sit...
Rub lightly... like that
That's how you do it..
How is it?  it's good?
What do you want?
She's naughty
She is very naughty
shown...
Do you want to get wet?...
Do it yourself...
So?
Do it faster...
Want?
Do you want to moisten it?
Tell me!
In the pussy...
In the pussy?
-I want you to moisten her...
-Hhahaha
It is already...
It is sticky and damp
Oh... Asahi's pussy...
Look what came out of it
Very sticky... haha
Let's shake it...
So... loud
So
Here ..
Take your fingers out...
If you do this... I think I'll finish already...
Juisează...!
It's a reaction similar to yesterday.
Do you want to finish?
Do you want me to finish you?
Let me finish...
Are you ok ?
Ah... so good...
A little more... I feel so good...
Ah... I think I'll finish...
Can I go on?
A... I'm done...
I have an orgasm again...!
You have a very sensitive body...
What would you like to do next?
What are you going to do now?
I do not know what to do...
Now...
come here
Ah, I regained my energy.
Should you put it in your mouth?
In your mouth..
Can you suck it?
My Grandpa's cock...
Now here ?
I should see that well
Grandpa's cock...
Wonderful...
Come on ..
Put it in your mouth
You have to put it in your mouth
Ah... you lick her so badly
Turn it over and lick it lightly on the back
.. from top to bottom on the balls
Ah... now you lick her very nicely
Are you feeling alright?
Ah... so good...
Excellent...
Suck it until you feel it rise...
Okay, now, it's really cool
come here
Come here...
You should also take off your panties.
Are you excited?
I really want you
to put it inside me...
Good!
Where and what do you want?
Asahi ..
What do you want?
Want this?  Where do you want that?
I want cock...
Where do you want it?  say!
I want Grandpa's cock... I
want to put it in my pussy...
Then open your pussy
If you want it, open it as much as possible
Try to open it so you can see better.
What you want me to do?  rub it like that?
Grandpa fuck me!...
It's coming...
It's coming...!
I'll fuck you deeper
He went very deep...
Do you like it that way?
Stronger...
I think I'm done...
Excellent...
You are so good ..
I finish, I finish... I have an orgasm again...
Get up!
Climb above me...
Feel it all, how it gets inside
It's wonderful... Grandma...
Yes Yes
you feel good, Grandma...
Let's move together.
you feel good, Grandpa...
Aaaahh .. Deep...!
It's good?
I like it this way...
Asahi...
No... not yet...
Finish...
Do you want more?  Asahi
Grandpa... you fucked me so good...
I love this...
Yes, please do this...
Nooo!  I'm done again...!
It's coming...
Ready...!
Excellent ..
Put it on yourself and rub it
You're doing well Asahi...
You look very sexy
I really like...
I love you so much... ♥
Excellent!... so good
I feel so good that I
feel like Kaneko is back.
That's it... it's coming!  ..
Finish...
I'm ejaculating inside you...
He's not leaving yet.
It's still loud... I'm still not tired.
I can fuck you more than that
Lower your ass a little more
Ah... great
Wonderful...
So good...
Ready...
It's coming...!
No no no...
Termin...
I'll fuck you more than
that to change position
Buniculee...
lie on your back...!
can i sprinkle you  Yes but
you can't download it inside
Oh, no!
I did it, Asahi
Let's do this too ..
Today I will fuck you until I die
Come here quickly
Isn't it too much?  Grandfather
I do not
I can still do it... ha ha ha
I'm still horny... it's cool
I'll get it for you now!
I can't take Grandpa anymore...
I'm exhausted...
I can't do it anymore!...
De Mimo Mumime
Subtitle production: Abja subtitles (Jamakav.com)