[soft music playing]
[Pénélope la bonne]
[birds singing
and Penelope's footsteps]
Penelope: My name is Penelope
and to tell you the truth,
I don't know why my parents
gave me such a name.
My family is poor,
so I accepted to go to work
as a maid in the house
of the town's richest man.
The people are not mean.
They treat me all right.
Especially Marzia,
who's got certain special attentions
toward me.
She often has
very nice gifts for me.
I remember the last one.
It was a dress.
I wanted to try it on right away,
and she gladly offered
to help me put it on.
But that almost perturbed me,
because she brushed against me
not quite casually,
making me excited
and causing my nipples to perk up.
I was saved
from that embarrassing situation
by the Baron's arrival.
The Baron: Is my dear daughter-in-law here?
Marzia: Yes. I'm with Penelope.
Marzia: Okay. You're on your own.
The Baron is calling me.
The Baron: What the heck are you doing?
Can I know?
Just as I expected.
You always dress like a whore.
How the hell did my son end up,
marrying someone like you.
I will never understand.
It's scandalous. But now...
Now you will show me,
how you seduced him.
Come on, get moving!
Very good.
You women always have
this kind of weapon to seduce a man.
Suck it...
[soft music playing]
[The Baron moans]
Penelope: I was still shaken
by her persistent touching,
when I saw an incredible scene.
The Baron was having sex,
with his daughter-in-law.
[The Baron moans]
[The Baron continues to moans]
I got closer to better see,
something that was unusual,
yet full of energy.
I was like hypnotized.
My hands went
up and down over my body.
[The Baron moans]
I felt wet
and excited between my legs.
And I couldn't help touching myself,
without turning my eyes away,
from what was happening,
in from of my very own eyes.
[sighs]
The Baron: Go on, go on!
Suck my cock, come on continue!
[The Baron continues to moans]
You're a whore...
a big, fat whore.
Come on, come on, do it!
Suck my balls bitch.
Come on...
[The Baron continues to moans]
Continue. You like it, huh?
Take it in your mouth, like that!
Yes, sucks, sucks...
Penelope: I couldn't stop feeling excited.
I felt myself throbbing with desire.
I had not tasted,
what a male organ felt like,
so I satisfied myself,
by masturbating.
The Baron:
Like that, like that, deep!
Penelope: What Marzia was doing
to the Baron,
was for me,
a world yet to be discovered.
I imitated everything
those two lovers were doing.
And I felt immense pleasure
in tasting in my mouth,
my own wetness
from between my legs.
[The Baron continues to moans]
The Baron: Now lay down here!
I want you to open up for me now.
[The Baron and Marzia moaning]
What a wet, juicy, pussy.
[The Baron and Marzia continue moaning]
The Baron: What a pussy.
Penelope: I lost all control,
and was masturbating
like a wild woman.
[soft music playing]
[The Baron and Marzia moaning]
The Baron: Look, how it goes inside of you.
Take it.
[The Baron and Marzia continues to moans]
You wanted me to fuck you
for a long time, huh?
The Baron & Marzia: yes...
The Baron: You like it?
So, take it.
[The Baron and Marzia continues to moans]
The Baron & Marzia: yes...
The Baron: Take it
The Baron: Look how he goes in...
[Marzia moans]
Penelope: My finger slid in and out
of my pussy at a frenzied pace
making me enjoy that moment,
like never before.
The Baron: Now pull yourself up like this!
Good.
You like it when I fuck you
like this slut, don't you?
Like that. Continue.
Take it like that!
Look how it goes inside you
It goes inside you
You like it like this, huh?
The Baron: You like that I fuck you like that.
[Marzia continues to moans]
You like it
Take it.
[The Baron and Marzia continues to moans]
Yes, move...
Lets go, move like this
Marzia: Pound me, pound me, pound me!
[Marzia moans higher]
The Baron: Take it...
The Baron: Come here.
Penelope: It was an incredible scene.
The Baron was fucking his son's wife.
Never could I have
imagined such a thing,
in a family like that.
But Marzia seemed to enjoy
the Baron's repeated penetrations.
[The Baron & Marzia, moaning]
Yes, yes, yes
Marzia: Don't stop...
Please, don't stop...
[The Baron & Marzia, screaming and moaning]
The Baron: Oh yes...
Marzia: We are going to come...
[The Baron & Marzia, continue to scream and moan...]
The Baron: I'm cumming, cumming, yes.
The Baron: aah!
Marzia: eeh...
[Baron and Maria continue to moan softly]
[soft music playing]
[The Baron laughing]
[soft music playing].
Penelope: The time had
come to step away,
so I straightened out my clothes,
and without being noticed,
I slipped out of that room.
[soft music playing and crickets singing]
I want to introduce you
the lady of the house.
She's a Baroness.
Her name is Marzia
Now, you're going to have
the pleasure of meeting her.
She is very hot.
She likes men and women too,
and she feel proud of that.
Now she is going to show you
the pleasure of sex
without, any inhibition
[soft music playing]
Penelope: Prepare to enjoy
these pleasures intensely.
[footsteps of the maid]
The Baron: You, my son.
You need to understand
what I expect from you.
Your brother is really smart.
[dishwashing sounds]
He has a job,
and he is studying in Milan.
You are the one who's not
doing anything all day long.
Right, Marzia?
But Lorenzo,
it's not fair to humiliate him,
in front of the servants.
And why not?
You've seen him
how he sleeps all day long.
And when he's not sleeping,
he's at the tennis club.
If I go to the club,
it's because, I don't know
what to do around here.
Dad, I do realize that.
I cannot go on like this.
- It's just that...
- You sleep standing up.
No, it's not true.
Anyway, right now let's eat.
Okay?
then, we'll go into my office
and we can discuss
what we can do about this.
- Enjoy!
- Thank you
Leave it there. Cover it up
or it will get cold.
[Rita's footsteps]
Rita: I'll finish up here.
You go take care of the bedrooms.
Lisa: Very well.
[soft music playing and Lisa's footsteps]
But keep in mind that you
never gave me the opportunity
to express myself!
So it's better there than here.
Bravo, bravo, bravo.
The kind of people like you
go to the tennis club.
Penelope, listen!
You've been hired
just a short while ago.
But I think you've figured out
how people are in this house.
To be okay, you have to be...
Let's say,
a little cooperative with them.
Especially with Marzia.
Always do everything she asks you.
The Baron: You two, stop gossipping!
Make me some coffee, come on!
Rita: Right away.
I don't feel too well.
I'm going back to my room.
Dario: Go, darling! I'll stay
a bit longer here with my father.
[soft music playing and Marzia's footsteps]
Penelope,
when you're done serving coffee,
please come over to my room!
The Baron: Son, you have to apply yourself
in everything you do.
And most importantly,
you have to be resourceful.
This is very, very important.
You got the drift, my son!
Your coffee, please.
No, he's too nervous.
No coffee for him today.
Just give me mine!
But you are the new maid.
What a cute ass.
Nice, huh? Cute. Nice tits.
Leave everything here, my dear,
leave it here! Go to Marzia, go!
[soft music playing]
[knocking at the door]
Penelope: May I come in?
Marzia: Yes, you can.
At last you've come. I'm exhausted.
Can you help me change?
[soft music playing]
Okay. Get my night clothes!
Over there on that little table.
Penelope: Here, Ma'am.
Thanks
[soft music playing]
You're wonderful. I like you.
If you want to live here,
you have to do
everything I ask you to do.
[soft music playing]
Come, sit here, we'll be confortable.
Your skin is wonderful velvet-like.
You excite me.
[soft music playing]
Would you like if I kiss you?
[Penelope moans softly]
[soft music playing]
[soft music playing continues]
Now I too will get undressed.
You know what I want from you?
Kiss me.
[soft music playing continues]
Your body drives me crazy.
You're quivering with desire.
I can feel it.
You're wet already, you little pig.
[Penelope and Marzia, starting to moan]
["Shape Of My Heart" by Sting]
[Penelope and Marzia, moaning softly]
[Penelope moaning softly]
["Shape Of My Heart" by Sting]
[Penelope and Marzia, moaning softly]
[Penelope, moaning softly...]
[Penelope, moaning more intensely]
["Shape Of My Heart" by Sting, continues to play]
[Penelope, moaning more intensely ...]
[Penelope, moaning]
["Shape Of My Heart" by Sting, continues to play]
[Penelope moans and Marzia licking sounds]
[new soft music playing]
[Penelope groaning intensely]
I like you, I like you.
[singing birds
and sounds of a hoe on the ground]
[Penelope's footsteps]
Come here.
You haven't been working here long.
In a few days my son will arrive,
and I want everything to be perfect.
Go now. Continue your work.
Penelope. Are You still a virgin?
- Have you ever made love?
- No.
We'll have fun anyways.
[soft music playing]
Marzia had some
very exciting plans for me.
And I was starting to enjoy myself
- Antonio.
- Yes.
- You must come right away.
Marzia wants to talk to you.
- And what does she want?
- You'll find out soon.
Augh...
What could have possibly happened?
Marzia Come my dear.
You'll see something
you've never seen before.
I will make love with
Antonio for you.
Now, hide here.
How long does it take
that big idiot to get here.
[soft music playing
and Antonio's footsteps]
[door closing]
[Antonio moans]
[new soft music playing]
[Antonio continues to moans]
[Marzia lickings sounds]
[Penelope moans softly]
[Antonio moans]
[Marzia starting to moan]
I want to fuck you.
Yes, fuck me...
[Marzia moaning]
Like that.
Fuck me, fuck me.
[Penelope moans softly]
[Antonio moans]
[Antonio and Marzia continues to moans]
Marzia: Like that.
Do it, do it!
Antonio: I like to fuck you.
[Antonio and Marzia continues to moans]
Fuck me, fuck me.
[Antonio and Marzia moans even louder]
[Antonio and Marzia continues to moans
with echo effects]
[Marzia moans intensely and Antonio also]
Antonio: I'm coming...
[Antonio moans gets louder]
[Antonio's moaning decrease]
Marzia: now get lost.
I've saved this for you.
[Penelope and Marzia, making sounds of excitement]
[soft music playing]
[water sounds]
Come on, take it in your mouth.
Suck it.
You're fantastic.
[The Baron moans and Rita also]
You're really fantastic.
You're great, you're great.
Ah, it feels so good
I like it when you take it
in your mouth.
[soft music playing]
[The Baron moans]
Get undressed,
I want to see you naked.
[soft music playing]
I'm going to fuck you.
[Rita moans]
[Rita moans gets louder]
[The Baron moans]
Rita: Yes, more
[Rita moans louder]
[The Baron and Rita moaning]
[The Baron and Rita moaning louder]
[Rita moans louder]
[The Baron and Rita moaning]
[The Baron moans louder]
Now, I want to come in your friend
Penelope's mouth, go get her, go.
Come on, move...
Hurry up doll.
[The Baron moans louder]
[The Baron moans]
The Baron: Yes like that.
[Penelope blowjob sounds]
The Baron: Very well.
The Baron: Don' stop...
[new soft music playing]
[Penelope making sounds]
The Baron: Oh! I like it
Like that.
Suck the hell out of me!
This is great.
Fantastic, Unbelievably
Oh, Like that...
Continue!
Don't stop...
Keep going...
I'm coming...
Very good...
and now you have to wait a bit.
I'll fuck you, don't worried.
And you'll like it.
You have to give me
one more opportunity Marzia.
So I can show you
that I am not impotent.
All right, Dario.
Tonight I will wait for you in my room.
Dario: Thanks darling, you'll see,
- I won't disappoint you.
You have to know
that my husband so far...
hasn't been able to make love to me.
And how can I help you?
I'd like you
to take part in our union.
Realy?
Maybe the idea
of having two women at his disposal,
will make him come.
Dario: May I come in?
- Yes, please come in.
I have a nice surprise for you.
If you want to prove me
your virility.
You can have both of us.
To satisfy all your desires
She is still a virgin.
But she's dying to try out,
what a real man's dick feels like.
Look at these tits,
hard and firm, ready to be fondled.
And here is the flower
still to be taken.
Come on Penelope,
touch my husband's dick.
I see that my surprise
was a good one, my dear Dario.
I've never seen you so excited.
[Penelope and Dario, starting to moan]
[kissing sounds]
[soft music playing]
Marzia: Yes, touch her.
- Like this Dario?
Dario: Yes, very good.
[Dario moans]
[Penelope and Dario moan]
[Penelope moans louder]
[Penelope and Dario moan louder]
[Penelope making linking sounds]
[Dario moans]
[Penelope and Dario, moan higher]
[Penelope and Dario, final moaning]
[Dario moans louder]
This has been
the best fuck of my life.
Penelope: Dario was healed from the ancient spell
of which he was a victim.
Thanks to his wife's initiative.
And thanks to my virginity.
[Antonio's footsteps and birds singing]
Life in the Baron's house
went by pleasantly.
Between Marzia's intention for me
and the Baron's spicy adventures.
The only girl
who was left alone was... Lisa.
But not for long, because...
Antonio, the house's handyman
was some sort of animal,
always ready to have sex anywhere.
Even in his employers home.
He behaved like a caveman.
And perhaps
that was the secret of his charm.
As no woman was able to resist him.
Antonio: Come on Rita.
Bring me something to drink.
I'm thirsty.
Nothing beats a glass of red wine
Rita: There you go.
But off those boots from the table.
Antonio: Come here cutie.
You know
what I like more than red wine.
I'm extremely excited.
Today I want to fuck you both.
Antonio: And now, your ass.
Oh, yes !!!
Penelope: This is Francesco,
the Baron's favorite son.
He studies in Milan. And he is always
busy with his business activities.
I made love
the very first time with him.
It all started one evening.
Marzia: Francesco has arrived.
The Baron's favorite son
and my brother-in-law.
I'm sure you will like him.
I'm sick and tired of my husband.
I don't like making love with him.
I want to make love
with Francesco...
But he doesn't want to.
Today I have an idea.
Maybe together,
we'll talk him into it.
So he can take your virginity.
Penelope: Yes Ma'am.
[♫ Phone ringing ♫]
Marzia: The phone. I'll get it.
[♫ Phone chime ♫]
Hello Francesca, how are you?
Yes, me too, no, no. He's not.
He went with my husband.
Antonio: Let me talk.
Marzia: No, they didn't tell me anything.
No.
- Don't worry dear! Yes.
Francesco: Why don't you give me the phone.
Marzia: I'll tell him to call you.
Francesco: I want to talk to her
Marzia: Sure!
Wait, I hear the door bell.
Maybe it's them.
Hold on a second,
I'll go see if they are back.
You know, so many people
come and go in this house.
Yes it's them.
- It's Francesca, your wife.
- Hello darling,  yes.
Sure-- of course.
I've been waiting for this moment.
Francesco: Yes darling, sure.
I want you.
Francesco: Of course--
Okay, but--
Marzia: Do you like my tits?
Francesco: Yes, yes-- but
Look-- the thing is--
Darling, everything you say
Yes, yes, you are right.
Marzia: I want you all inside of me.
I'm so wet
Francesco: But--
- I want you.
Francesco: Yes, darling.
Everything you say.
Yes, yes-- but look-- I think--
Sure, yes--
Very well, I'm fine-- of course--
You also, I'm glad-- yes.
At once, of course.
Yes, yes-- don't worry.
Yes.
Darling, everything you said.
You know I agree with you--
Yes, I will call you back. Don't worry.
My dear sister-in-law
you are a real slut.
- Do you like it when I suck it?
- Yes.
- Now I have a surprise for you.
- Realy
- Here she is, her name is Penelope.
She is a virgin and she is all yours.
My Dear, He is all yours too.
He will take your virginity.
Don't be too tense.
Ma'am, It's so good.
I like it.
Don't be too tense.
I will prepare you for the big event.