=======================
Fix or feedback: please let me know
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
Are you sure to know what we're going to do?
Yes, of course I know.
Please, forgive me to insist but... I think it doesn't fit your style.
You look so shy, so pure
Miss, you're so fresh
You can call me Rosy, it's easier
OK Rosy.
Why do you want to meet me?
I'd like... I want to be a nasty girl
Do you really know what it means?
- Yes
- Perfect
What are you thinking about?
I think about my friend Jenny
I want to be like her.
Tell me about Jenny
Happy New Year!
Take me!
- No, no. I can't Jenny
- But I want it. I want you to fuck me.
- No, I can't.
You can! Forget who you are, and forget who I am.
Focus on pleasure. Fuck me. I want to make love with you.
But I can't. I'm married!
I'm married too! Nobody will know. Take me.
Your mouth is so soft...
Yeah, it's good...
I'm going to swallow you
That's good, yeah
Use your teeth, nibble me
You're really beautiful. Come over me.
Turn
Like this?
Take me from behind
Cum in my mouth
Oh Jenny... yeah...
Why do you want to become like her?
I don't know... I'd like it, that's all.
Take off your jacket.
Take off your shirt.
Untie your watch.
Do you know other nasty girl?
Trinia
Who is Trinia?
Sha's a nurse, like me.
We work together
What does she like?
Girls above all.
And you? Do you like girls?
I don't know, I've never tried.
Once, I've seen Trinia with a girl.
It excited me.
Tell me.
- You like it?
- Yeah
Make me cum
Look at my pussy
Lick my pussy
Push your tongue deeper.
Lick my pussy.
It's so wet
Suck my finger. Suck it.
How tasty is a little pussy
You like it too, don't you.
Carress yourself.
Do you feel more nasty now?
Yes
Suck your finger
I will give you the name and the address of a man.
You will go there at midnight.
He likes sexy lingerie. Do you have some?
- Yes.
- Good.
He likes nasty girls.
I want to be nasty.
Do you want to suck me?
Oh yeah, I really want it.
Maybe I don't want to let you do so.
Please, let me suck your cock.
Suck me slowly
Fuck me.
Tell me, do you still need a massage?
I need a special massage.
- This kind of massage?
- Yes
Like this?
It's exactly what I need.
With your tongue
A deep massage
How was it?
It was fine.
Carress your breasts
Do you like to carress yourself?
Yes, pretty much.
Yeah I love it.
- Do you feel more nasty like this?
- Yes
Could you suck your nipples?
I'll try.
Pinch them.
Masturbate yourself in front of me.
Does it feel good?
Yeah
Do you feel more nasty?
I totally feel nasty.
Put your finger inside.
Carress you clit.
I know someone else for you. He wants 2 girls.
I can find one, except you know someone else.
My friend Trinia
I'd like to go there with her.
OK
I'm training to be nasty
Subtitled by truc1979
2015-10-24 (1)