the BB gun the water gun what didn't you
shoot me with a swear to god you would
have dumped me if I was in the tank
instead of that silly little cloud I
didn't know they were really around in
there yeah you are laughing I'm sorry I
got scared
you're a baby I'm not a big I'm
sensitive and women like sensitive
mm-hmm I mean who would have thought a
girl like you and a guy like me and be
hanging out after we both ordered of
what double blended soy mocha cappuccino
lucky coincidence it's not a coincidence
it's a kiss it's like meant to be your
shower is heavy yeah you don't want
paying it no it's just happy that you
like him like actually I didn't think
could add me to guy ordering a coffee
and then 20 minutes later I'm going to
the fair with him yeah I mean it's cool
I'm just what wasn't cool is that
deep fried candy bar I'm sorry oh my god
yeah that was a good idea in there you
need a but in all actuality it tasted
like Elvis
yes I'm sorry anyway the pair just we're
bummed that the evening is coming to an
end seriously look at any phone Wow it
does have to I still get tickets for one
more ride come here yeah hey yeah you
gotta be this tall to ride the thread
that right are you ready oh yeah
hey bro good boy we like that come here
oh I like it
Oh
ah
in the back to bed
there was nothing you can't don't want
you to worry about seeing today
but I think
hello hello miss Branson I was just
wondering if you were going to create
this with your presence here today I
work I do I do I do
um my alarm clock didn't go off your
alarm clock funny last week your my
mother died the week before that your
dog got run over but you know what
you're fired
good morning beautiful thank you
oh okay well I should see the year away
I'm looking gorgeous as ever I thought
this morning we can go get one of our
favorite double mocha soy yeah they did
that pony fucker right there right there
did that go walk did that alarm clock
the fuck oh shit we're off of my girl
look so beautiful sleep and I thought
I'd miss you okay well you can take all
that booty right there you better get
the fuck out my oh we had again I'm Adam
oh yeah Manny Manny Manny your harsh
Mandela it's Brady he's cool
oh my god
looks bad let's go check it out yeah
yeah oh my god what happened
I got fired oh my god I'm so sorry
sweetie that's like the third time this
month you know what you need you need it
like more than a job you need a career
like me you're a secretary ah ah I am
the AAA to the VP and that's the
administrative assistant to the vice
president you get coffee and you make
copies they do way more than that yeah
she does way way more than that yeah
could you please come in for some
dictation yeah boss right away
yes have a seat take some dictation
please dear board members it has come to
my attention that certain members of
this organization
do not feel that the proper course is
the one I've out wanted so I've decided
to pursue my stock options to buy out
the existing shares and to conduct a
hostile takeover my decision to do this
has not only been prompted by the
situation in the boardroom last week but
also by the confusion about last month's
inventory but what was that last bet the
last month's inventory it has also come
to my attention of the quarterly
adjustments should be taken in full
context and not individually as outlined
by policies and procedures
furthermore aha
I would like to conclude
ah
yeah yeah
huh
ah
give it
ha
oh fuck oh fuck me fuck yes
yeah
Oh
get it
yeah
[Laughter]
ah
ha
yeah
huh
Oh
Oh baby you wouldn't even have a job if
you weren't screwing though I am
climbing the corporate ladder
you could be banging the boss too if you
were just more motivated that's your
family
yeah and Plus corporate goals aside he
loves me and he's gonna marry me
um one he doesn't know your last name
and - yeah I'm pretty sure he's already
married that's true Bambi why us have to
be so negative
okay he made you take candy and flowers
to his wife on Valentine's Day yeah but
if she hadn't been there they would have
totally been mine that's true Randy oh
wait I have an idea what mr. Hendricks
is secretary just totally got fired she
was feeling like pens and secrets and
shit
I could totally call human resources I
could fuck you up you mean a secretary
like you yes
just like me it'll be so much fun well
dress the same and we can have lunches
together and you can carve look we could
carve it it'll be so much fun I guess it
sounds okay
we are not dressing the same but it is
better than nothing I mean
it'll be fun yeah I promise all right
all right yeah every secretary okay miss
Branson I need me call me brandy right
miss Branson I need you to make 50
copies of these collate them staple them
sort them bring them into the boardroom
the meeting starts within five minutes
so I need these for all the employees in
the boardroom okay you understand I'm
the copy clean copies copies you can
count on me I'm the best really I can do
it in my sleep
you all regretted or like messily Oh
cute correct all day long secretary wise
got tell me to do whatever already know
oh no no gentleman okay okay Oh
what mama don't do this to me okay all
right okay
oh okay close up kids get out from it
still got my right all right all right
come on baby
toner okay all right
oh there you are it's holed up right
poori race horns serve it
miss Pierce and wear those
he'll be a couple more minutes
let me guess I'm fired
Brandi come out of there it's not so bad
sweetie come on no where's my thank you
fan hey it could happen to anybody but
it didn't it happened to me yeah well
but look on the bright side they're not
gonna sue you maybe I'm not cut out for
the work force bullcrap we all have
something to offer the world to make it
a better place that's why I'm a home
health care nurse's assistant
professional I feel good making people
feel good
Brandi that totally sounds like you
uh-huh what what do you even do well I
work for a bedridden hunky billionaire
with fibromyalgia fire burn my heart
hurts all over
I'm responsible for feeding him bathing
him and putting him to treatment of
aggressive physical therapy I'm his
world
good morning sir how are you feeling
today I'm a little achy oh where does it
hurt the most everywhere but especially
concentrated around here oh maybe I
should have a look
they are looking a little bluish hmm I
think I know what you need
and shit all the way down over tell them
fuckin through there you go just like
that just like
oh all the way
ah ha me
Oh
free
Oh you
oh yeah
um don't I need some type of training or
yeah but you could just download a
certification off the internet I have a
computer well whatever I mean I guess
working for hunky billionaire wouldn't
be so bad
hi mr. Johnson how you feeling buddy I'm
dying here that's our feeling I'm number
Berlin and I'm harder than a whore in
church
hey let me put it to you you can
understand I'm sweating balls is here
you are a little warm let's take your
temperature dying here alright are you
ready here we go it's just obviously
your first time around the track it goes
in the other end sweetheart here let me
let me let me help you give you some
sweet cheeks there sweet cheeks
watch the hemorrhoid I'm sorry okay
sometimes things slip out what we're
gonna try this one more time okay okay
try this again I'm sorry they gave me
Kelly I told them no cucumbers and they
give me the coke um er it's not my fault
all right yeah what are you gonna
cooperate now all right
look one more time okay are you ready
[Laughter]
yeah soak that in sweet that's a that's
the smell of death right there oh and
cabbage yeah oh okay we're gonna check
your heart oh yeah I remember this I
know what I'm doing all right
quicker than this K what are you trying
to do kill me oh wait oh wait let me let
me check let me wait I hear beeping yeah
mr. Johnson oh good oh oh oh look you
guys throw up a little right here I'm
sorry no no no it's okay I'll clean it
up okay
yeah I've never I've never gotten this
sick ah it's okay brandy not everyone
was cut out for the healing arts brandy
this is perfect it's so you a singing
telegram yes can you just imagine happy
birthday to you Bambi from the moment I
met you I knew that I should give Jackie
the Saeki and marry you well if it's for
the good of the country remember ask not
what your country can do for you but
what you can do for your president's
penis
hello hello back to me here back to me
what can you imagine
hmm you Bailey yeah Billy yeah this is
for you
this is a message from your girlfriend
head a special delivery from a singer
Burnett I think it's best that you heard
it this way you're the reason that I've
gone gay please don't make me out to be
the villain PS you might wanna get a
shot up here in a sailor
yeah wait wait wait wait she's breaking
up with me yeah not only that but she's
apparently given up for weekly visits to
the free clinic oh because of your
cheating ways what wait wait no no no
Hannah is my life
she's everything to me she's she's the
air I breathe the ground I walk on
she's the nice thick foam I'm on top of
my beer okay all right third hero that
I'm sure you'll bounce back oh wait wait
wait wait wait well my whole body mate
maybe you and me we could go out Oh hail
to the no oh oh no no no no
oh oh yeah oh no ahh there has got to be
something here that I can do well I'm a
this guy that was a human guinea pig for
your it body spell oh my god I love that
stuff it drives me wild I know and it
needs to be even more driving Wilder
before it went on the market she made
good money as the test subject plus
benefits like health insurance or a 401k
not quite
right this way
first of all outside would just like to
say thank you on behalf of the people
here at your in body spray for you
volunteering that we are dozens of them
today first of all what I'm going to do
is spray you with a solution of highly
concentrated dose of yak pheromones
okay I'm gonna spray you with a light
mist and basically we want to see the
female subjects reaction to you after
president is that okay sure
okay now we are going to monitor the
entire thing on closed-circuit TV and
should anything go wrong all you have to
do is today is there something that
could go wrong oh no no we don't foresee
any problem it's just a safety first you
know kind of thing
so if by chance anything should go wrong
and once again we don't foresee that
happening we you have a safe word all
you have to do is say yeah kazakh
saralyn and we will come in we will stop
the experiment right away and everything
will be fine
so let's get you sprayed down for it all
done just one moment
how's that feel okay
doesn't burn no oh good okay good well
why don't you come over here and up
ladies this this is Alex Alex good luck
where's the cute guy at okay thank you
what is that you're wearing my favorite
shirt
yeah this is Mel yeah yak-yak juice kids
I don't want to you know get to know a
little bit better before we get
fuck
what she wants you once you're confident
yeah it totally changed the way America
consumes well do lightening products and
love getting paid
join me some six yeah why not okay
Brandi first of all I would really like
to thank you for coming down to the
testing labs and testing our new
serenity sprite the big help to us today
will be testing a new stress relief
spray it's made up of rose petals a bee
venom and poison ivy should be very
soothing to the skin now what I'm going
to do is I'm going to spray a little bit
tiny goggles oh no no they won't be
necessary won't be getting in your eyes
um once I spray this on you you probably
will feel a warm sense of calmness just
wash over you it'll be like a day at the
beach or possibly do a sense of like you
for yeah that's okay okay alright that's
that get this stuff ready we'll just get
you a little spray here okay
I have a few things I need to read you
first of all we here at the testing lab
problem your safety word today shall be
brandy brandy
not bad ok good
Oh bummer means you sign your rights
away so you can't sue you could have
been set for life um on the bright side
at least you can open your eyes again
yeah yeah yeah oh oh I thought it the
perfect job for you my friend was an
extra on a soap opera oh my god which
one the beautiful I'm a beautiful art oh
my god I love that was either one Solan
bitch here can we focus thank you thank
you
anyway she totally hooked up with Todd
Dillon Hoff and became his arm candy on
the red carpet and celebrity poker
tournament and paparazzi car chases
stuff you should totally do that yeah
you who knows you could become a star or
fuck a star yeah I could work a star
damn it
as your friend and doctor I've I
strongly against it you don't think I
know that I have the rare disease tickle
sick gnosis and that it only affects one
in 90 million and I happen to be that
one
look I know my odds are that I'm going
to die but if I still have a chance then
I still have a choice and I choose life
can I take your order yes bring me a cup
of life that was awesome
that was awesome that was absolutely
terrific people anyways people in this
set is a wrap you could say but you know
time-space that down for 30 people come
on then let's go look I just wanted to
tell you how amazing you were I mean if
you hadn't fed me that perfect are you
ready to order line I would have never
been able to follow up with my cup of
lifeline oh no no you're amazing would
you like to go back to my trailer and
talk about how amazing we are your dad
deal enough yes I am yes it's quite nice
it serves us well I can't believe I'm
really here your time feeling up yes yes
I am I get this reaction quite a bit
actually listen I wanted to compliment
you on that delivery you did earlier
really moment I saw you I said that girl
is potential okay
I can be a star I can't I can I don't
know star but you definitely have
potential I was thinking maybe we can do
a little rehearsal a little ad-lib as
they say in the business okay okay okay
you could pretend to be the starstruck
fan who's trying to seduce star I can do
that I can do that can you do that yeah
no that's good that's good but you
seemed a little well dance
something's something's holding it back
maybe no see maybe if you lost your
shirt release some tension you wouldn't
feel so constricted okay you know you
have to do things
in the movie business - uh it's okay
nervous is good use it use it I never
feel like the movies time before all
right I can't get this privilege how
does I feel um you know like you can
breathe better now
good now what would you say to a star in
order to seduce them Wow Wow your world
Oh
yeah
fuck
oh yeah soap opera star so me sure yeah
but you might want to wait for your face
to clear first yeah
I forgot about that no no really guys
does it really look that bad how you
know make it just a little bee sting
yeah yeah like a whole swarm of bees
attention first up everyone's doing an
excellent job I just wanted to say that
first and foremost this is a very
special week it's sweeps week and that
means that the network needs us to do a
live episode as if there's not enough
pressure on each and every one of us so
when we go back it's going to be all
live so we can have any fuck-ups
that means remember your lines remember
your positions and remember your
positions so I'm gonna do a countdown
from five and then everyone's gonna
start so here we go five four damn it
as your friend and doctor I advise
strongly against it look you don't think
I know that I have the rare disease
tickle sick gnosis and then it only
affects 190 million and that I happen to
be that one and I know that my odds are
that I'm going to die but if I still
have a chance then I choose life
choose life I choose life life is what I
choose can that can I get you a couple
please go to the space set and that's
for youth space does not exist there's
no space shuttle in your life sweetie
you are so out of here
a couple live you know oh my god
we saw you on TV we're so sorry yeah I
was fired fact everyone on set was fired
but you know what I'm gonna be fine in
fact within minutes of the broadcast the
clip was already downloaded on the
Internet
and I was the most watched clip more
than that girl shoots bananas out her
ass yep
oh my god more than the midget that
lights himself on fire and shoots
himself out of a cannon yeah wait what
about the baby dancing otters Oh even
more than them
in fact the network executive offered me
my own reality show who would have
thought I could become famous by being a
fuckup shut up I'm a bigger fuckup than
you no way I'm a total fuck-up
oh no oh no watch this shit okay um okay
okay I'll have my people call your
people I am a bigger