oh good the BB gun the water gun what
didn't issue me with I swear God you
would have dumped me if I was in the
tank instead of that silly little cloud
I didn't know there were brutally ground
in there yeah you are laughing I'm sorry
I got scared at the top of the Harris
baby I'm not a big I'm sensitive in
women like sensitive mm-hmm I mean who
would have thought a girl like you and a
guy like me and be hanging out after we
both ordered a what double blended soy
mocha cappuccino lucky quick it's not a
coincident it's a kid a white Christmas
it's like meant to be or Sarah but my
wife is heavy yeah you don't like Paris
no it's just heavy what you like it like
actually I didn't think could add me to
guy ordering a coffee and then 20
minutes later I'm going to the fair with
him yes
I mean it's cool I'm just what wasn't
cool was that the deep-fried candy bar
I'm sorry oh my god yes that was a good
idea in there in a but in all actuality
it tasted like Elvis yes I'm sorry
anyway the parasite or just we're we're
bummed that the evens coming to an end
seriously look at me phone Wow it does
have to I still got tickets for one more
ride so what I do you going all right
come here
yeah well yeah my cute my hat oh I'm
using let go over there hey
yes you got to be this tom Oh a rabbit
thread the Rose are you ready oh yeah
hey bro good boy we liked it
come here
I like it
with
side it Oh God
yes
so
ah
oh oh oh oh oh oh
Oh
ah
that women go back to bed
there was nothing nice clothes you can't
I want you to worry about today
Oh
that effect
hello hello miss Branson I was just
wondering if you were going to grace us
with your presence here today I work I
do I do I do
um my alarm clock didn't go off your
alarm clock funny last week your
grandmother died the week before that
your dog got run over
yes you know what you're fired good
morning huge thank you
oh okay well I could see the year away
I'm looking gorgeous as ever I thought
this morning we can go get one of our
favorite double mocha soy yes wrap again
bitch oh good did that holy fuck her
right there right there did I go up did
that alarm call scope the fuck of course
it will also my girl look so beautiful
sleep and I thought a mission okay well
you can take all that booty right now
you better get the fuck out my oh we had
again I'm at a motel today fuck is
Montgomery good you got like Taiwan
Academy I bet yes many many many your
Harshman oh it's Brady Oh get ready go
to that I got another buddy Callie he's
cool
Oh
oh my god damn let's go check it out
yeah yeah oh my god what happened
I got fired oh my god I'm so sorry
sweetie
oh that's like the third time this month
okay you know what you need you need is
like more than a job you need a career
like me you're a secretary
uh-uh I'm the AAA to the VP and that's
the administrative assistant to the vice
president you get coffee and you make
copies they do way more than that yeah
she does way way more than that Wow
could you please come in for some
dictation yeah boss
have a seat take some dictation please
dear board members this come to my
attention that certain members of this
organization do not feel that the proper
course is the one I've outlined so I've
decided to pursue my stock options to
buy out the existing shares and to
conduct a hostile takeover my decision
to do this has not only been prompted by
the situation in the board room last
week but also by the confusion about
last month's inventory that's what was
that lasted the last month's inventory
it has also come to my attention the
quarterly adjustments should be taken in
full context and not individually as
outlined by policies and procedures
furthermore aha
I would like to conclude
huh
Oh
yeah yeah
ah
Oh
oh yeah
ah
Oh My yes fuck with fit ha ha oh fuck me
ah fuck yeah
yeah
ha
ah yeah
yeah
ha
baby you would even have a job if you
were stronger I am climbing the
corporate ladder
you could be banging the box too if you
were just more motivated Nazi really yes
and plus and corporate goals aside he
loves me and he's gonna marry me um one
he doesn't know your last name and -
yeah I'm pretty sure he's already
married that's true Bambi why us have to
be so negative
okay he made you take candy and flowers
to his wife on Valentine's Day yeah but
if she hadn't been there they would have
totally been mine that's true Randy oh
please I have an idea what mr. Hendricks
is secretary just totally got fired she
was feeling like pens and secrets and
shit if you totally hold human resources
I guess you are
yeah you mean a secretary like you just
like me
it'll be so much fun well dress the same
and we can have lunches together and you
can carve look we could carve when it'll
be so much fun I guess it sounds okay we
are not dressed in saying that but it is
better than nothing
I mean it'll be fun yeah I promise
domi all right all right yeah every
secretary all right okay miss Branson
hey buddy
call me baby right miss Branson I need
you to make 50 copies of these collate
them staple them sort them bring them
into the boardroom the meeting starts
within five minutes so I need these for
all the employees in the boardroom okay
you understand I'm the copy clean copies
copies crack you can count on me I'm the
best
really I can do it in my sleep you all
regretted
like or like math we arrest
it's nice Oh Fred Oh
cute correct all day long secretary what
tell me to do whatever already know
oh no no general me now okay I can fix
okay okay Oh
right now we're with Mama where would a
woman don't do this to me all right come
on sir the mama for Michael Scott
oh oh ok alright ok oh ok close out kids
The Alchemist you'll gonna rat one all
right oh all right come on baby all
right
what whoa toner
ok maybe study all right oh there you
are
oh hey oh no oh it's all now oh yes
everything's fine
I'm in 30 copies right now
Oh
the parents and where are those
awesome it'll be a couple more minutes
let me guess I'm fired
Brandi come out of there it's not so bad
sweetie come on no where's my thank you
fan hey it could happen to anybody but
it didn't it happened to me yeah well I
look on the bright side they're not
going to see you maybe I'm not cut out
for the work force
bull crap we all have something to offer
the world to make it a better place
that's why I'm a home health care
nurse's assistant professional I feel
good making people feel good Brandi that
totally sounds like you uh-huh what what
do you even do well I work for a
bedridden honky billionaire with
fibromyalgia fibromyalgia is below
feeding him bathing him and putting him
to treatment of aggressive physical
therapy I miss world
good morning sir how are you feeling
today I'm a little achy oh why does it
hurt the most everywhere but especially
concentrated around here Oh maybe I
should have a look
um they are looking a little bluish hmm
I think I know it's need
that's it all the way down we tell them
fuckin through you got just like that
just like that fucking working
Oh
oh is it all the way oh oh it's me hard
it's it all the way that's it
open up open up open
aha
Oh
I'm free
ah
Oh
I'll make you feel better
oh yeah
ah
Oh you
Oh
oh yeah
ah
oh good
don't I need some type of training or
yeah but you could just download a
certification off the internet
I have a computer whatever I mean I
guess working for on-q billionaire
Lumbees have been
hi mr. Johnson how you feeling buddy I'm
dying here that's all feeling us I'm
improper burning I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm
hotter than a whore in church
yeah yeah let me put it to you you can
understand I'm sweating boss is here
as me you are a little warm let's take
your temperature okay
sinister sis I was burning up yeah sure
take your time I'm really dying here
here we go all right are you ready oh
here we go here we go like this it's
just obviously your first timer on the
track it goes in the other end
sweetheart huh here let me let me let me
help you give you some sweet cheeks
there sweet cheeks okay okay ready
watch the hemorrhoid this Oh
jon-fen I'm sorry okay sometimes things
slip out I hope it wasn't wet we're
gonna try this one more time okay okay I
would try this again mr. Johnson I'm so
I'm sorry they gave me Kelly I told him
no cucumber and they give me the to
cover it's not my fault all right
look what are you gonna cooperate now oh
I'm laying here what am i doing all
right one more time
oh are you ready oh that's good hmm yeah
soak that in sweet that's a that's the
smell of death right there oh and
cabbage yeah oh okay we're gonna take
your heart Oh
yeah I remember this I know what I'm
doing Artie another hmm I bet tax audits
that that were quicker than this for
Christ's sake
well sometimes you need help
Oh mr. Johnson oh oh don't you die on me
don't stay away from the light
oh my god okay what are you trying to do
kill me
Oh somebody get here don't go away
where are we let me let me check perfect
oh right I hear beeping yes mr. Johnson
oh oh well it was a good oh oh oh look
you guys throw up a little right here
hmm I'm sorry Brenda no no it's okay
I'll clean it up oh okay
I've never I've never gotten this it's
okay Brandi not everyone's cut out for
the healing arts Brandi this is perfect
it's so you a singing telegram yes can
you just imagine Nesta president happy
birthday to you Bambi from the moment I
met you I knew that I should give Jackie
the Saeki and marry you well if it's for
the good of the country remember ask not
what your country can do for you but
what you can do for your president's
penis
hello hello back to me here back to me
sit
can you imagine hmm you Bailey
yeah all Billy yeah this is for you
this is a message from your girlfriend
has a special delivery from a singer
banana I think it's best that you heard
it this way you're the reason that I
gone gay please don't make me out to be
the villain PS you might wanna get a
shot at parasailing
yeah but why wait wait wait she's
breaking up with me yeah not only that
but she's apparently given up for weekly
visits to the free clinic Oh
because of your cheating wait what wait
wait no no no Hannah is my life she's
everything to me she's she's the air I
breathe the ground I walk on
she's the nice thick foam on top of my
beer okay all right sorry hero that I'm
sure you'll bounce back oh wait wait
wait wait wait well Michael Manny mate
maybe you and me we could go out hail to
the nose oh no oh no no no no so shut
the dough just I got five more to do
okay
oh he'll know on there is got to be
something here that I could well I knew
this guy that was a human guinea pig for
your it body spell
oh my god I love that stuff drives me
wild
I know and it needs to be even more
drive your Wilder before it went on the
market she made good money as the test
subject plus benefit like health
insurance or a 401 K not quite right way
first of all outside would just like to
say thank you on behalf of the people
here at your in body spray for you
volunteering that we are dozens of it
today first of all what I'm going to do
is spray you with a solution of highly
concentrated dose of yak pheromones
okay I'm gonna spray you with a light
mist and basically we want to see the
female subjects reaction to you after
present is that okay sure okay now we
are going to monitor the entire thing on
closed-circuit TV and should anything go
wrong all you have to do is say is there
something that could go wrong oh no no
we don't foresee any problem it's just a
safety first you know kind of thing so
it's by chance anything should go wrong
and once again we don't foresee that
happening we you have a safe word all
you have to do is say yeah kazakh sarah
lean and we will come in we will stop
the experiment right away and everything
will be fine so let's get you sprayed
down for it all done just one moment
loads look at sensors how's that feel
doesn't burn no oh good okay good oh why
don't you come over here and up ladies
this is Alex Seafarer
good luck
where's the cute guy hat right here
small kind of in thank you
what is that you're wearing sure yeah
it's now no Jack nectars kids
I want to do that too I want you to set
my finger chi-chi wanax trying to you
know get to know you a little bit better
before we get close let me slow it down
a little bit
Hey
there
Oh
I heard what she wants you went to
cotton
now
Oh
welcome
yeah it totally changed the way America
consumes well I do like me products and
love getting paid enjoyed means to move
six from ten times oh yeah okay Brandi
first of all I would really like to
thank you for coming down to the testing
labs and testing our new serenity sprite
the big help to us sure
today we'll be testing a new stress
relief spray it's made up of rose petals
a bee venom and poison ivy should be
very soothing to the skin now what I'm
going to do is I'm going to spray a
little bit tiny ghazals
oh no no that won't be necessary won't
be getting in your eyes um once I spray
this on you you probably will feel a
warm sense of calmness just wash over
you it'll be like a day at the beach or
possibly to a sense of like you for
something that's okay okay all right
that's that get this covered it will
just get you a little spray here okay
I have a few things I need to read to
first of all we here at the testing labs
problem your safety word today shall be
brandy brandy oh look it's not art so
another bad okay good
Oh bummer hands you sign your rights
away so you can't sue you could have
been set for life um on the bright side
at least you can open your eyes again
yeah yeah yeah oh I thought of the
perfect job for you my friend was an
extra on a soap opera oh my god which
one the beautiful and the beautiful art
oh my god I love that when did you - why
no it's either one works giving swollen
bitch here can we follow this thank you
thank you anyway
she totally hooked up with Todd Dylan
Hoff and became his arm candy on the red
carpet and the celebrity poker
tournament and paparazzi car chases stop
you should totally do that yeah you who
knows you could become a star or fuck a
star yeah I could work a star huh
I could I could work a star hmm
damnit as your friend and dr. i'vei've
strongly against it you don't think I
know that I have the rare disease tickle
sick gnosis and that it only affects one
in ninety million and I happen to be
that one look I know my odds are that
I'm going to die but if I still have a
chance then I still have a choice and I
choose life can I take your order yes
bring me a cup of life ah that was
awesome that was awesome that was
absolutely terrific people anyways
people that sent is a wrap you could say
but you know possible fit come on let's
get going this is going with poop
wasting time space it down for 30 people
come on then let's go look I just wanted
to tell you how amazing you were I mean
if you hadn't fed me that perfect are
you ready to order line I would have
never been able to follow up with my cup
of life line oh no no you're amazing
would you like to go back to my trailer
and talk about how amazing we are your
dad deal enough yes I am Wow yes it's
it's quite nice it surfaces well I can't
believe in oh yeah oh my god I'm really
here your time feeling up yes yes I am I
get this reaction quite a bit actually
listen I wanted to compliment you on
that delivery you did
really moment I saw you I said that girl
has potential good I can be a star I
can't I can well I don't know star but
you definitely have potential I was
thinking maybe we can do a little
rehearsal a little ad-lib as they say in
the business okay okay okay okay
you could pretend to be the starstruck
fan who's trying to seduce star I can do
that you can do that could you do that
yep
oh no oh that's all I was good that was
good but you seemed a little well can't
something's something's holding it back
baby no see maybe if you lost your shirt
release some tension you wouldn't feel
so constricted oh okay you know you have
to do things
in the movie business - uh it's okay
nervous is good use it use it never pay
with them at any time before hey
fredwich
goodbye there you go Wow
how does I feel um like you can breathe
better now
okay now what would you say to a star in
order to seduce them
come 12:00 Wow
j'tia little sigh I'm gonna rock your
world
Oh
fuck
ah
yeah
Oh
ah
barbar
oh yeah
so bumper stars so me sure yeah but you
might want to wait for your face -
Claire first yeah I forgot about not
really guys doesn't really look that bad
oh you know make it just a little bee
sting yeah yeah like a whole swarm of
bees okay let's have a tension with have
attention first off everyone's doing an
excellent job east wanted to say that
first and foremost this is a very
special week it's sweeps week and that
means that the network needs us to do a
live episode as if there's not enough
pressure on each and every one of us so
when we go back it's going to be all
live so we can at any fuck-ups
that means remember your lines remember
your position sweep and remember your
positions so I'm going to you would
count down from five and then everyone's
going to start so here we go five four
three one damn it
as your friend and doctor I advise
strongly against it fuck you don't think
I know that I have the rare disease
tickle sick gnosis and that it only
affects 190 million and that I happen to
be that one and I know that my odds are
that I'm going to die but if I still
have a chance then I choose life
choose life I choose life life is what I
choose can that can I get you a cup of
life cup a cup of cup of life Marty my
doing can't you get for fucking me
listen this is the line this is the
whole movie here what am I freaking out
like this is a disaster this is a wrap
people please go to the space set and as
for you space does not exist there's no
space shuttle in your life sweetie you
are so out of here
a couple live you know that's as long
Jesus but you make me go don't forget
about him he's mine anyway oh my god
we saw you on TV we're so sorry yeah I
was fired fact everyone on set was fired
but you know what I'm gonna be fine in
fact within minutes of the broadcast the
clip was already downloaded on the
internet and I was the most watched clip
oh ah more than that girl up shoots
bananas on her ass
yep oh my god more than the midget that
lights himself on fire and shoots
himself out of a cannon yeah
wait what about the baby dancing otters
also gears up all right
even more than them in fact the Network
executive offered me my own reality show
who I thought I could become famous by
being a fuck up shut up I'm a bigger
fuckup than you no way I'm a total
fuck-up oh okay I know I know I love it
watch this shit okay um okay okay I'll
have my people call your people I am a
bigger sometimes a bigger