the BB gun the water go what didn't you
shoot me with I swear to god you would
have dumped me if I was in the tank
instead of that silly little cloud I
didn't know they were really round in
there there's baby I'm not a big I'm
sensitive and women like sensitive
mm-hmm I mean who would have thought a
girl like you and a guy like me and be
hanging out after we both ordered Oh
what double blended soy mocha cappuccino
lucky coincidence it's not a coincidence
it's a kiss oh it's like meant to be or
so yeah yeah you don't want panda no
it's just happy that you like it like
actually I didn't think could add me to
guy ordering a coffee and then 20
minutes later I'm going to the fair with
him yeah I mean it's cool I'm just what
wasn't cool is that deep-fried candy bar
I'm sorry
oh my god yeah that was a good idea in
theory but in all actuality it tasted
like yes I'm sorry
anyway the pattern we're just we're
we're bummed that the evening is coming
to an end seriously look at any phone
well it doesn't have to
I still got tickets for one more ride
come here yep hey yeah you gotta be this
tome red thread that right are you ready
oh babe real good boy we like that come
here
Oh
ah
in the back - damn it was nothing I want
you to worry about it
I think
hello hello miss Branson I was just
wondering if you were going to create
this with your presence here today I
work I do I do I do
um my alarm clock Dingle your alarm
clock funny last week your my mother
died the week before that your dog got
run over but you know what you're fired
good morning beautiful
oh okay well I could see the year away
and looking gorgeous as ever I thought
this morning we can go get one of our
favorite double mocha soy yeah did that
fucker right there right there did that
go up did that alarm clock the fuck oh
my girl look so beautiful sleep and I
thought I'd miss you okay well you can
take all that booty right there you
better get the fuck out my oh we had
again a many many many harsh Mandela
it's Brady
oh my god looks bad let's go check it
out yeah yeah oh my god what happened
I got fired oh my god I'm so sorry
sweetie that's like the third time this
month you know what you need you need it
like more than a job you need a career
like me you're a secretary ah ah I am
the AAA to the VP and that's the
administrative assistant to the vice
president you get coffee and you make
copies they do way more than that yeah
she does way way more than that yeah
could you please come in for some
dictation yeah boss right away
yes have a seat
take some dictation please dear board
members it has come to my attention that
certain members of this organization
do not feel that the proper course is
the one I've outlined so I have decided
to pursue my stock options to buy out
the existing shares and to conduct a
hostile takeover my decision to do this
has not only been prompted by the
situation in the boardroom last week but
also by the confusion about last month's
inventory but what was that last bit the
last month's inventory it has also come
to my attention of the quarterly
adjustments should be taken in full
context and not individually as outlined
by policies and procedures
furthermore aha I would like to conclude
yeah yeah
huh
Oh
give it
fuck
yeah
Oh
huh
baby you wouldn't even have a job if you
weren't screwing though I am climbing
the corporate ladder
you could be banging the boss too if you
were just more motivated not fear family
yeah and plus corporate goals aside he
loves me and he's gonna marry me um one
he doesn't know your last name
and two yeah I'm pretty sure he's
already married that's true Bambi why
you guys have to be so negative okay he
made you take candy and flowers to his
wife on Valentine's Day yeah but if she
hadn't been there they would have
totally been mine that's true Randy oh
wait I have an idea what mr. Hendrix's
secretary just totally got fired she was
feeling like pens and secrets and shit
I could totally hold Human Resources I
can fuck you up you mean a secretary
like you yes just like me it'll be so
much fun well dress the same and we can
have lunches together and you can carve
look we could carve wood it'll be so
much fun I guess it sounds okay we are
not dressing insane but it is better
than nothing
I mean
it'll be fun yeah I promise all right
all right yeah every secretary okay miss
Branson I need me call me brandy right
miss Branson I need you to make 50
copies of these collate them staple them
sort them bring them into the boardroom
the meeting starts within five minutes
so I need these for all the employees in
the boardroom okay you understand I'm
the copy Queen copies copies you can
count on me or like mess
all right all day long secretary was I
tell me to do whatever no no no mom
don't do this to me all right all right
all right come on baby
oh there you are
hold up miss Pierce and wear those
don't be a couple more minutes
let me guess I'm fired
Brandi come out of there it's not so bad
sweetie come on no where's my thank you
fan hey it could happen to anybody but
it didn't it happened to me yeah well
but look on the bright side they're not
gonna sue you maybe I'm not cut out for
the work force bullcrap we all have
something to offer the world to make it
a better place that's why I'm a home
health care nurse's assistant
professional I feel good making people
feel good
Brandi that totally sounds like you
uh-huh
what what do you even do well I work for
a bedridden hunky billionaire with
fibromyalgia fibromyalgia bathing him
and putting him to treatment of
aggressive physical therapy I'm his
world
good morning sir
how are you feeling today I'm a little
achy oh where does it hurt the most
everywhere but especially concentrated
around here oh maybe I should have a
look
they are looking a little bluish hmm I
think I know what you need
that's it all the way down
there you go just like that
oh all the way
ah me
Oh
shut them free
oh you
oh yeah
Oh
um don't I need some type of training or
yeah
but you could just download a
certification off the internet I have a
computer well whatever I mean I guess
working for hunky billionaire wouldn't
be so bad
hi mr. Johnson how are you feeling buddy
I'm dying here that's not feeling I'm
burning I'm hotter than a whore in
church
let me put it to you turn you can
understand I'm sweating balls here you
are a little warm let's take your
temperature here all right are you ready
obviously your first time around the
track it goes in the other end
sweetheart here let me let me let me
help you give you some sweet cheeks
there sweet cheeks
watch the hemorrhoid I'm sorry okay
sometimes things slip out we're gonna
try this one more time okay okay I'm
sorry they gave me Kelly I told them no
cucumber and they give me the cucumber
it's not my fault
all right yeah what are you gonna
cooperate now all right one more time
oh are you ready that's good yeah soak
that in sweet that's a that's the smell
of death right there
Oh and cabbage yeah oh okay we're gonna
check your heart oh yeah I remember this
I know what I'm doing all right
I bet tax audits quicker than this
Johnson okay what are you trying to do
kill me wait for me let me let me check
let me wait I hear beeping yeah mr.
Johnson oh good oh oh oh look you guys
throw up a little right here I'm sorry
no no no it's okay I'll clean it up okay
good I've never I've never gotten this
sick ah it's okay brandy not everyone
was cut out for the healing arts brandy
this is perfect it's so you a singing
telegram yes can you just imagine happy
birthday to you Bambi from the moment I
met you I knew that I should give Jackie
the Saeki and marry you well if it's for
the good of the country
remember ask not what your country can
do for you but what you can do for your
president's penis
hello hello back to me here back to me
but can you imagine you Bailey yeah I'll
Billie
yeah this is for you this is a message
from your girlfriend had a special
delivery from a singer Burnett I think
it's best that you heard it this way
you're the reason that I've gone gay
please don't make me out to be the
villain PS you might wanna get a shot up
here nice Ellen yeah
wait wait wait wait she's breaking up
with me yeah not only that but she's
apparently given up for weekly visits to
the free clinic oh because of your
cheating ways what wait wait no no no
Hannah is my life
she's everything to me she's she's the
air I breathe the ground I walk on
she's the nice thick foam I'm on top of
my beer okay all right third hero that
I'm sure you'll bounce back oh wait wait
wait wait wait well my whole body mate
maybe you and me we could go out oh hey
oh oh yeah oh no ahh there has got to be
something here that I can do well I'm a
this guy that was a human guinea pig for
your it body spell oh my god I love that
stuff it drives me wild I know and it
used to be even more driving Wilder
before it went on the market she made
good money as the test subject plus
benefits like health insurance or a 401k
right this way
first of all outside would just like to
say thank you on behalf of the people
here at your in body spray for you
volunteering that we are dozens of them
today first of all what I'm going to do
is spray you with a solution of highly
concentrated dose of yak pheromones
okay I'm gonna spray you with a light
mist and basically we want to see the
female subjects reaction to you after
president is that okay sure
okay now we are going to monitor the
entire thing on closed-circuit TV um and
should anything go wrong all you have to
do is say is there something that could
go wrong oh no no we don't foresee any
problem it's just a safety first you
know kind of thing so if by chance
anything should go wrong and once again
we don't foresee that happening uh we
you have a safe word all you have to do
is say yeah cos a casera lead and we
will come in we will stop the experiment
right away and everything will be fine
so let's get your spray down how's that
be okay doesn't burn no oh good
okay good well why don't you come over
here and ladies this this is Alex good
luck
where's the cute guy hat thank you what
is that you're wearing my favorite shirt
no this is Mel yak you know get to know
you a little bit better before we
Oh
she wants you much you're confident
yeah
you could totally change the way America
consumes well do lightening products and
love getting paid join me some six okay
Brandi first of all I would really like
to thank you for coming down to the
testing labs and testing our new
serenity sprite the big help to us sure
today we'll be testing a new stress
relief spray it's made up of rose petals
a bee venom and poison ivy should be
very soothing to the skin now what I'm
going to do is I'm going to spray a
little bit tiny goggles oh no no that
won't be necessary
won't be getting in your eyes um once I
spray this on you you probably will feel
a warm sense of calmness just wash over
you it'll be like a day at the beach or
possibly do a sense of like you for yeah
that's okay okay all right let's get
this stuff ready we'll just get you a
little spray here okay
I have a few things I need to read you
first of all we here at the testing lab
problem your safety word today shall be
brandy brandy okay good
Oh bummer means you sign your rights
away so you can't sue you could have
been set for life um on the bright side
at least you can open your eyes again
yeah yeah yeah oh oh I thought it the
perfect job for you my friend was an
extra on a soap opera oh my god which
one the beautiful I'm a beautiful art oh
my god I love that was either one Solan
bitch here can we focus thank you thank
you
anyway she totally hooked up with Todd
Dillon Hoff and became his arm candy on
the red carpet and celebrity poker
tournaments and paparazzi car chases
stuff you should totally do that
yeah you who knows you could become a
star or fuck a star
yeah I could work a star damn it as your
friend and doctor I've I strongly
against it you don't think I know that I
have the rare disease tickle sick gnosis
and that it only affects one in 90
million and I happen to be that one
look I know my odds are that I'm going
to die but if I still have a chance then
I still have a choice and I choose wife
can I take your order yes bring me a cup
of life that was awesome
that was awesome that was absolutely
terrific people anyways people this set
is a wrap you could say but you know a
set down for 30 people come on then
let's go look I just wanted to tell you
how amazing you were I mean if you
hadn't fed me that perfect are you ready
to order line I would have never been
able to follow up with my cup of
lifeline oh no no you're amazing would
you like to go back to my trailer and
talk about how amazing we are your dad
deal enough yes I am yes it's quite nice
it surfaces wow I can't believe I'm
really here your time feeling up yes yes
I am I get this reaction quite a bit
actually listen I wanted to compliment
you on that delivery you did earlier
really moment I saw you I said that girl
I can be a star I can't I can I don't
know
star but you definitely have potential I
was thinking maybe we can do a little
rehearsal a little ad-lib as they say in
the business okay okay okay okay
you could pretend to be the starstruck
fan who's trying to seduce the star do
that I can do that can you do that
that's good that was good but you seemed
a little dance something's something's
holding it back baby no see maybe if you
lost your shirt release some tension you
wouldn't feel so constricted okay you
know you have to do things
in the movie business - it's okay
nervous is good use it use it never been
with no babies time before how does I
feel oh no I can breathe better now
good now what would you say to a star in
order to seduce him wow you're tight a
little
yes I am rock your world
Oh
ah
oh yeah soap opera star so me sure yeah
but you might want to wait for your face
to clear first yeah
I forgot about that no no really guys
does it really look that bad how you
know make it just a little bee sting
yeah yeah like a whole swarm of bees
first up everyone's doing an excellent
job I just wanted to say that first and
foremost this is a very special week
it's sweeps week and that means that the
network needs us to do a live episode as
if there's not enough pressure on each
and every one of us so when we go back
it's going to be all live so we can't
have any fuck-ups
that means remember your lines remember
your positions and remember your
positions so I'm gonna do a countdown
from five and then everyone's gonna
start so here we go five four damn it as
your friend and doctor
I advise strongly against it look you
don't think I know that I have the rare
disease tickle sick gnosis and then it
only affects 190 million and that I
happen to be that one and I know that my
odds are that I'm going to die but if I
still have a chance then I choose life
choose life I choose life life is what I
choose can that can I get you a cup of
life people please go to the space set
and that's for you space does not exist
there's no space shuttle in your life
sweetie you are so out of here
a couple live you know that's his law my
god we saw you on TV we're so sorry yeah
I was fired fact everyone on set was
fired but you know what I'm gonna be
fine in fact within minutes of the
broadcast the clip was already
downloaded on the internet and I was the
most watched clip more than that girl
shoots bananas out her ass yep oh my god
more than the midget that lights himself
on fire and shoots himself out of a
cannon
yeah wait what about the baby dancing
otters even more than them
in fact the network executive offered me
my own reality show
who would've thought I could become
famous by being a fuckup shut up I'm a
bigger fuckup than you know where I'm at
okay okay okay I'll have my people
close your people I am a bigger