[Music]
[Applause]
this is Martin this is dr. Jones I'm in
cruella industries headquarters
excellent any trouble but I have clean
three floors with the toilets to get
here
[Music]
excellent work dr. Jones your country
appreciates it
any sign of the idol it's right in front
of me can you secure it its value is
security looks easy enough that's what
worries me
it's our deal still in place yes you
will be allowed to study it for your own
research as long as we know it's not in
the hands of our enemies one want the
CIA going back on their word now no
tricks Jones just get the Idol away from
evil a gorilla it doesn't seem to be an
alarm system in place I'll call you what
Sam outside be careful
don't worry I've stolen my fair share of
idols piece of cake over and out
[Music]
hmm
you will look spectacular in my trophy
case breathe put your hands up
easy lady what are you doing in here let
me guess
silent alarm that's right now I asked
you what were you doing what's it look
like
Einstein I'm the cleaning lady I'm
cleaning up how'd you get in here all
the doors are locked
can I help it I get paid to clean I
finished three floors this was my last
stop that's right I saw you on the
second floor you do good work
Thanks I try well I guess there's no
harm done we better not let anybody know
about this they'll fire one of us for
sure why would I tell anyone I don't
want to lose my job well neither so we
agree this never happened
what happened yeah that's the idea you
know my shift is over now what do you
say you and me seal the deal this way
neither one of us is tempted to talk
about it later you mean you and me right
here in the desk well I guess no no miss
me for a little while great let's not
waste any time
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh baby you're already starting to give
me good luck and that mr. Martin is how
I stole the sacred Idol of arrows -
right from under their noses
excellent work dr. Johnson excellent you
know word on the street is that evil
Agrella
is absolutely having a cow over this and
while she might we have to ensure that
this never falls into our hands again
don't forget our deal I keep the idol
for my research and when I'm done you
CIA boys can have it for your little
collection I wish you'd reconsider our
agreement dr. Jones we can't afford to
have that floating around out there
somewhere it won't be floating anywhere
it will be with me I'll take good care
of it you realize that on that Idol
somewhere is the location of the temple
of eros exactly and whoever finds the
temple finds a tiara of Aisha exactly
and whoever has the tiara of Aisha shall
be the ruler of the Empire of moronica
can you believe a villa
Krewella with all her millions still
wants to be ruler of the Empire that's
not gonna happen we're counting on you
listen Martin I'll give you this trinket
as soon as I decipher the map to the
temple that's all I'm interested in and
what then you hold on to the tiara it's
a museum piece I have no intention of
becoming queen of the morons that's your
job
contact me the moment you break the code
ciao baby
[Music]
I want that Idol it's mine by right of
my ancestry perhaps but I thought you
were from Hoboken hoebuck well my
grandpa did settle there but my real
destiny is the Empire of moronica yes of
course this is all very unfortunate I
entrusted my spies to bring me my idol
we had it but it slipped away and I want
it back how can we help you achieve your
goals mistress I must have that idol it
alone has the location of the temple of
uros with it I can acquire the tiara of
Aisha and rule all of moronica and then
you will be the supreme Empress of
erotica suits me well don't you think it
does indeed then get me that Idol I
don't care how you do it or by what
means just bring it back to me I
understand that dr. Jones the eminent
archeologist has it in her possession
then you know what to do
rally our spies in America and bring me
that Idol at your command
[Music]
man hell I haven't showered in a week Oh
at least I still smell like a blonde
security guard well I can fix that
[Music]
[Applause]
who the hell are you Carol summers
department of national antiquities
Martin asked me to stop by to see if I
could be of any assistance is that so
well I didn't hear anything about this
and I don't remember asking for any help
well Martin's anxious to have the idol
and safekeeping as long as you possess
it it could fall into the wrong hands
yeah I've heard the spiel can you give
me a moment all right you can just step
outside into the hallway Martin yeah
this is dr. Jones ah doctor
everything all right just calling to
check on a Carol Sommers yes one of
yours
Carol is an excellent cipher so am i but
I could use some help might speed up the
process a little that's what we thought
she's very good I'm sure you two will
hit it off I'll let you know
Hey and next time you ask someone to
drop in on me warn me first
understood Carol everything hunky-dory
yeah it's all hunky-dory so what's your
game sister now just your average red
blooded all american egghead I guess too
smart for my own good no luck with the
boys huh no guys don't make passes at
girls who wear glasses that's why I wear
contacts I wish I could but it hurts my
eyes hmm studying too hard you should
get out more yeah maybe everything okay
oh that's a whitmark a wit mark
got an Istanbul that's incredible
someone actually whipped you well they
tried but they didn't get away with it I
had a live Cobra in my pants
a live Cobra never underestimate the
power of a highly poisonous and very
pissed-off snake sounds like you've been
through a lot and I've got the bruises
to prove it a person who leads a
dangerous life like you do needs to
relax more maybe but in my line of work
you got to keep on your toes
sounds like you need a massage I studied
Reiki in college
Reiki Reiki take eat ah be the art of
sensuous mongoose massage are you any
good well I haven't had any luck with
the boys
but I scored a pretty high with the
girls well Martin did say you were to
lend a helping hand he didn't say where
those hands would be used so what the
hell
[Music]
ah
Oh
[Music]
at last person who possesses its rules
the Empire bug who wants it this was too
easy hold it okay okay don't shoot not
gently put everything back on the
counter that's a good boy
now tell me who do you work for I think
you already know I work for the rightful
owner that idle a Villa Cruella the heir
to the empire moronica you mean the
airhead wait isn't she from Hoboken
well her grandpa settled in Hoboken but
her answer says we're morons make no
mistake about it I'm gonna have to trust
you on that one
unfortunately the idol is mine now and
when I finish the CIA is gonna put it
where the Sun don't shine you don't know
what you're playing with dr. Jones a
villa will go to great lengths to regain
that Idol you could be a very rich woman
what's money to me
you could have power lots of power
I'm already telling the CIA where to
stick it how much more power do I need
you could have rocking sex day and night
nice but I'm a little tired now turn
around and put your hands behind your
back
okay but this is gonna hurt you a lot
more than it hurts me
that's what all the boys say good work
Carol I thought you might sleep through
the entire thing
dr. Jones takes a lot out of a woman I'm
still a little weak in the knees cool
your jets Carol let's grab everything
and get out of here before she wakes up
see a doctor thanks for the hot sex
[Music]
terrible news dr. Jones yes I mean what
is are you sure you're all right
me of course am what did you just call
me you're dr. Jones I am oh dear don't
you remember anything that's happened of
course I do I took a shower got to know
Carol a little better and then I found
this strange guy in my house and he was
stealing the idol yes yes I had the
upper hand and then he told me that he
Villa Cruella what to be empress of
myrrh annika she comes from a long line
of morons from Hoboken
so I'm told yeah that's what I thought
too but the bottom line is whoever finds
a tear of Aisha can crown themselves
Empress it's a slam dunk
anyone can be ruler even you what about
Carol go on when I woke up maybe she
split maybe she got kidnapped you
haven't heard from her nothing now you
understand it's vitally important that
we recover this Idol it's your personal
responsibility this never would have
happened had you taken my advice in the
first place save your speeches I feel
bad enough don't worry
how can I not worry I've got a secret
tell me tell me I placed a small
tracking device on the idols base I've
got a GPS signal onto every move
excellent dr. Jones where is the idol no
I don't know the tracking units broken
but I'm working on it I'll send a tech
over to help out in the meantime please
keep in touch
listen to knock next time okay partner
[Music]
ah
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
mr. Martin sorry I was away from my
phone yeah let me stop by my house
I'll change get my tools and I hunt over
there okay
you have news for me the best excellent
finally a man who does not disappoint
I've got the notebook good Carol your
training has paid off these pages are
blank we didn't have a chance to start
unscrambling the code this is worthless
what now mistress Carol I want you to go
back to dr. Jones tell her you were
kidnapped but managed to escape then I
want you to gain her confidence and see
what you can find out yes mistress
you've done well Drago you deserve a
reward and I alone will give it to you I
am unworthy but I will take it come with
me
[Music]
[Applause]
take this type
[Music]
uhh
Oh
oh yeah yeah sorry go ah
[Music]
yes yes
yes yes more
[Music]
[Applause]
damnit close but not good enough to get
me a signal
Carol dr. Jones what happened to you
after you were knocked on the head
two men grabbed me from the bed and
kidnapped me poor thing
it was terrible just terrible they
thought I knew something so they brought
me to this abandoned warehouse where
they did awful things to me but I
couldn't tell him anything cuz I didn't
know anything you know I know
did they hurt you I'm okay just scared I
guess
when they realized I couldn't help them
they left me there I managed to wiggle
myself loose and rush over here to see
if you were okay Carol you're wearing
different clothes well I went home first
cuz they kidnapped me Wow is naked after
all
of course oh well I'm glad you're okay
what are you doing I managed to put a
tracking device in the base of the idol
really I'd know that well I did but my
tracking device is on the blank and I
can't seem to get it to work can you fix
it
maybe I'm working on it
is there anything you can't do
can't give myself head but I'm working
on that to really know that was a joke
do me a favor go see you that is okay
look what I found mark 10 let me guess
you're here to help you don't look happy
to see me
I don't know time for your CI a boy toy
games I've got a lot of work to do here
that's why I'm here
Lauren thought that I can work the bugs
out of your tracking device knock
yourself out ah what seems to be the
trouble it's not working I got that much
did you drop it or well yeah from about
50 feet up in the air
that sounds pretty reckless even from
you well when you're hanging by a
toenail butt-naked from a Portuguese
hot-air balloon or Olivia your set of
priorities tends to change a bit I guess
so
nice view though huh no one complained
yeah do you mind
go ahead I've got to take off for about
an hour
Carol here I'll keep you company where
are you going
Marvin sent me up with a certain dr.
Xavier seems I'm still a bit foggy up
here hopefully I'll have this up and
running by the time you get back good
luck no let's see if we can fix his baby
[Music]
these places always have to be freezing
then they give you these stupid gowns
with your butt hanging out honestly so
you're dr. Jones
doctor of ancient relics and archaeology
I'm not a medical doctor I'm relieved
for a moment I thought you were trying
to treat yourself
I'm dr. Xavier dr. X I like that so what
seems to be the trouble well this sounds
crazy but I had this guy at gunpoint
real numbskull you know IQ hovering
around room temperature I think I know
the type well I got the drop on this
goon and I was about to handcuff his ass
when someone hit me from behind and then
when I woke up I had a touch of amnesia
I can't remember take one of these this
will help this will help me remember
not exactly but don't make the exam go
by a lot easier okay I'm down for easy
now what give it a moment oh that really
gives a kick oh I feel a mile huh good
cuz we're gonna go on a little trip
I'm tripping right now doctor come on
how about some free love huh 1960 style
well we have a few hours until the plane
leaves I guess we can start the exam
right now doctor I want you to start
from top to bottom and don't leave
anything out
I won't
[Music]
damn it work your little son of a bitch
still no luck it should be working but
it's not too bad
hey wait a minute I see something I
might have found the problem what is it
okay I got the bugs out yeah it's
working
can it locate the idol it's searching
it's gonna take a little while for the
gather to satellite info and provide us
a map so now what now we get this over
to CIA headquarters and that Martin and
the boys get on it stop shouldn't we
wait for dr. Jones
it is her device yeah maybe but I hate
waiting I'd better call Martin
Marda near its mark I got the GPS
working great news
can you locate the idol not clear yet
but I think it sounds way too moronica
just what we suspected as soon as dr.
Jones returns I'll be on my way
one more thing copy that
I'll handle it what'd he say he says we
wait well maybe I can help the time go
quicker well I have been under a little
stress lately
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
you know you're not gonna get away with
this I already have besides you always
wanted to see the temple of arrows
now you can up clos leave it quick
jerking my chain dude mr. Martin did
have a message for you I almost forgot
to tell you what was it about he said
that he found the real Carol Sommers
tied up in a warehouse in Hoboken direct
you were pretty clever and your ploy to
keep me here worked beautifully
dr. Jones isn't coming back is she no
she's not she's probably halfway around
the world by now
well then I'll use this to find her and
effect a rescue what about me
oh I'll call Martin tell them where they
can pick you up
it's been real baby you bastard
[Applause]
some Hill it looked a lot more exotic in
the brochure that's not the devil doctor
that is where we'll meet mr. Sevilla not
exactly a palace shut up and do tough
talk mr. hope you can back it up Wow
what a dump and no homies even the
monster keeps everyone away
this place has out a customer in years
location location location which is why
it is the perfect place for a rendezvous
so a villa Cruella we need it last dr.
Jones you led us on a merry game but
it's over now I'll admit you outsmarted
me you win
release for Drago she has nowhere to run
to
I think you realize that now thank you
it's beginning to get
ring-around-the-collar drink make it a
double
[Applause]
hmm dr. Jones
you're a worthy opponent and this
doesn't have to end here do you tell
when I'm crowned empress of moronica I'm
gonna need a sharp mind like yours
around one that knows her way around
ancient treasures and can handle herself
in tough situations flattery will get
you everything hmm
we'll have all the money we desire the
ancient treasures of Aisha will be ours
to plunder I'm your girl how do I know I
can trust you Oh my minions let's prove
their loyalty to me
how about I put out like a dime-store
diva on a tequila bender huh what'd that
do it mm-hmm
that's a start
ah
[Music]
I'll show you
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
whoa I think I know where the temple is
first you took a right and then the left
and then another right and the left and
then you go straight so what's left
no that's right what's right the left
the left is right the left is right
right can we just go now yeah let's go
[Applause]
[Music]
finally I knew the left was actually a
right and the right was right and
getting him left got the tempo of arrows
ah Dana Freddy's fried chicken come on
what are we waiting for let's go I must
say I thought it would be a bit grander
look ah it's here of Aisha the kingdom
[Music]
here let's try it out for size Wow if
you will fist not so fast
damn it I'll take that well it probably
looks better on you anyway I don't think
so
son of a bitch I'll take that lucky for
us you came along
don't be so sure get your hands up all
of you mr. Martin you yes me do you
think I'm an idiot I let you imbeciles
do all the heavy lifting
no it is my son you yes dr. Jones you
hit the nail on the head when you said
anyone even me it could become Empress
of moronica if they had the tiara Ayesha
and now you have it that's right and I
am now the Emperors of moronica
oh so pretty so pretty and say it yep
you're pretty alright yeah very pretty
no doubt a real looker damn right I am
well dude
that was seriously fucked up let's get
him you can't eat me I'm too pretty Wow
well I guess that's it for him there
goes the tiara he truly was queen for a
day hey that thing's got a poop sometime
are you thinking what I'm thinking first
one in the poop get surprised which one
follow that's an adventure best left for
another day
finally we both agree on something
I have no intention of becoming queen of
the morons that's your job I work for
the rightful owner that Idol the villa
Cruella the heir to the Empire Veronica
[Music]
but he couldn't tell him anything
because I didn't know anything you know
got the bugs out that's right I saw you
on the second floor you do good work
[Music]
[Applause]
and
[Music]
[Applause]