[Music]
this is Martin this is dr. Jones I'm in
cruella industries headquarters
excellent any trouble but I have clean
three floors where the toilets to get
here
excellent work dr. Jones your country
appreciates it
any sign of the idol it's right in front
of me can you secure it its value is
hostile security looks easy enough
that's what worries me
it's our deal still in place yes you
will be allowed to study it for your own
research as long as we know it's not in
the hands of our enemies one want the
CIA going back on their word now no
tricks Jones just get the Idol away from
evil a guerrilla circus it doesn't seem
to be an alarm system in place I'll call
you what Sam outside be careful
don't worry I've stolen my fair share of
idols he's a cake over and out
hmm you will look spectacular in my
trophy case freeze put your hands up
easy lady
what are you doing in here let me guess
silent alarm that's right now I asked
you what were you doing what's it look
like
Einstein I'm the cleaning lady I'm
cleaning up how'd you get in here all
the doors are locked
can I help it I get paid to clean I
finished three floors this was my last
stop that's right I saw you on the
second floor you do good work
Thanks I try well I guess there's no
harm done we better not let anybody know
about this they'll fire one of us for
sure why would I tell anyone I don't
want to lose my job well neither so we
agree this never happened
what happened yeah that's the idea you
know my shift is over now what do you
say you and me seal the deal this way
neither one of us has tempted to talk
about it later you mean you and me right
here in the desk
well I guess no no miss me for a little
while
great let's not waste any time yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh baby you're already starting to give
me good luck and that mr. Martin
it's how I stole the sacred Idol of
arrows - right from under their noses
excellent work dr. Johnson excellent you
know word on the street is that evil a
gorilla is absolutely having a cow over
this and while she might we have to
ensure that this never falls into her
hands again don't forget our deal I keep
the idol for my research and when I'm
done you CIA boys can have it for your
little collection I wish you'd
reconsider our agreement dr. Jones we
can't afford to have that floating
around out there somewhere it won't be
floating anywhere it will be with me
I'll take good care of it you realize
that on that Idol somewhere is the
location of the temple of arrows exactly
and whoever finds the temple finds a
tiara of Aisha exactly and whoever has
the tiara of Aisha shall be the ruler of
the Empire of moronica can you believe
Avilla
Cruella with all her millions still
wants to be ruler of the Empire that's
not gonna happen we're counting on you
listen Martin I'll give you this trinket
as soon as I decipher the map to the
temple that's all I'm interested in and
what then
you hold on to the tiara it's a museum
piece I have no intention of becoming
queen of the morons that's your job
contact me the moment you break the code
ciao baby
[Music]
I want that Idol it's mine by right of
my ancestry perhaps but I thought you
were from Hoboken hoebuck well my
grandpa did settle there but my real
destiny is the Empire of moronica yes of
course this is all very unfortunate I
entrusted my spies to bring me my idol
we had it but it slipped away and I
wanted back how can we help you achieve
your goals mistress I must have that
idol it alone has the location of the
temple of uros with it I can acquire the
tiara of Aisha and rule all of Morocco
and then you will be the supreme Empress
of moronica suits me well don't you
think it does indeed then get me that
Idol I don't care how you do it or by
what means just bring it back to me I
understand that dr. Jones the eminent
archeologist has it in her possession
then you know what to do
rally our spies in America and bring me
that Idol at your command
[Music]
man I feel like I haven't showered in a
week
Oh at least I still smell like a blonde
security guard well I can fix that
[Music]
who the hell are you Carol summers
department of national antiquities
Martin asked me to stop by to see if I
could be of any assistance is that so
well I didn't hear anything about this
and I don't remember asking for any help
well Martin's anxious to have the idol
and safekeeping as long as you possess
it it could fall into the wrong hands
yeah I've heard the spiel can you give
me a moment all right you can just step
outside into the hallway Martin yeah
this is dr. Jones ah doctor everything
all right just calling to check on a
Carol Sommers yes one of yours
Carol is an excellent cipher so am i but
I could use some help might speed up the
process a little that's what we thought
she's very good I'm sure you two will
hit it off I'll let you know
Hey and next time you ask someone to
drop in on me warn me first
understood Carol everything hunky-dory
yeah it's all hunky-dory so what's your
game sister now just your average red
blooded all american egghead I guess too
smart for my own good no luck with the
boys huh no guys don't make passes at
girls who wear glasses that's why I wear
contacts I wish I could but it hurts my
eyes
hmm studying too hard you should get out
more
yeah maybe everything okay oh that's a
whitmark a wit mark
got an Istanbul that's incredible
someone actually whipped you well they
tried but they didn't get away with it I
had a live Cobra in my pants
a live Cobra never underestimate the
power of a highly poisonous and very
pissed-off snake sounds like you've been
through a lot and I've got the bruises
to prove it a person who leads a
dangerous life like you do needs to
relax more maybe but in my line of work
you got to keep on your toes
sounds like you need a massage I studied
Reiki in college Reiki Reiki take itto
be the art of sensuous mongoose massage
are you any good well I haven't had any
luck with the boys but I scored a pretty
high with the girls well Martin did say
you were to lend a helping hand he
didn't say where those hands would be
used so what the hell
[Music]
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
at last the person who possesses its
rules the Empire Doug who wants it this
was too easy hold it okay okay don't
shoot not gently put everything back on
the counter that's a good boy
now tell me who do you work for I think
you already know I work for the rightful
owner of that Idol a villa karela the
heir to the empire moronica you mean the
airhead wait isn't she from Hoboken
well her grandpa settled in Hoboken but
our ancestors were morons make no
mistake about it I'm gonna have to trust
you on that one
unfortunately the idol is mine now and
when I finish the CIA is gonna put it
where the Sun don't shine you don't know
what you're playing with dr. Jones a
villa will go to great lengths to regain
that Idol you could be a very rich woman
what's money to me you could have power
lots of power
I'm already telling the CIA where to
stick it how much more power do I need
you could have rocking sex day and night
nice but I'm a little tired now turn
around and put your hands behind your
back okay but this is gonna hurt you a
lot more than it hurts me
that's what all the boys say good work
Carol I thought you might sleep through
the entire thing dr. Jones takes a lot
out of a woman I'm still a little weak
in the knees cool your jets Carol let's
grab everything and get out of here
before she wakes up see you doctor
thanks for the hot sex
[Music]
terrible news dr. Jones yes I mean what
is are you sure you're all right me of
course am what did you just call me
you're dr. Jones I am oh dear don't you
remember anything that's happened of
course I do I took a shower got to know
Carol a little better and then I found
this strange guy in my house and he was
stealing the idol yes yes I had the
upper hand and then he told me that he
Villa Cruella went to be Empress of
moronica she comes from a long line of
morons from Hoboken so I'm told yeah
that's what I thought too but the bottom
line is whoever finds a tear of Aisha
can crown themselves Empress it's a slam
dunk
anyone can be ruler even you what about
Carol
go on when I woke up maybe she split
maybe she got kidnapped you haven't
heard from her nothing
now you understand it's vitally
important that we recover this Idol it's
your personal responsibility this never
would have happened had you taken my
advice in the first place save your
speeches I feel bad enough don't worry
how can I not worry I've got a secret
tell me tell me I placed a small
tracking device on the idols base I've
got a GPS signal on every move excellent
dr. Jones where is the idol no I don't
know
the tracking units broken but I'm
working on it I'll send a tech over to
help out in the meantime please keep in
touch
awesome to knock next time okay partner
[Music]
you
Oh
[Music]
mr. Martin sorry I was away from my
phone yeah let me stop by my house
I'll change get my tools and I hunt over
there okay
you have news for me the best excellent
finally a man who does not disappoint
I've got the notebook good Carol your
training has paid off these pages are
blank we didn't have a chance to start
unscrambling in the code this is
worthless
what now mistress Carol I want you to go
back to dr. Jones tell her you were
kidnapped but managed to escape then I
want you to gain her confidence and see
what you can find out yes mistress
you've done well Drago you deserve a
reward and I alone will give it to you I
am unworthy but I will take it come with
me
[Music]
take this
Oh
oh yeah yes yes
[Music]
yes yes more
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
damnit close but not good enough to get
me a signal Carol dr. Jones what
happened to you after you were knocked
on the head
two men grabbed me from the bed and
kidnapped me poor thing
it was terrible just terrible they
thought I knew something so they brought
me to this abandoned warehouse where
they did awful things to me but I
couldn't tell him anything cuz I didn't
know anything
you know I know did they hurt you I'm
okay just scared I guess
when they realized I couldn't help them
they left me there I managed to wiggle
myself loose and rush over here to see
if you were okay Carol you're wearing
different clothes well I went home first
cuz they kidnapped me Wow is naked after
all of course oh well I'm glad you're
okay what are you doing I managed to put
a tracking device in the base of the
idol really I'd know that well I did but
my tracking device is on the blank and I
can't seem to get it to work can you fix
it maybe I'm working on it is there
anything you can't do
can't give myself head but I'm working
on that too
really no that was a joke Oh do me a
favor go see who that is okay
look what I found mark 10 let me guess
you're here to help you don't look happy
to see me I don't have time for your CIA
boy toy games I've got a lot of work to
do here that's why I'm here
Marv not that I can work the bugs out of
your tracking device knock yourself out
ah what seems to be the trouble it's not
working I got that much did you drop it
or well yeah from about 50 feet up in
the air
that sounds pretty reckless even from
you well when you're hanging by a
toenail butt-naked from a Portuguese hot
air balloon or Olivia your set of
priorities tends to change a bit I guess
so nice view though huh
no one complained yeah do you mind go
ahead I've got to take off for about an
hour
Carol here I'll keep you company where
are you going
Martin set me up with a certain dr.
Xavier seems I'm still a bit foggy up
here hopefully all this up and running
by the time you get back good luck no
let's see if we can fix his baby
[Music]
these places always have to be freezing
then they give you these stupid gowns
with your butt hanging out honestly so
you're dr. Jones doctor of ancient
relics and archaeology I'm not a medical
doctor I'm relieved for a moment I
thought you were trying to treat
yourself
I'm dr. Xavier dr. X I like that so what
seems to be the trouble well this sounds
crazy but I had this guy at gunpoint
real numbskull you know IQ hovering
around room temperature I think I know
the type
well I got the drop on this goon and I
was about to handcuff his ass when
someone hit me from behind and then when
I woke up I had a touch of amnesia I
can't remember take one of these this
will help this will help me remember
not exactly but don't make the exam go
by a lot easier okay I'm down for easy
now what give it a moment oh that really
gives a kick oh I feel a mile huh good
cuz we're gonna go on a little trip I'm
tripping right now doctor come on how
about some free love huh 1960 style
well we have a few hours until the plane
leaves I guess we can start the exam
right now doctor I want you to start
from top to bottom and don't leave
anything out
I won't
[Music]
dammit work your little son of a bitch
still no luck it should be working
but it's not too bad hey wait a minute
I see something I might have found the
problem what is it
okay I got the bugs out yeah it's
working
can it locate the idol it's searching
it's gonna take a little while for the
gather to satellite info and provide us
a map so now what now we get this over
to CIA headquarters and that Martin and
the boys get on it
stop shouldn't we wait for dr. Jones it
is her device yeah maybe but I hate
waiting I'd better call Martin
Martin here it's mark I got the GPS
working great news
can you locate the idol not clear yet
but I think it's on its way to Monica
just probably suspected as soon as dr.
Jones returns I'll be on my way
one more thing copy that
I'll handle it what'd he say he says we
wait well maybe I can help the time go
quicker well I have been under a little
stress lately
[Music]
ah
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
you know you're not gonna get away with
this I already have besides you always
wanted to see the temple of arrows now
you can up clos leave quick jerking my
chain dude mr. Martin did have a message
for you I almost forgot to tell you what
was it about he said they found the real
Carol summers tied up in a warehouse in
Hoboken direct you were pretty clever
and your ploy to keep me here worked
beautifully dr. Jones isn't coming back
is she no she's not she's probably
halfway around the world by now well
then I'll use this to find her and
effect a rescue what about me oh I'll
call Martin tell them where they can
pick you up
it's been real baby you bastard
Samuel it looked a lot more exotic than
the brochure that's not the devil doctor
that is where we'll meet mr. Sevilla not
exactly a palace shut up and move
tough talk mr. Wow what a dump
and no homies either the monster keeps
everyone away
this place has out a customer in years
location location location which is why
it is the perfect place for a rendezvous
so Avella Cruella we meet at last dr.
Jones you led us on a merry game but
it's over now I'll admit you outsmarted
me
you win release her Drago
she has nowhere to run to I think you
realize that now thank you
it's beginning to get
ring-around-the-collar drink make it a
double
[Applause]
hmm dr. Jones
you're worthy opponent and this doesn't
have to end here do you tell when I'm
crowned empress of moronica I'm gonna
need a sharp mind like yours around one
that knows her way around ancient
treasures and can handle herself in
tough situations flattery will get you
everything hmm
we'll have all the money we desire the
ancient treasures of Aisha will be ours
to plunder I'm your girl how do I know I
can trust you
Oh my minions let's prove their loyalty
to me how about I put out like a dime
store diva on a tequila bender huh what
that mm-hmm that's a start
I'll show you
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
whoa I think I know where the temple is
first you take a right and then the left
and then another right and the left and
then you go straight so what's left
no that's right what's right the left
the left is right the left is right
right can we just go now yeah let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
finally I knew the left was actually a
right and the right was right and
getting him left got the tempo of arrows
ah Dana Freddy's fried chicken come on
what are we waiting for let's go I must
say I thought it would be a bit grander
look ah it's here of Aisha
[Music]
here let's try it out for size well if
you insist
not so fast damn it I'll take that
[Music]
well it probably looks better on you
anyway I don't think so son of a bitch
I'll take that lucky for us you came
along
don't be so sure get your hands up all
of you mr. Martin you yes me do you
think I'm an idiot
I let you imbeciles do all the heavy
lifting
no it is my son you all yes dr. Jones
you hit the nail on the head when you
said anyone even me it could become
Empress of moronica if they had the
tiara Ayesha and now you have it that's
right and I am now the Empress of
moronica
so pretty so pretty
[Music]
say it yep
you're pretty alright yeah you're very
pretty
no doubt a real looker damn right I am
well dude
that was seriously fucked up let's get
him you can't eat me I'm too pretty Wow
well I guess that's it for him there
goes the tiara he truly was queen for a
day hey that thing's got a poop sometime
are you thinking what I'm thinking first
one in the poop get surprised which one
follow that's an adventure best left for
another day
finally we both agree on something
I have no intention of becoming queen of
the morons
that's your job I work for the rightful
owner that Idol the villa Cruella the
heir to the Empire Veronica
[Music]
[Laughter]
but he couldn't tell him anything
because I didn't know anything you know
[Music]
got the bugs out that's right I saw you
on the second floor you do good work
[Music]
[Applause]