you
this is Martin this is dr. Jones I'm in
cruella industries headquarters
excellent any trouble but I have clean
three floors with the toilets to get
here
excellent work dr. Jones your country
appreciates it
any sign of the idol that's right in
front of me can you secure it its value
is House national security looks easy
enough that's what worries me
I deal stolen place yes you will be
allowed to study it for your own
research as long as we know it's not in
the hands of our enemies well I want the
CIA going back on their word now
no tricks Jones just get the idol away
from Villa gorillas and you've done the
world great service it doesn't seem to
be an alarm system in place I'll call
you what I'm outside be careful
don't worry I've stolen my fair share of
idols piece of cake over and out
hmm you will look spectacular in my
trophy case
breathe put your hand up easy lady what
are you doing in here let me guess
silent alarm that's right now I asked
you what were you doing what's it look
like
Einstein I'm the cleaning lady I'm
cleaning up how'd you get in here all
the doors are locked
can I help it I get paid to clean I
finished three floors this was my last
stop that's right I saw you on the
second floor you do good work
Thanks I try well I guess there's no
harm done we better not let anybody know
about this they'll fire one of us for
sure why would I tell anyone I don't
want to lose my job well neither so we
agree this never happened what happened
yeah that's the idea you know my shift
is over now what do you say you and me
seal the deal this way neither one of us
is tempted to talk about it later you
mean you and me right here on the desk
well I guess no no miss me for a little
while
great it's not wasting time
Oh
you
Oh baby she already started to me good
luck and that mr. Martin its how I stole
the sacred Idol of arrows - right from
under their noses
excellent work dr. Johnson excellent you
know word on the street is that evil a
gorilla is absolutely having a cow over
this and while she might we have to
ensure that this never falls into her
hands again don't forget our deal I keep
the idol for my research and when I'm
done you CIA boys can have it for your
little collection I wish you'd
reconsider our agreement dr. Jones we
can't afford to have that floating
around out there somewhere it won't be
floating anywhere it will be what small
I'll take good care of it
you realize that on that Idol somewhere
is the location of the temple of arrows
exactly and whoever finds the temple by
the tiara of Ayesha exactly and whoever
has the tiara of Ayesha shall be the
ruler of the Empire of Myr Annika can
you believe a villa
Krewella with all her millions still
wants to be ruler of the Empire that's
not gonna happen we're counting on you
listen Martin I'll give you this trinket
as soon as I decipher the map to the
temple that's all I'm interested in and
what then you hold onto the tiara the
museum piece I have no intention of
becoming queen of the morons that's your
job
contact me the moment you break the code
ciao baby
I want that Idol it's mine by right of
my ancestry perhaps but I thought you
were from Hoboken whole book well my
grandpa did settled there but my real
destiny is the Empire of moronica yes of
course this is all very unfortunate i
entrusted my spies to bring me my idol
we had it but it slipped away and I want
it back how can we help you achieve your
goals mistress I must have that Idol it
alone has the location of the temple of
uros with it i can acquire the tiara of
aisha and rule all of moronica and then
you will be the supreme empress of
maracas suits me well don't you think it
does indeed then get me that Idol I
don't care how you do it or by what
means just bring it back to me I
understand that dr. Jones the eminent
archaeologist has it in her possession
then you know what to do
rally our spies in America and bring me
that Idol at your command I will have
that Idol
man until I haven't showered in a week
Oh at least still smell like a blonde
security guard well I can fix that
you
Oh
who the hell are you Carol summers
department of national antiquities
Martin asked me to stop by to see if I
could be of any assistance is that so
well I didn't hear anything about this
and I don't remember asking for any help
well Martin's anxious to have the idol
and safekeeping as long as you possess
it it could fall into the wrong hands
yeah I've heard the spiel can you give
me a moment all right you can just step
outside to the hallway Martin yeah this
is dr. Jones ah doctor everything all
right
just calling to check on a Carol Sommers
yes one of yours
Carol is an excellent cipher so am i but
I could use some help might speed up the
process a little that's what we thought
she's very good I'm sure you two will
hit it all off I'll let you know
Hey and next time you ask someone to
drop in on me warn me first
understood Carol everything hunky-dory
yeah it's all hunky-dory
so what's your game sister I'm just your
average red blooded all american egghead
I guess too smart for my own good no
luck with the boys huh no guys don't
make passes at girls who wear glasses
that's why I wear contacts I wish I
could but it hurts my eyes
hmm studying too hard you should get out
more
hmm maybe everything okay oh that's a
whitmark a wit mark
got an Istanbul that's incredible
someone actually with June well they
tried but they didn't get away with it I
had a live Cobra in my pan a live Cobra
never underestimate the power of a
highly poisonous and very pissed-off
snake sounds like you've been through a
lot and I've got the bruises to prove it
a person who leaves a dangerous life
like you do needs to relax more maybe
but in my line of work you got to keep
on your toes sounds like you need a
massage
I studied Reiki in college Riki Riki
Tiki Tavi the art of sensuous mongoose
massage you any good well I haven't had
any luck with the boys but I scored a
pretty high with the girls mm-hmm well
Martin did say you were to lend a
helping hand he didn't say where those
hands would be used so what the hell
at last the person who possesses its
rules the Empire bug who wants it this
was too easy hold it okay okay don't
shoot
not gently put everything back on the
counter that's a good boy now tell me
who do you work for I think you already
know I work for the rightful owner that
Idol
Abdullah karela the heir to the Empire
moronica you mean the airhead wait isn't
she from Hoboken
well her grandpa settled in Hoboken but
her answer says we're morons make no
mistake about it I'm gonna have to trust
you on that one
unfortunately the idol is mine now and
when I finish the CIA is gonna put it
with a Sun don't shine you don't know
what you're playing with dr. Jones
a villa will go to great lengths to
regain that Idol you could be a very
rich woman what's money to me you could
have power lots of power
I'm already telling the CIA where to
stick it how much more power do I need
you could have rocking sex day and night
all right
but I'm a little tired now turn around
and put your hands behind your back okay
but this is gonna hurt you a lot more
than it hurts me
that's what all the boys say good work
Carol I thought you might sleep through
the entire thing
dr. Jones takes a lot out of a woman I'm
still a little weak in the knees cool
your jets Carol let's grab everything
and get out of here before she wakes up
see you doctor thanks for the hot sex
terrible news dr. Jones yes I mean what
is are you sure you're alright well car
Sam what did you just call me you're dr.
Jones I am oh dear don't you remember
anything that's happened of course I do
I took a shower got to know Carol a
little better and then I found this
strange guy in my house and he was
stealing the idol yes yes I had the
upper hand and then he told me that he
Billa Cruella what to be Empress of
moronica she comes from a long line of
morons from Hoboken so I'm told
yeah that's what I thought too but the
bottom line is whoever finds a tear of
Aisha can crown themselves Empress it's
a slam dunk anyone can be ruler even you
what about Carol God when I woke up
maybe she split maybe she got kidnapped
you haven't heard from her nothing now
you understand it's vitally important
that we recover this Idol it's your
personal responsibility this never would
have happened had you taken my advice in
the first place save your speeches I
feel bad enough don't worry
how can I not worry I've got a secret
tell me tell me I placed a small
tracking device on the Isles base I've
got a GPS signal onto every move
excellent dr. Joe where is the idol no I
don't know the tracking units broken but
I'm working on it
house undertaken a doc in the meantime
please keep in touch
awesome to knock next time okay partner
Oh
ah
mr. Martin sorry I was away from my
phone yeah let me stop on my house
I'll change get my tools and I hunt over
there okay
you have news for me the best excellent
finally a man who does not disappoint
I've got the notebook good Carol your
training has paid off these pages are
blank we didn't have a chance to start
unscrambling the code this is worthless
what now mistress Carol I want you to go
back to dr. Jones tell her you were
kidnapped but managed to escape then I
want you to gain her confidence and see
what you can find out yes mistress
you've done well Drago you deserve a
reward and I alone will give it to you I
am unworthy I will take it come with me
good
take this type
not
ah
Oh
oh yeah yeah yeah
yes yes more
yeah
damnit close but not good enough to get
me a signal Terrell dr. Jones what
happened to you after you were knocked
on the head
two men grabbed me from the bed and
kidnapped me poor thing
it was terrible just terrible they
thought I knew something so they brought
me to this abandoned warehouse where
they did awful things to me but I
couldn't tell him anything cuz I didn't
know anything you know I know did they
hurt you I'm okay just scared I guess
when they realized I couldn't help them
they left me there I managed to wiggle
myself loose and rush over here to see
if you were okay Carol you're wearing
different clothes well I went home first
cuz they kidnapped me Wow is naked after
all of course
oh well I'm glad you're okay what are
you doing I managed to put a tracking
device in the base of the idol really I
know that well I did but my tracking
device is on the blank and I can't seem
to get it to work
can you fix it maybe I'm working on it
is there anything you can't do can't
give myself head but I'm working on that
too really no that was a joke do me a
favor with you that is okay
look what I found
mark 10 let me guess you're here to help
you don't look happy to see me I want no
part for your CIA boy toy games I got a
lot of work to do here that's why I'm
here Martin thought that I can work the
bugs out of your tracking device
knock yourself out ah what seems to be
the trouble it's not working I got that
much did you drop it or well yeah from
about 50 feet up in the air
that sounds pretty reckless even from
you well when you're hanging by a
toenail butt-naked from a Portuguese
hot-air balloon or Olivia your set of
priorities tends to change a bit I guess
so
nice view though huh no one complained
yeah do you mind
go ahead I've got to take off for about
an hour
Carol here I'll keep you company where
you going Marty set me up with a certain
dr. Xavier things I'm still a bit foggy
up here hopefully I'll have it up and
running by the time you get back
good luck no let's see if we can fix his
baby
one of these places always have to be
freezing then they give you these stupid
gowns with your butt hanging out
honestly so you're dr. Jones and doctor
of ancient relics and archaeology I'm
not a medical doctor I'm relieved for a
moment I thought you were trying to
treat yourself
I'm dr. Xavier dr. X I like that
so what seem to be the trouble well this
sounds crazy but I had this guy at
gunpoint real numbskull you know IQ
hovering around room temperature I think
I know the type
well I've got the drop on this goon and
I was about to handcuff his ass when
someone hit me from behind and then when
I woke up I had a touch of amnesia I
can't remember take was ease this will
help this will help me remember not
exactly
but I'll make the exam go by a lot
easier okay I'm down for easy now what
give it a moment oh really
gets a kick oh I feel a mile huh cuz
we're gonna go on a little trip I'm
tripping right now doctor come on how
about some free love her 1960 style yeah
well we have a few hours into the plane
leaves I guess we can start the exam
right now doctor I want you to start
from top to bottom and don't leave
anything out there
Oh
ah damn it work your little son of a
bitch
still no luck it should be working but
it's not too bad
hey wait a minute I see something I'm
way to find a problem what is it I think
I got the bugs out yeah it's working
can it locate the idol it's searching
it's gonna take a little while for the
gather to satellite info and provide us
a map so now what now we get this over
to CIA headquarters and that Martin and
the boys get on it stop
shouldn't we wait for dr. Jones it is
her device yeah maybe but I hate waiting
I better call Martin
Varda near its mark I got the GPS
working great news
can you locate the idol not clear yet
but I think it sounds way too moronica
just probably suspected as soon as dr.
Jones returns I'll be on my way
one more thing
copy that
I'll handle it what'd he say he says we
wait huh maybe I can help the time go
quicker well I have been under a little
stress lately
keep moving dr. Chile's you know you're
not gonna get away with this I already
have besides you always wanted to see
the temple of arrows
now you can up clos move it quick
jerking my chain dude mr. Martin did
have a message for you I almost forgot
to tell you what was it about he said
they found the real Carol Sommers tied
up in a warehouse in Hoboken direct you
were pretty clever and your ploy to keep
me here worked beautifully dr. Jones
isn't coming back is she no she's not
she's probably halfway around the world
by now
well then I'll use this to find her and
effect a rescue
what about me I'll call Martin tell them
where they can pick you up
it's been real baby you bastard
some girls it looks a lot more exotic
than the brochure
that's not the devil doctor that is
where we'll meet mr. Sevilla not exactly
a palace shut up and move
tough talk mr. hope you can back it up
Wow
what a dump and no homies either the
monster keeps everyone away
this place has out of customer in years
location location location which is why
it is the perfect place for a rendezvous
so Eve Ella Cruella we need it last dr.
Jones you let us on a merry game but
it's over now I'll admit you outsmarted
me you win
release her Drago she has nowhere to run
to
I think you realize that now thank you
beginning to get ring-around-the-collar
drink make it a double
hmm dr. Jones
you're a worthy opponent and this
doesn't have to end here do you tell
when I'm crowned empress of moronica I'm
going to need a sharp mind like yours
around one that knows her way around
ancient treasures and can handle herself
in tough situations flattery will get
you everything what kind of price hmm
we'll have all the money we desire but
ancient treasures of Aisha will be ours
to plunder I me a girl how do I know I
can trust you
oh my minions let's prove their loyalty
to me how about I put out like a dime
store diva on a tequila bender huh
would that do it mm-hmm since the start
Oh
I'll show you
you
Oh
ah
oh good work
Oh
yeah
hi
whoa think I know where the temple is
first you took a right and then the left
and then another right and the left and
then you go straight so what's left
no that's right what's right the left
the left is right the left is right
right can we just go now yeah let's go
finally I live the life was actually
right and the right was right and
Gillingham left that the simple arrows
ah Dana Freddy's fried chicken come on
where we waiting from Stoke I must say
not it would be a bit grander look Oh
hirabai Isha Kingdom Annika
here let's try it out for size Wow if
you insist
not so fast damn it I'll take that
well it probably looks better on you
anyway
hmm I don't think so son of a bitch I'll
take that
lucky for us you came along don't be so
sure
get your hands up all of you mr. Martin
you yes me do you think I'm an idiot I
let you imbeciles do all the heavy
lifting now it is my day in the Sun you
all yes dr. Jones you hit the nail on
the head when you said anyone even me
could become Empress of moronica if they
had the tiara of Aisha and now you have
it that's right and I and now the
Empress of Monica
ah so pretty so pretty huh
say it yep
you're pretty alright yeah you're very
pretty
no doubt a real looker damn right I am
well dude that was seriously fucked up
let's get him you can't eat me I'm too
pretty
Wow well guess that's it for him there
goes the tiara he truly was queen for
there hey that thing's got a poop some
time are you thinking what I'm thinking
first one in the poop get surprised
which one follow that's an adventure
best left for another day
finally we both agree on something I
have no intention of becoming queen of
the morons that's your job I work for
the rightful owner that idle a Villa
Cruella the heir to the Empire Veronica
but it couldn't tell anything cuz I
didn't know anything you know
got the buzz oh that's right I saw you
on the second floor you do good work
Oh
you
yeah
you won't regret
Oh
you don't
ah
you
Oh