=======================
Author: truc1979, Reviewer: DNR
Fix or feedback: please let me know
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
[♪ Tango music ]
[♪ Por una cabeza ]
Congratulations on becoming agent Rachel.
I knew you had it in you.
Unfortunate about your husband though.
Yes.
Well, I could not let my feelings
for George compromise the mission.
Oh... Sorry.
Sorry!
Sorry...
Nice tits.
Does your husband appreciate these?
No... Husband doesn't appreciate anything.
Bull!
Dead fool.
Ah, George never does that.
George couldn't even make coffee.
Oh God Agent X, That's what a real fucking
secret-agent dick feels like.
Yeah.
- You can't teach that on training.
- No.
I don't need that anymore.
George never makes me come.
George is a fool.
No evidence.
Mission complete.
- Ah!
(- Ah)
Jesus Christ.
George you scared the crap out of me.
Yeah? You should see it
from my point of view.
Dreamed about
that damn fish tank again?
Yeah. Something like that.
Thank you.
Oh I have my cereal.
Oh you think so?
Yeah. I do.
You feeling lucky?
Would you try to come take it?
Oh, I will.
You call yourself a secret agent,
no wonder
they won't give you a promotion.
Argh.
Holly bitch.
Hey honey, I was thinking
we could ride in together.
I take it as a "no".
Ladies first.
Age before beauty.
Brains before stupidity.
What I meant was you're the stupid one, ok?
(- Idiot)
(I'm the smart one.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT)
I meet you up--
Everybody knows that.
No.
Oh...
Oh no.
Oh yeah, you want some of this.
[composing phone number]
[phone rings]
I spank you like a red-headed stepchild.
Oh no you didn't!
Can't believe you stick my spot.
Oh, is this your spot?
You're dirty. You're dirty. Damn it.
(Hi Rachel)
Morning fellows.
(Good morning)
I made brownies!
Who wants some?
You don't have to do that.
I had to park 4 blocks away.
Well. Now you've had your cardio.
Those are the last of the brownies,
isn't it?
I didn't even get one.
Oh, honey...
You've to watch your girlish figure.
It's not fair Rachel.
You know I wanted a brownie.
George, life's not fair.
That's one hell of a woman.
One hell of a good cook.
Yeah, well you try being married
to her for 6 years.
Rachel: SEVEN!
I'm sorry the lack of sex
is making my memory blurry.
[beep]
Sorry you got to remove
all metal from your pockets.
[beep]
All metal.
Looks like we're gonna be
a little more thorough.
Ah!
Sam, it's time
for a deep body cavity search.
Agent X: So there I was...
...surrounded by the enemy...
...deep in the jungles of Bolivia...
...unarmed and then suddenly I...
Agent Z?
Yes Sir.
You're late.
Yes Sir,
there was a malfunction at security.
I apologize Sir.
- Malfunction...?
- Yeah.
I'll tell you what though...
I've got a big mission for you.
What?
(Yes Sir)
Go down to the break room
and give me a cup of coffee.
[laughs]
You know how I like it.
As I was saying,
bullets buzzing over my head.
I had no weapon.
Suddenly, from the canopy above,
came the enemy: *zeeee*.
- Hi!
- Argh!
Oh... Hi Amy.
Ah, sorry,
I didn't mean to startle you.
No, it's okay,
it's a...  I'm a little on edge.
Too much caffeine.
Well, I must compliment you
on your cat-like reflexes.
Oh...
Yeah, I was... uh...
Comes with being a secret agent.
I'll have to be a little bit
more careful around you.
I didn't know
you could be so... dangerous.
Yeah, that's... that's me:
dangerous you know.
You could... lose an eye.
[laughs]
Hmm... Speaking of danger,
I have something to show you.
Won't you come in?
How... cool!
(Wow)
[amazed laughs]
This is cool!
What does this do?
Oh, be careful with that,
I'm having a lot of problems with it.
[George's smelling]
It contains nerve gas, but it keeps leaking.
A mini supercomputer.
Complete. With wireless internet.
Digital camera.
MP3 player.
Cigarette lighter. Even an AM/FM radio.
Can I have it?
No.
What's this?
Hum...
That's...
That's... That's my vibrator.
So you're planning on doing
a little fly-fishing?
Oh that?
That is my pride and joy.
It's impenetrable.
Watch.
[gunshot]
Wow!
You're crazy.
Watch this.
[sound of arrow]
Okay, I get it.
This vest is specially designed.
to increase the adrenaline
and testosterone of its wearer.
Giving him more strength, endurance.
Even enabling him to run faster.
Well you think he could've made it
a little bit more fashionable.
I mean it looks like a fishing vest.
Do I look like
I know anything about fashion?
Oh..! No no no, you know...
No, the vest works. It's um...
You know it's just got lots of...
...convenient pockets.
It has an internal cooling system.
that regulates body temperature
and increases stamina.
Imagine what that could do
for you under fire.
Just think what it could do
for me in the bedroom.
I already have.
George: [um-um]
This is my latest invention:
Training goggles.
It can create virtually
any situation imaginable.
Really?
From flying to combat. Try.
(Okay)
Wow.
That's cool. You do anything?
Anything.
- Anything?
- Anything.
You want to ***.
You don't know how long it's been.
Oh god you're naughty.
Oh yes George take it.
You know you've always wanted
that tight little fucking ass of mine.
Alright in that tight fucking ass?
Okay, that was a little weird.
You don't know how long
I've waited for that.
You tricked me!?
You lured me down here
to take advantage of me.
You... you gadget siren.
Oh... So...?
Oh come on you know I like you.
I'm married, I feel so violated.
It wasn't real.
Felt real!
Don't! Don't touch me!
Predator.
[Rachel's smelling]
- Where have you been?
- Huh? What?
You've been gone over an hour.
X was looking for you.
He was?
Yeah. He needed his coffee.
Oh, yeah, right.
So?
- So what?
Rachel: So where were you?
I was taking care of business
in the lab.
Business, huh?
And was this "business"
wearing a white lab coat.
and reeking
a fake designer perfume?
What are you talking about?
Don't play stupid with me, George.
That little trollop, Amy.
What about her?
George I'm serious.
I know that you know that she knows
that we're... having marital issues.
She's like a vulture waiting
on the wings.
You're a crazy Lady.
Haha. I'm crazy?
I'M CRAZY?
I'm not the one was provoked
by a glass of milk this morning
I'm not the one that hassled
the security guards,
and we won't even discuss your bouts
of mourning road rage
WHAT??
I did not harass those security guards
you set me up, and for your information
they proceeded
to get very intimate with me
I guess I should be grateful
because it's the closest thing I'm
head to sex in months
There you go again,
always with the sex
We know what George?
Maybe if you learn a little technique
instead of humping me
like a drunken Chihuahua
I would be a little more
willing to participate
- Really?
- Yeah!
Really?
Is there a problem here?
Together: NO SIR
Good
Rachel, I would like to see you alone,
please
Absolutely
- Z?
- Yes?
- Where's my coffee?
- Coming up, Sir
"Where's my coffee?"
Rachel, have a seat
I am sitting, Sir
Right
Rachel... I need you.
Excuse me?
Your help.
Oh
You're the only one
that I can trust.
I have to go on a secret mission
No one here even knows about it
I can't help it, but I have a
feeling it may be my last
Really, Sir?
I don't think there's any coming back
from this one, kid
Sir...
Don't cry
It's the terrorists
The Middle Eastern ones
You know... those guys...
mm-hmm
They've developed
a plan to destroy the world
and I have to go and steal the magic
ingredients to the weapon
(Ah... weapons)
- Rachel?
- Yes, Sir?
X:
I need you to help me save the world
Rachel: Huh... The whole world?
Can you do that? Can you be a hero?
Yes, Sir
Good
Here's what I need for you to do
Take this cellphone,
guard it with your life
I'm going to be meeting my contacts
and they are very dangerous men
and they are going to want to know
that I am who I say I am
Do you understand?
Not really, Sir
Gonna take me into custody
They're gonna dial that phone
for a code
If you don't give him that code,
or you don't answer that phone
I'll be killed
Now you understand?
Rachel: Huh... I think so, Sir
X: Protect that with your life
From now on, you shall be known
as agent...
..."D"
Rachel: "D"?
Any questions?
What's the code word?
Code word?
Right
Huh...
Hmm... "Peppermint"
"Peppermint"?
X: "Peppermint"
Now go.
I've to prepare
for this kind of mission
But Sir...
[X: tears in voice] Please. Go.
Hmm?
Uh! George!
What... What are you doing?
Here you go, Sir
You know I like two sugars
You're dismissed
[George is laughing slowly]
What's so funny?
You don't actually believe that
secret mission crap, do you?
Rachel: hmm
Oh my god, you do!
That's the oldest trick
in the book
He just wants to fuck you
You're jealous
Jealous that I got a mission
You are a secretary
No one's gonna give you a mission
I am an administrative assistant
but I guess you know a thing or two
about not getting missions now,
wouldn't you?
Well, except fetching coffee
Now why would you have to go there,
okay?
I was just trying to warn you,
he's trying to get in your pants.
All he'd to do is ask.
What did you say?
I said don't be such an ass
[sigh]
What is it with you
and that fish tank anyway?
This is going to be
the perfect underwater ecosystem
And I will be its God
You are not right
Yeah
Well at least I'm not waiting by
a phone that's never going to ring
It will ring
Why don't you have a little faith that
he'll accomplish the mission?
You just don't get it
He's not on a secret mission
Nobody knows anything
about a secret mission
That's because it's secret, duh!
Honey, you know nothing of protocol
You really think he would tell a secretary
about a secret mission?
I am an administrative assistant!
Let me see if I get this straight:
The story is there's a group of terrorists
and they've built a bomb
and they've threatened to
blow up the planet Earth
But alas this will be
his last call of duty
And his fate rests squarely
in palms of your hands
You're the only one he can trust
His last hope
Bla bla bla bla bla bla
Rachel: Huh
George: Yeah
Listen, that's a story
he gave his last secretary
Rachel, listen, don't get mad
[tazzer sound]
George: Aargh!
[Breathes]
That was totally unnecessary
You just... pist because
you're fighting for Agent X.
in a faraway tropical island.
...getting his dick sucked by a native girl.
Do not make me
tazz you twice in the same night
Okay
[tazzer sound]
I am an administrative assistant!
[George cries]
She's crazy
Jesus, who are you, for God sake
I think I just found heaven.
What do you think of this little swine?
Isn't it cute?
Beautiful
It's not to say
say what we "swine"
it's just things with asses
you know it's so much fun to say.
Isn't it terrific?
You like this little swine here?
Do you like more swine?
This is like the other other pink meat,
but how about some white meat?
Excuse me
No no, seriously
let's just take a bite together
Let me-- Let me lick your hole.
Nah, seriously. Oh come on...
Another one for "special agent man"
Thank you
So how do you say your name?
"Lei Mi" (lay me)
[smiling]
Well, if you insist...
Yeah... like I haven't heard that one bi--
Wait a minute, you're not gay?
No
So, you didn't know that this is a gay,
lesbian, bisexual, transgender luau?
Ah... No.
I didn't.
Um.
About that name.
You know the offer still stands
But you might want to hurry because my country
could call me into service at any moment
As a matter of fact...
I'm expecting a call from the
President of the United States
[phone rings]
Oh... There he is
Hold that.
[phone rings]
Yes, Mr President.
Yes Sir, it's me Sir.
That's top-secret
Of course, Sir
You know you can count on me
Yes Sir. Goodbye Sir
So uh... to some... yeah... everything ok?
Yeah
I'll ship out in an hour
Wow... Then I guess...
Guess we... Better hurry
Call me Mr Secret Agent
Yeah Mr Secret Agent man,
*** that cock in my pussy
Well uh...
... I guess I should be going
Yeah, that thing...
- Yeah the... President...
- Yeah
Jesus Christ...
You bitch!
Oh my god
Are you okay?
[2001, Space Odyssey's theme]
[phone rings]
Don't you even think about it!
Oh shit!
Oh shit! Idiot!
Me?
You want to tackle me!
You should've gone in my phone
in the first place.
It was my secret mission
But now you've upset
my pristine ecosystem
Would you shut up
about your ecosystem?
Just get it out.
Here
...that does not work anymore.
Thank you captain Obvious
Oh.
Oh! Oh my god.
Do you think he's dead?
No
[Indistinct chatting]
Good morning everyone,
I am agent J
from the Washington field office
I'm afraid I have some terrible news
One of ours is missing.
Agent X has disappeared
All we know is
he left for an unknown destination
(and has not been heard of since Friday afternoon)
[Rachel's speaking to George]
All communication attempts have failed
and we are forced to use all
of our resources at hand
[Rachel starts crying]
(The search and rescue...)
She's really upset, sorry
You shut your hole.
- We can't leave him--
- Rachel, listen!
Okay!
Rachel, you need to get yourself together
Did you hear them?
- Shhh!
- Terrorist!
What if they bomb the United States?
What if they find out I'm responsible?
- I DON'T WANT TO BA A TRAITOR!
- Rachel! Rachel!
- Get yourself together
- Ouch
Ouch!
Rachel, listen!
Did anybody else hear your
conversation that you had with X?
- No
- Okay, good
Now we're gonna march back in there
and we're gonna act as
if we know nothing, okay?
I don't want to go back...
Hey hey hey, you want to be
brought up in treason charges?
No? Have you ever been to prison?
Okay
Now we're gonna go back in there
we're gonna act as if we know nothing
until I come up with a plan
You got that?
Shake your head yes that you got it.
Good. Now let's go.
Rachel!
This way!
Rachel.
[Indistinct chatting]
(Get yourself together...)
No no no
Yes, this is where the best
place to catch crab is.
[Indistinct chatting]
Yeah, give that
[Rachel coughs]
...toast.
You need to get yourself together.
Do you understand me?
Sit down. Sit
- Act normal, keep it together, yes.
- You understand?
Keep it together.
- Rachel isn't it?
- Maybe
May I have a word with you in private
Hey you!
Bring me a cup of coffee
(Help... help... help...)
So... I understand
that you're agent X's secretary
Administrative a...ssistant
Right
Well since
you worked so closely with him,
(I'm just a little curious
who've you overheard)
(anything strange the last few days)
(Maybe notice
anything out of the ordinary)
(He didn't discuss
anything with you?)
(Mentioned taking a trip?)
(Think hard)
Well, British intelligence have informed
us of a possible terrorist threat
This is not what we need right now
with our biggest agent missing
We're still waiting for more information
to come in from the Brits
I'm gonna go check on some possible
leads on agent X
In the meantime I want you
to sit next to the fax
and call me the instant
something comes in.
I'm depending on you
Yes Sir
I mean Ma'am
Yes... Ma'am
Not again
[sound of door]
- Hey
What are you doing still here?
You didn't actually think I was
gonna leave you now, did you?
We have our problems and everything
But in 6 years marriage,
I ever let you down
Seven... We've been married 7 years.
Seven years, four months, two days
Come here
Right here? Wait.
We can't do this, out here.
Come on, in here
You know
you don't have to wait with me
I know, but everybody's gone home
for the day
I figured... keep you some company
Um
That feels good
You like that?
What are you doing?
What? I thought we could fool around.
At a time like this?
You're an insensitive prick.
What's wrong with you?
Great. Now I'm a prick
Well you know what?
You are a frigid bitch
Fuck you!
No. Fuck you!
[Fax's noise]
You can't really be serious about this
Oh I'm serious
George, wait, shouldn't we
call someone, you know, for backup?
You saw the report, there's no time.
The terrorists are gonna bomb
the US in a couple of days
The British agents are already in route
Exactly why we should call for backup
Why? so they could pass the
assignment under somebody else?
So I can get overlooked. Again.
Rachel, I'm fucking tired of
getting coffee and dry-cleaning
So this is about you?
No!
(Well... maybe)
You selfish jerk
I don't think risking my life
for my government is selfish
It's patriotic
Besides,
if you hadn't killed our top operative
I wouldn't be forced to do this
Fine. Well I'm going with you
No. No, no. You're not
You said it yourself:
I'm responsible so I'm going
No way
If you won't let me go, I'm telling.
Fine
Yes! My first mission as an agent
You're not an agent.
You're a secretary
I am an administrative assistant
Did you hear that? Terrorist
I got to call Washington.
You're not calling anyone my dear
[guy's screaming]
[phone dialing]
It's me. We've got a problem
[beep]
- Oh like it's gonna work for you
- Tsss
You don't even know a code.
Um
How did you do that?
Honey, you forget:
in addition
to being able to type 87 words a minute
I can hack into anything
Impressed
As you should be
"As you should be"
Wow
Grab the bag
Oh yeah, you're mine now
George, I really don't think there's
gonna be time for fishing
This isn't a fishing vest
This is a high-tech fight
enhancing super vest
Right. You know you don't have
to make shit up, George
Follow me
[George's laughing]
That's what I'm talking about
Is that
one of those penis extension things?
What?
Feeling a little "inferior"?
Are you, George?
I'm surprised
you even remember that I have a penis
- Ouch
- Don't touch
- Maybe a knife
(- Hey!)
- No, I definitely want that one.
- Hey hey
Back away from the weaponry
- I want gun
- No
- George, I want a gun!
How the hell
do you expect me to defend myself?
Satisfied?
You've got to be kidding me
Listen: go to the house pack a few things.
Essentials only
I'm gonna go try and secure it right
in here for something... inconspicuous.
Try not to shoot yourself
What is all this?
Essentials.
Okay.
Do you understand we're going undercover?
Yeah
That's why I need so many disguises. Duh!
Okay. You know, fine. Have it your way
I don't care
if I am not carrying this luggage
Not one single piece
Wait!
This is our inconspicuous ride?
No one's ever gonna guess
where we're going
Rachel, just get in the van.
Fine. Get the bags
- I ain't getting the bags!
- George, bags!
- Not getting the bags.
- George get the fucking bags.
The Falcon has left the nest
Who is it?
The fox is in the henhouse
What?
The 2 idiots are on their way to you!
Ah, what the ***
for the god's sake.
Okay okay,
here we go: capital of Finland
Helsinki
No no no.
How many times do I have to tell you:
Form it as a question
What is Helsinki?
Yes!
Efendi, please excuse the interruption,
but the British are coming
I know this one:
Who is Paul Revere (?)
No, no, Sir
The British are coming now
Here, English agents, they're on to us
Why are you tell me this?
Uh... Okay...
Scout the area, find out where the
infidels keep their camp
and destroy them
Yes, Effendi
(Sighs) Well, if my plan to take over
the world doesn't work
I always have plan B
"Plan B", Sir?
Hum! Right.
Why do you think I see your tushy?
Want to know how much I like that?
Honey, Look at this:
Survey says I like it
That's it, fuck my asshole
This is why I'm gonna be a bigger star
Yeah, okay
- I love you considerate that--
- Keep on saying that to yourself.
You like it?
-Yeah
[Actress] This is good camera angle?
Last time I check.
It's really hot out here
You should put some sunscreen on, baby
(Okay)
- Agents?
- Argh!
Shhhh!
I am Ahmed Abdul Al-ahjeer
Durka-durka Martinez Junior
But you can call me Bob
I'm your contact!
I'm gonna take you to your base camp
But we gonna hurry up before we're seen
I work with you guys as an Agent expert,
for the states all the time.
Honey, hold still.
I've located the British agents
Send 3 men to cut them off at the path
Take no prisoners
Meet me back at the palace
[goat and camel noises]
What a shithole
Yes Watson, I don't see our
bloody contact anywhere
We're gonna have to move fast
Hostiles are everywhere
We need some transport Watson.
Get us a ride
Should I contact HQ sir?
- Nonsense we move in as planned
- Ah!
Now just get us a ride, would you?
What? What the bloody?
What the bloody has he gone?
Watson? What the bloody are
you doing over there?
Hello there, do you speak english?
- Okay
- Alrighty then, um...
- I will take the...
[waiter is spitting]
...brand a double mocha with extra cream
And do you have any muffins?
[waiter's speaking arabic]
Hmm... Guess not.
Do you take credit cards?
- Watson?
- Yes Sir
What nerves(?) are you doing?
Having a coffee Sir, it's a sandbox.
Sandbox?
[waiter's speaking arabic]
- Uh, Good Lord
[goat's bleating]
Watson, it's a goat!
It's an indigenous species, Sir
- Watson!
- Yes Sir
Where's the ride?
- Sir?
- Yes?
If you look very close,
I don't think there's any taxis
Watson, just get us our bloody ride,
would you?
- Can I take my coffee, Sir?
- No! Quick.
Got any donuts?
[speaks arabic]
No! I said donuts. Oh, shit.
Rachel: Why we stop?
- Wait guys...
My instincts...
...they tell me there's danger
Your instincts, huh?
I don't see anything
I think your instincts are wrong
[gunshots]
Oh!
I'll kill them
Definitely, my favorite dress in there.
Aargh... Virgins here I come
Sweetie...!
Oh my God, that's awesome.
I didn't know that
Run!
Oh that's just dirty.
Can we go now?
Yeah
Honey? A little help, come on
Uh...
Here's your bag, sweetie.
[a dog's whining]
[Traditional arabic music]
Haha, this had better be good
Efendi, I have located
the agent south of the palace
but these are different from the rest
They want us to know they are here
It's like they are taunting us
and I think they have
the American agent with them
Only he would be so bold
I think his name is X
Hold on a second
[Hussein coughs]
Agent X is here and you're sure?
He took out some of our best men
It's got to be him
But we've captured a prisoner
(Find Abdul,)
tell him to double the guard
watch and get out there
I want to know everything
they're doing
They take a shit
I want to know about it
Okay, they take a crap I don't
need to know about that
But anything else I'm gonna know about it,
you understand?
And you interrogate the prisonner, okay?
- Yes Effendi
- Go
This room is very beautiful
It must certainly is,
but not as beautiful as you
Your beauty is as expansive as the desert
You are like an oasis
Oh...
Look at me
Do not fear my power
What?
Oh!
My maid must have left this. Nevermind
Look into my eyes.
I want your passion
You're so powerful
- The treasures ***
- Abdul!
Abdul!
I've been looking all over
the palace for you.
What are you doing in my room?
(This is not your room?)
And what is Teddy doing on the floor?
Let... Let me explain...
Explain what?
That you have one of Hussein's
concubines in my bed?
If he finds out
he'll cut off both our balls
I will not tell
You know what? Begone with yourself
Be out of here before someone sees you
Yes... A thousand pardons... [arabic]
I should kick your ass, but I have no time
Hussein needs us. Dress quickly
Huh.
Wait a minute.
Some of my cases are missing
And where's Muffy?
Has anybody seen Muffy?
What's a "muffy"?
Muffy's my baby!
We have to go find Muffy
She could be in the desert all by herself
Rachel, get a hold of yourself.
We CANNOT go back
Alright? There's no way she'd survive
the heat of the desert
She's the casualty of war
My baby...
Hey look is this your shoe bag?
These are the new summer collection
See.
See how easily she forgot about Muffy
You know that could be me out there
I though she you'd knew the difference...
but married 6 years.
Seven!
Seven years
Seven looooong years
[camel grunting]
Ooh
Watson, this is not what I had in mind
You've been
on that damn thing all night, sir.
surely it's my turn to ride
Soon Watson, soon.
Remember those hostiles everywhere
I must keep a lookout
Oh
- What is it?
- I see something in the distance
Where?
Look alike southeast of our position
Pass me my lens
What do you see?
What is it?
I don't quite know Watson.
I can't make it out
Good God
I think the hit
he's gotten to me man
[aaargh (George's making a big effort)]
Stop trying to force it, George.
It's really tight
Try sliding it in gently
[George's forcing]
Gently
Hold on
Okay
[camel's grunting]
Stop! Identify yourself
Agent Jackson Watson,
British Intelligence
Now where the hell were you today?
You could have cost us the mission, man
What?
I made my pickup I don't understand
The agents are...
Yoohoo!
Who the hell are you?
(- You???)
(- What?)
Wooo... I like your camel!
Are you guys on a mission too?
Identify yourself, what's your agency?
Field agent Z, had a command a CIA
You liar
I'm sorry this is my husband Geroge
He watches the mission files
in our building
And I am the director's administrative
assistant, Rachel
You guys must be the British
fellows who sent me the fax
Pleased to meet you folks
Good God what are you both doing here?
This is a Code Red top-secret mission
Not a sightseeing tour
Okay, we'll take it from here
You two, back in the camp while
we'll do recon of the area,
and 0500 hours okay(?)
Yes. Stay close to your tents
Oh, don't get in our way
- Hey, I think we can be of service
- Yeah
Yes I think you might
Be a good man and go make me
a nice cup of tea.
I'm rather parched.
Honey, your reputation precedes you
Shut up Rachel
So not really gonna stay in our tent
to let them have all the fun, are we?
Yeah.
Those limey bastards... Who they think they are?
Secret agents or something?
Uuuuh... They are
Oh... yeah... right
Oh...
I have an idea
You know what we should do?
We should get that nerve gas
that you had
and put it in their tent and then,
after they're asleep,
We can go to the palace and steal
the map to the warehouse
That's a great idea
Why do I have to go
gas him in the tent?
I thought you were the leader
and if I was a leader that's
what I would do
Yes, of course
I knew that
I was just testing you, and you did well
I want to go prepare the equipment
Who do you work for?
Tell me who sent you
Where is the camp?
Your silence only angers me
Oh!
Look at the will(?)
Dog. Little dog
Hum. Leave the prisoner with me
Thank you
- Pfff
- Dismissed
We'll get the will(?) puppy wuppy
You're so sweet
I think I'll name you Jihad
Wanna dance?
So that's the way, uh-ha uh-ha,
I like it
[snorking]
[*noise of camera taking a photo*]
Which tent do you think they're in?
I think it's that one
- That one?
- Yeah
With the Union Jack?
- Yeah I think so
- That's a good guess
- Yeah
- Yeah, okay.
[*gas is leaking*]
Guys, remember:
The only way inside the palace office,
without setting off the alarm,
is going to be through the roof
Once you're inside,
the map is going to be
inside the desk
- Got it?
- Okay
Got it
[body felt on the floor]
Honey?
How did you get in here?
Front door. It's unlocked
Okay
- I'm gonna find the office
- Okay
It's this way
Okay
Rachel, wait
You set off the alarm.
That was amazing
Did you forget
how flexible my body is?
Well considering the fact that
you never let me see it anymore
I've forgotten quite a few
things about your body
Not now, George. Really
It's locked
- George?
- Uh?
I found it
- Lets get out of there
- Okay
[*crash*]
[*alarm*]
Come on Rachel
- Go, go
- There's a problem George
[*gunshots*]
Oh...
Watson, the full of my head's been
bashed in
I think it was this, sir
Those damned Americans
They're gonna get us killed, Watson
They think they're Cowboys or something
Too much television I'd say
What the hell was you thinking?
You're gonna get us all killed
This isn't a game
You do anything like that again,
and I will...
You'll what?
I'll be forced to kill you
[Rachel's laughing]
I would like to see you try
[tazzer]
Ha ha ha
That's smart, doesn't it?
Oh you gotta watch her with that,
she's like a ninja
Anything you'd like to add?
We got the map
You what? Well done!
So we're team now, right?
♪ You want our help ♪
Good! Say it!
Say it!
Yes, yes, we need your help
Oh, and I also got you this
On here you'll find all the
reconnaissance photos
to get you safely into the palace
Excellent work my dear
What the hell happened to you, man?
Oh well I had to take out a couple
of guards too
In fact I killed them with my bare hands
I got rid of the bodies,
I dragged them far away
They'll never be found so, you know,
you don't have to worry
Won't come back on you
Yes. Quite the hero he was
Oh. Good job, man.
I was wrong about you
I thought you were just a pen pusher
Well... We got lots of training to do
We've to go over the intel reports
that Rachel gather.
Argh... Watson?
Yes?
That's one tough burd(?), Watson.
I should say
[♪ camera shutter]
Nice
You're okay, sir?
No. I'm not okay
Get a cup of tea?
Two sugars
Yeah, ok, I go get some, sir
Let's go! Ladies,
let's look alive here.
Let's go, move it, push it up,
yeah, that's right Jackson
Move it, up and down, up and down
Watson, good job!
Go, go, go
I'm okay!
[*crash*]
Okay, now listen up
Me and Watson will take out
the palace guards here
and here
Moving forward to the throne room
and take out Husein
Rachel, George,
take Bob's Jeep,
go to the warehouse
Go to the warehouse
and disarm the weapon,
by removing the uranium warhead
Now don't mess this up
Is everyone clear?
Yes, sir
Good
Watson, what are you doing?
Something to remember our trip together
Good God, man.
This is not a bloody lads holidays,
this is a mission
Now move out
Not that cheap, it's almost paid off(?)
- Nicely done(?), sir.
- Thank You Watson.
Listen Watson,
We have the element of surprise on our side.
Any idea?
we can't going guns blazing.
So you have your silencer?
And knife
Then you go on fire, and kill anyone
you come across
Anyone?
Yes. Anyone, man,
if you want to get out alive.
- Is that clear?
- Crystal
Follow me
[*Indistinct girls voices
in the background*]
- You hear that?
Oh my God...
I've died and gone to heaven
Don't worry, I'll take out this
What are you doing, man?
You forgot your training?
Hostiles, sir
Kill anyone I see
It's them or me, that's what you said
Goodness me, have you forgot what
is to be a British agent?
To protect our fine country, sir
Oh my God, no no no,
to be licensed to kill,
and licensed to fuck the finest
women the world has to offer
Ah...
So this is not the time to kill
No
No no no,
this is time to "party"
- Yes
- No no no, don't, no
What are you doing in these chambers,
it is forbidden
- You can scream and I'll just know it
- Oh...
Don't worry
We would not alert the guards to
the presence of our rescuers
Rescuers?
You're here to rescue us, aren't you?
Of course we are! Yes,
Yes, we're here to rescue.
We're just glad you're all in one piece
We have not seen men like you before
We only see one man
Oh... That's nice... I guess
Nice? Have you seen him?
Holy Jesus!
Uh... Nasty
You see?
Well, yes, I do
Well, we must be awful.
We're gonna clear the palace
to rescue you of course
Wait!
You must do one thing for us
before you leave
You must pleasure us before
you leave this place
What? All of you?
My God. I did die and go to heaven
God damn it
Hostiles on the road
What could I do?
You know, I have an idea
I want to use the big gun
Rachel, this is not a big gun,
this is a rocket launcher
Whatever it is, I want to use it
- It's my turn
- No, no
- Yes
- Rachel, no
Yes
No
If you don't let me use it, you never
gonna see my naked body again
Oh, and that's any different
from now how?
Aw, just thinking you know,
it's really hot out here
Look at me... you...
how cute you look in those
desert camel outfit
- Good
- Yeah
You know,
how much I wanna touch your big,
hard, rocket?
[*sigh*]
[*bang*]
See George,
that's the problem with you:
Alyways premature
Rachel, shut up, come on.
Let's get out of here
30,000 FEET ABOVE THE EARTH,
EVIL SWOOPS IN
On the way
Target acquired.
Go, go, go
I think you should try
to make it to the door
Maybe it's unlocked
Come on hop with me
Ready?
What are you doing?
I think we should go by the window
and yell for help, okay?
George, that's a stupid idea
Come on this way
No
- This way
- No, this way
[Together:] - THIS WAY
No!
Ah!
Oh, fuck
(Ouch)
Idiot...
I can't believe you blew up Bob's Jeep.
Me?
ME?
I can't fucking believe I brought
you on this mission
After six years of marriage,
you think I've learned my lesson,
but no.
My dumb ass brings your dumb ass
halfway around the world
so you can make me look
like a bigger dumbass
Unbelievable!
Wow,
Little pent-up, aren't you?
- You think.
- *ouch*
Can a man just get a little head,
just a little,
just a little sucky sucky,
a blow job here and there?
Have you lost your mind?
Are you crazy?
We're in this mess because
you blew up the Jeep
[George coughs]
This- was- your- fault
My fault?
How the fuck is this my fault?
"Oh you're so sexy in the uniform".
Blah blah blah
If you weren't busy molesting
a rocket launcher,
I wouldn't have accidentally set it off
Are you kidding me?
Rachel,
Do you've any idea how hard it is to be
married to a beautiful woman like you,
and having guys constantly
vying for your attention,
trying to impress you?
I know you want to be with
a successful man,
like... like Agent X,
and on top of that,
you know every day I still want you,
just as bad and just as passionately,
as the first day I laid eyes on you
And you don't seem...
...to want me... to...
to want me at all
That's not true, George
You're just...
You're obsessed with your job and...
[*sigh*]
getting a mission...
...it's...
...it's like I'm not
important to you anymore
Don't you get it?
It's because you're important to me
that I want a mission,
that I want to keep my head buried
in the work
I want you to be proud of me,
I want you to...
I want you to be proud
walking around with me
Baby,
I am proud of you
You mean it?
Yes, of course
I love you
I love you too
How very touching
Agent M?
Don't look so shocked
And it's Miranda
(- But why?)
Uh, money. Why else?
Come.
I've brought the coordinates
to the White House,
I'll deal with these lovebirds later
Always thought she was kind of a bitch
Yeah
She'd big monstrous feet too
I hope the Brits
are having better luck than us
Hum hum. Sir?
What is it Watson?
We're gonna need a damn good
plan to get past his own guards
Yes Watson. I'm on it
I have an idea
Are you fidgeting?
Trust me
I know that sound
What is that?
It's my nail file
Oh...
Shit!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah
Did you mean what you said?
Of course I did
We still gonna stop them now
I know
All right, I'm going to disarm the bomb,
you create a diversion
Okay
Okay?
Rachel?
Did I thank you?
No
I will
I could go this way, disarm the bomb,
you go that way
Okay?
Oh shit
Hi
Just...
...looking for the...
...ladies room
I tell you Gamush:
donkey fucking will become a sport
Babali, it will never become a sport
Who, in the right mind,
would pay good money
to see such a thing,
when you know that horses are
so much more entertaining?
Horses aren't entertaining
[*door opens*]
[*chains and arabic jewelry sounds*]
This's never gonna work
Have some faith, man
Some faith?
How I became an agent
and run around in lady's underpants.
Shhh!
What do we have here?
I have two new concubines for His Highness
Ah... Very very nice
I'm thinking I like this one
Uh
Strong like horse
How dare you touch Hussein's property?
He would cut your hand off
for showing such disrespect
Now step aside and let us through.
Thousand pardons, thousand pardons.
What were you thinking?
What we're...
Oh oh, that was for me?
For you? What are you talking about?
You look like every other guard here
I'm a very handsome man
I have a nice physique
Hmm, maybe you are right. Okay.
(I thank you Sir.)
- Let's go back to our post
- Okay
Who's my little Jihad?
Who is my little Jihad?
Come on
A kiss to Papa
Come on, don't be shy
There you go
Oh, would you talk cutie thing(?)
Hello, what's this?
I have brought two new wives for you
Ah... Two wives for me
Jade you shouldn't have
Is this in honor
of my birthday next week?
[*gunshots*]
Go
Wait for me
What took you so long?
Gather the girls
and meet me out front.
Okay
Now Watson.
Where did he go?
Come
Let's see...
Ah... It is nice
[*Jafar laughs*]
Silly American fashion
[*noise of a public cheering up*]
[*Jafar laughs*]
[*Music from the 50's*]
[*Circus theme*]
[*Psycho's theme*]
I am mistress Stern
Well, hello to you sexy lady
Come to Jafar
Come on
[*strike of a whip*]
Move that out of my way
So...
You've been a bad boy, huh?
- You do not scare me
- Really?
- I am Jafar
- Really
[*sound of whip*]
How about now?
Oh... maybe a little
- Little?
- Little
Oh... Are you gonna do
what I tell you to do?
Yes
I hope so, or I have to punish you
Let's see what we got here
Sounds like fun for me
Come here
Put your face in there
- You will fuck me good?
- Yes
I hope so
*** will be
But don't you start
by eating my pussy, huh?
Show me what you can do
That's right, take Jaffar
come on.
[Music]
(You like that)
Come on take Jafar, that's right
Oh you like that, you like that
HOW TO DISASSEMBLE A NUCLEAR BOMB
[*Salsa music*]
What's going on in there?
You asked for distraction
I'd say they're pretty
fucking distracted
Yeah, I'll give you that
So, I found the bomb. I defused it
And I found a room full of Jeeps,
so we get that hell out of here
Let's go
What?
I left the bag here, I know I did.
George...
Perhaps you're looking for this?
Oh no...
Rachel, get down!
[*ouch*]
[*Jafar laughs*]
All right [*indistinct speech*]
(George!)
Rachel, give me that… the vest, please.
My mother kicks harder than that
Oh does she? How about...
...down here,
let's see what we have over here.
Hello, missy.
George!
I'm sorry, but I don't think it's such
a good time for fishing my friend
You're not my friend
Oh my God
I told you these vests were cool.
Are you okay?
I'm okay. You okay?
Yeah, I'm okay
God...
Ouch
You wouldn't shoot an unarmed
woman, won't you?
I would never do that
I only use my bare hands
so I can feel it
You bitch
[*tazer*]
[*electricity*]
George
It was the sexiest thing
I've ever seen
and scariest too
You okay?
- Yeah. You okay?
- Yeah
I can't wait
Yeah, me too
- I've time now.
- Me too.
Oh...
[*alarm*]
Oh no...
FIVE
FOUR
THREE
TWO
ONE
ZERO
IGNITION
- Oh!
- You idiot!
Oh now I'm an idiot
Miss I gotta have you now
Wait, I thought you just disarmed
that thing
I did. I took the plutonium out
It will still launch, it just won't
detonate on impact
Well it's big enough to do some
serious fucking damage
and it's aimed right
to the White House
God damn it
Oh God
I know
You can't call it back now,
it's too late
No but I can change the coordinates
[*drifting skid sound*]
Please tell me that's gonna land
in the middle of the ocean
Nope.
Better
What's going on?
[*explosion*]
***
This way
I said "more head", not "warhead"
Oh boy... Come on Jihad
Come on!
Freeze
Where am I gonna go?
Cuff him.
But he isn't going anyway, sir
Thank you Watson
End of the road for you Hussein
That's alright I got it in here, boys
Time to be left professionals
This guy is mine
This guy belongs to a mutt?
The bounty hunter
Who the hell are you?
I told you:
I'm Mutt, the bounty hunter
Hell no
[*gunshots*]
Oh
[*Tango music*]
[*applause*]
Beautifully done darling.
What's wrong?
You step on my foot
- Oh
- Ouch
Congratulations on becoming
an agent, Rachel
I always knew you had it in you
Sir, we thought you were dead
Oh, non sense
Oh, it was very scary. Really
Then, without warning,
a coconut hits him
in the head out of nowhere
He was unconscious for four days,
and when he came to,
he couldn't remember a thing
Aww...
I was so worried for him
A coconut, sir?
- Cheers
Oh and congratulations, agent Z
Thank you
Agent A...
Hey, no hard feelings
Okay
Let's get this party started!
[*yeah*]
Cheers!
You ready get out of here?
I thought you never asked
[*door closes*]
God!
Sweetie!
Not again!
[*Salsa music*]
Baby...
I love you
[*phone's ringing*]