=======================
Fix or feedback: please let me know
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
Come on April, don't make me beg
Saturday is going to be a big party in the city
I would like you to come
I don't waste my time with the boys. Your place is in the playground.
Why do you think she's so stuck up?
Maybe she likes girls.
Forget her guys. I have a good news.
In this afternoon there will be a new chick
Tell us about her Robert?
That's all I have on her. Miss Baker told me when I went to see her this morning
Yeah we have to break in the new chick
- Oh yeah!
- Okay
Not bad, uh?
Okay guys. Training stops. It's going good
Hmm you know the teacher may have been right,
But I think we got something we could shoot a whole lot better with
What are you thinking about?
- I know what he thinks about!
- Oh yeah...
I almost forgot, Rachel: I promised at the Dean
if you usher this new girl around the school
We can't go swinging with the boys
Did you know, the club is like that, they need a lot of money.
let's go
I don't mind
Everybody take advantage of me. I'm sick of this.
Everyday the guys go for April, and here comes this new girl Vicky.
Probably a spoiled brat.
- Hi, I'm Rachel, you must be Vicky?
- Yes, hi Rachel
I hope we can be friends
You never know how can happen let me
- Let me help you
- Ok thanks
There! She's fine!
Baby! Baby I need you!
All guys are idiots...
What happens with that girl? They can't make working their mind?
Okay everyone. You know that soon there will be a test
and that is why you should workout
and anyone with a special workout they should start in the weight room
Well I have an idea: why don't we all go on our workout?
The others probably went swimming
I'm interested in everything about her
Angela, she was the main force of the guys
but now the guys are paying more attention to Vicky
No, not like that
I'm so excited Steve. Last time I was also excited,
when I was a kid I went with my brother to climb the mountain
but this is different.
- Sorry Vicky, it's only me
- Don't be so stuck off Steve, let's keep going
- Okay
What's wrong April?
None of your business. You want to know,
since this little Vicky is here every guy is beating on her
Yes well with her at least I could probably get a good fuck
but with you we've been trying to get you in bed for two years
and no one's got lucky yet. Or am I wrong?
No you're wrong because I'm waiting for the right one that will marry me
You'll die a virgin.
no one's want to marry you or engage with you
until they get you in bed know how you are
She's so dumb.
So fine.
This Vicky is very interesting
Watch ou Steve!
Where did he go? Did he fall?
This is your fault!
Instead of paying attention to climbing
he's looking at your ass.
Let's not talk about this
Show me what happened
You are lucky it's not that bad
Did you check here? It hurts a little bit
Here?
A little bit more
- Maybe here?
- Yes, better
- Then... it may be... here.
- Yes
We got the permission to take Vicky at Rally Racing
The question is: which one of us?
Oh perhaps we should draw matches
that will be the fair way to do it
You are right
Okay guys have you got any matches?
Let's see
Let's see. I will take the head of some
I will stay the same, we'll go in line I will be
We'll go in line. I will be the last.
Whoever will get the match without head
get to take Vicky
Lucky bastard
Don't worry guys you will get later on
That what is very fine
okay
Hey, check the tire pressure also
Let's go baby
For Vicky, she sure knows a lot about cars
I hope her car will throw her
You are a fucking asshole April
Come on guys, we'll be late for volleyball match
you didn't tell me you can drive like that
I was a junior champion a couple of years ago
Ah, that's why it's so easy
that's why it's so easy
Can I give you a big hug?
- You don't want to hug me!
- What do you mean?
You know I've never did it on a race car before
It would be very weird to do it here
but I've nothing against it
(very funny...)
(yeah as you know him)
Hello girls
So which one of you girls wants to come
jet skiing? Maybe you Rachel?
I don't feel like it
Only three jets. I will stay here.
- Okay but no horse plan!
- Stupid!
What's up? Something wrong?
What did you say?
I've asked what is the problem?
With me? Nothing.
It's like you are in a different world
Oh. I doesn't think April likes Vicky.
They're almost the same because for
two years, didn't get none
That's enough of this!
Everyone is talking about little virgin April
and crazy sexy Vicky
What's her problem?
What's wrong with her?
I don't know. Maybe she's just...
Ah. The reason we came back here,
we ran into Maggie on the way back and
we thought we put together some hot sex action together
- It's a good idea
- yeah
- I think we're going to have some fun
- Yes
Look at this, men
- Ah, there are jetski
- Yeah, that's gonna be fun
Come on Pete, let's do a race
- Okay let's go
- Me too
Take one of the jet skis
Take one
You should pick this Mylar, Vicky
Don't (...) then we go this way. Take this Mylar
I would like to talk to you Steve
Now? About something concerning school?
No, what I want to talk about is different
I'm listening
- Not here, in the house
- Okay
Now you can tell me
This is so embarrassing, Steve
I know that you have been trying to get with me
and I've been shutting you out and everyone else
The only reason I did this is because
I never did it with anyone and I was scared
You're a virgin?
this is not important but I feel alone
Since Vicky has been here at the academy
everyone has been paying attention to her and I can't handle it
so I want you to fuck me
Are you kidding?
Does this convince you?
Wow, I can tell you're not joking
Come on, do something
If you want to
What happened?
Something hurts?
Yes, my... my ankle
You should go to see a doctor, it could be broken
What happened?
Vicky rolled over, someone sabotage her jet
That's probably April, because she hates Vicky
What do you have to say?
You're joking? You think I could do something like this?
You probably did this to be back in the spotlight
I would never do anything like this
Maybe she's telling the truth
Of course I'm telling the truth
well I have a different feeling
Maybe we'll go back out and you can try the other jet skis
Why not
- And Sue?
- Of course
- Rachel?
- Why not
Good. Then we can go into race
We'll go down there to that point and
turn around and come back
since you have the smaller boat, Rachel
you can have a 10-second head start
Here is the key
What's the matter Rachel? You're scared?
Maybe April did it
I wouldn't start it
you're the one who sabotaged it
Not true
If I remember at the start
you told Vicky to take the small boat
or do I remember wrong?
What do you say? For once, think.
You all are fucking assholes and I
hate this story and school anyway
How did you know, Eric?
I'll tell you at school
once Vicky gets back from the doctor
we'll have a big party
May I have your attention ladies and gentlemen
this afternoon we will cleared up that
accident what happened today and from
today Rachel Stern is suspended because
she took responsibility for what's
happened. And teachers got together and
everybody came up with the idea that we
go and shoot party
(Yeah)
And I suggest you use
your opportunity while the teaching
staff go in a city so starting Monday is
back to work
Now you can tell us how you knew Rachel did it
Well I didn't
it was just a gut feeling
When Steve and the girls left to go mountain climbing
I saw Rachel do something to Vicky's rope
and when I questioned her about it
she became defensive
if her little plan had worked,
April would have been expulsed from school
and Vicki may have been killed
Nice job Eric
Does your leg still hurt?
Not anymore
The main thing is that we cleared it up with April
I was going to say the same about Vicky because
because she made me understand
why sex is such an important thing
I am happy.
What but do you think people? Let's have a big party
Let's have a big party!