=======================
Fix or feedback: please let me know
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
So romantic,
those glittering lights,
fill me with pride,
my own, my beautiful, Riverside.
I wrote that
Yeah yeah, Riverside California
It's like so romantic
I hate this shit, you know that
Sometimes I think you have no poetry in your soul
No poetry? Try this:
We sit for hours in this old truck no more near
We had an agreement darling
The wedding is only in a few short weeks
and then, I promise,
that I will take this swelling cock of yours
and grease it it with my tongue
and so you can slide real easy
in my nice, warm, wet, hungry pussy
Do you have to make it any harder for me than it already is?
Don't do that anymore, please.
Poor dear
You need a nice handjob
Yours of course
Is that any better there?
What was that?
Do you need a hanky?
No, listen.
There's a clug
Do you feel that?
What is it?
He's taking my fucking aerial. 35 bucks
Motherfucker
Well, need a light, missy?
Certainly sir
Oh my god
Oh, officer Blount
as I live and breathe
What are you doing in this park?
Checking up on morals
Seems like all these kids come up here
and think they can break every code of decency
Come on, you can tell me
Like feeling each other's...
Anything else?
Sucking each other's... should I tell you?
I just can't believe the immorality of some people
Yeah you could say that
Yeah missy... Come on. That's it.
Take care of gentlemen. Thank you miss.
Damn. I'll make you pay, you vandals.
My camera?
Holy ***
It's cheap aerial, really
Really I guess from chump or dope lights
Well, you're the champ. You know.
He knows the best parking in town
Sounds like you've got a real head cold, sir
I can offer you a cough candy?
A football player? a big seller like you
A big fellow like you
I sure would like your autograph
What about a picture instead?
Picture, yeah? Picture
Ok. Ok, ready?
Ok, keep the aerial. Take my car.
Take my fiancee
What were you doing honey?
I was getting lonely
I hope it's true what they say
about absence making the heart grow fonder
Let me show if it is? Okay?
Naughty boy
How kind of a girl do you think I am?
Come on, let me just count the feel
- What is this?
- What?
This. This repulsive thing.
Good gravy, what is it he want?
I don't know, it sounds like he's in pain
*** paper now
Jesus Christ how is anyone expected to
be creative around here?
- I'm sorry
- Just don't care of him, he's always kind of bad time
I'm Nora, you must be Chelsea new photographer
- For today. I don't keep jobs too long
- Oh
I dropped it
Well this is fine since you're very handsome
it's fine here
I've got it
That's it
Lunch with the Shah: 2460 dollars
plus tips
Big story?
Expensive report, takes dollars, fame, ***
Chah's been dead ten years, love
I really don't think the cop departments gonna go for this one
I knew that, sure
I had lunch with the Shah's spirit
He contacted me from beyond the grave
He's giving me fashion tips what Ronald
Reagan should wear to his next big dinner
Seem to forget who you're working for, Sweetheart
This is the National Expire
not the Washington Post
Good point, Dick.
If you don't get a real story
soon, for all going to be unemployed
I mean your records are so bad
we can't even get a job at the LA Times
- Yeah
- Oh, hello Mr. President
- Hi Holly, how are you?
(Thay all prentend talking on the phone)
(...so not why is President lives...)
(...yes well well no I'm on fire...)
(...okay yeah all right...)
(...okay...)
Hey boss!
Hi
- Holly North?
- Uh-huh
Fixed
- Miss Taylor?
- Miss Taylor
President Reagan.
Pathetic
This your idea of news?
What I want is a real story
"Barry Manilow was a man in his former life"
Not bad... But unbelievable!
Come on, people!
We need the big one here, the real story
Like...
Nah. No, not Bigfoot's boss
and we've been following that Big Putts angle
for four years now
it just doesn't go anywhere. It's nowhere.
I have to fire your ass you worm
You think I've been wrong about Big Putts
all along, huh, Mr. Journalism 101
you wouldn't know a story if it goosed you
Here. Look at that.
Wow, that's incredible
It's Big Putts
I've had it authenticated
I want all three of you to get up there to Hicksville
and get the real story
otherwise you can all go looking for
another job
Understand?
- Yes
- All of you
- Does he say tonight?
- Yes
Miss Mews come to my office please
***, take a chair
No thank you, I already have one like this
Quick. I like that from my employees
So very few had it.
Look, I want you to take down everything I say.
- Alright?
- Okay
- Ready?
- Ready
"Pants"
I caught you
Thank you
How long have you worked for us, Miss Mews?
- This is my first day
- Mm-hmm
Run into any arbitrary sex scenes yet?
I don't know. What's "arbitrary"?
"Arbitrary" means that we do it with no dramatic
reason except that the public expects it
Got it?
Got what?
Don't they teach you anything at journalism school these days?
Um. I think it's all coming back to me
Listen girls... I...
Yeah, I think we've already been this way
You brought the compas, right Chelsea?
Oops. I think I dropped it
"Oops"? What do you mean "oops"?
Sorry
Great, forgot the ***
Lucky for you guys I think of everything
Bright, you brought a CB radio
No, something better. This.
One more time
I hate that damn tune
that's all you city slickers ever play
What is going on here?
Don't you know anything else?
I like Old MacDonald had a farm
I like the part where...
goes...
And in that farm he had some piggies
Can you squeal like a piggy, Sir?
I'll tell you all.
We got some friends waiting for us,
so we should gonna be on the way, so...
That's so bad.
You girls,
tie him!
What?
(...They're enforcing cold air down to the
(...northwest we'll be seeing some clouds in
(...the morning and showers in the afternoon
(...except in the mountains and canyons
(...which will be clear after around two
(...p.m. we'll see the clouds burn off so
(...you can go to the beach and your body right
(...down the hill tender tight spot...)
Oh good,
give me that beer, I've been waiting for all day
(...Hollywood yesterday...)
(...according to police and several...)
(...eyewitnesses the women have dropped her...)
(...groceries and walked in front of the...)
(...vessels right...)
Come on!
Ok, I know this isn't Mac, but
I won't *** a *** horse in the mouth
and you must be a horse
...Moo-moo here and moo-moo there
here a moo, there a moo
everywhere a moo moo
Old MacDonald had a farm
E-I-E-I-O
And on his farm he has some
Some what?
Come on, smarty pants city slickers,
what is the end?
- ... Old Mac Donald...?
- Dealers
And on his farm he had some dealers
E-I-E-I-O
With a...
What a hell sound does a dealer make?
Dealer... uh...
What would you say... Squeak-squeaker!
Squeak-squeaker
That's a damn mouse!
A faggot mouse!
You're a damn faggot boy?
Of course not!
That's too bad because I'm gonna have to kill you
Wait a minute you no need to be hasty big boy
(- He's gay)
- Hey you're kind of cute
Sweet, for real?
He's so gay, he's fast, he's a queer
- Anything best
- Check up on
You girls,
start working on.
Come on.
Move it
(...Something...) He's tied.
Use all your womanly charms:
Cocksucking, fucking, all of them
No
Nooo!
Don't do that so good
See:
They're not working on us
Let's clear the four dollar bill
I do dropped the notice anyway
Looks like you ***, boy
If you don't sing the Donalds farm
with the damn ***
I just got no use for you
Hey, I think he's hurt
Get me out of these ropes
so I'll finish this fucker off
Really
It's a clap of an arrow
No, it's a car aerial antenna
with feather state to it
(*Roar*)
Shit!
*** Big Putts
Well, say you say Beulah honey?
I said are you sure this how they have interviews
in the big city?
I mean it's sure hard to talk
I know it must be hard
But you can ease up for a little while
Now,
Tell me again how you saw Big Putts at the outhouse
Well, it's pretty disgusting
Oh no much like this
He'll have my ass in a sling
Boss what are you doing here?
Your job is what I'm doing. You might
think my days are over as a reporter, but
I could still kick your ass when it
comes to a story. This fine lady has just
given me an exclusive: she's actually
seen Big Putts in action
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah
Yeah, well, let's have this for a headline:
National expiry reporter target Big Putts
his anger brush with death
I nearly ate it this time he says
Go on. Hotshot.
Oh the old man crumpled his arrow found his
mark was a tragic end to a man they call
Big Mac the much-loved banjo player who
knew every verse of Old MacDonald for memory
I hate the second.
Where does Big Putts coming all of this?
It sounds like my old Mac but it can't be
he never knew every verse of Old MacDonald
I want you to take me to the scene of the crime
First, you will go for my clothes right back
There you do the...
- That hello interview?
- Yeah
Sort of.
I've come you know any closer
Wow, nice essay
*** dart is a a spanish fly
is thought to be the only genuine aphrodisiac
they tend to make even the most frigid women
sexually ravenous
Isn't that something?
oh I'm not frigid dear, I'm just a highly
Oh I'm not frigid dear, I'm just a highly
moral type of individual
Hey it's my nail polish in the basket?
Let me see
"Sweet seduction"? What kind of name is
that for a color
Oh don't get any ideas here
How about a toast to married life
Oh dear, I'm all wet at the moment
Here let me help you
You'll be wetter soon enough
Drink, drink, drink up
I... I... Wow
Darling what is wrong with you?
What are you doing?
***
Come here, come here
Is anybody home?
*** to fall for this routine
I hate porridge
So exhausted
Secret to life
is *** *** when to get there
Time to find pet: Meenie Miney and Mo
I'll start with Meenie
because you're kinda cute
And I will play with *** ***
Open the door, darling.
*** *** with me.
Eat me...
Yes...
I love your tongue
It's rude to talk with a survival knife in your mouth
I'm sorry
Whatever you may think of us
I do apologize
I said I hope you like *** Iraqi 69
It will take the last of my day, but
this is a special occasion
"Excusez-moi"
I knew I knew I know, don't say it
I don't seem as mature as I look
Everybody says it and it makes me sick
*** hard to get up
Are you kidding?
if I was dressed the way I wanted to,
a Don Johnson sort of style, you know lots
of *** and aqua I would never get the
moment of peace
What are you doing out here?
Such a long story...
When are we cooking I tell you about it
- Okay
- Go into my tent
- Good
- After you...
...blow me down he said,
and an arrow came out of a tree
and *** forward
How *** ?
My god...
Better get him to the authorities
Hope the killer had his *** made up properly
I mean I don't even know if it was perfect season anyway
Arg.... Hee-ya hee-ya oh
Not dead yet. He's still alive!
(...and in his farm he has ...)
Oh look at this!
- What?
- Arrow went right through his bottle
Saved his life
When he'll finds out his bottle's been punctured that will kill him for sure
What the fuck was that?
It was Big Putts, there is no doubt
...with quack quack here and a quack quack there...
Again, good.
So I knew I had to project to develop this tremendous roar
all that theater playing it was very worthwhile
I guess you could call me the original screaming...
But why did you shoot that man back there?
Need to ask?
He was singing Old MacDonald had a farm
I mean why not? What a rare mood I mean
or comes to the cavalry old chum
"Old MacDonald had a farm", this should be a hanging crime
But you took the law into your own hands
judge Wapner would be *** of that
Sometimes you have to rise above the lord to do the right thing
*** top of that
I think I know what your problem is
I'm sorry Missy but women are not my cup of tea
Who's talking about tea?
I'm talking about sex
Who are you?
I'm your fairy godmother
Oh good. Fuck me fairy godmother
Who is it dear?
It's just fairy godmother
Fuck me, fairy godmother
Hold *** this time, okay?
Oh...
They must be healthier in the ***
I'm really sorry it happened honey
Well, I suppose every girl has to lose
her virginity at some time
I'm just glad it was with you
Goodbye fairy godmother
And Thank you
Okay
God, I've got find out Chelsea
Boy I need a drink
So what else is new?
All this chasing around in the woods
I'm tired. I get too old for it
*** I wonder have we changed
And not like Vinnie
He's on the Big Putts trail right now
Just like a cub reporter
Yeah, but he's got what it takes
to be a good newspaper reporter
He's got energy, and maturity, and
a whole warped mind
There's something different about you
Well maybe it's because I don't have half my clothes on
Huh. No, no, that's huh
That's different. You have a glow
Is it huh...
Is that *** I've been fucked
until my ears *** ?
Sounds good though
I don't suppose you'd consider
something serious sex
I like men *** nice and straight ***
My *** reporter
On my tits
Who do that?
Hate to admit it but I did
Maybe the roar is the Big Putts'
Better go out of here
This is yours, that's mine
- Hic!
- Excuse me?
No, this is his name
Mac Hic is the musical pervert
And you know what I want from you, boy
You won't get it
Now then what if I *** your girlfriend here?
What do you want from him?
He wants me to sing Old MacDonald and I won't do it
I truly ***, stand up yourself, Flambo
Get the *** away
And on his farm he had some cows
Hee-ya hee-ya oh.
With a moo-moo here, and a moo-moo there,
Here a moo, there a moo, everywhere a moo...
Big Putts...!
I hear sound that a Big Putts make
It was alive
I never forget a face
Hey journalism has to rise above the facts
and fill ***