=======================
Fix or feedback: please let me know
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
Is it real?
But of course. And quite priceless.
My Dear you are looking at the famed...
..."Pink Pussy"
Why do they call it the Pink Pussy?
Look at it. It's beautiful.
Look deep into it. Can you see?
Can you see the light that it captures?
Yes, I see, the color pink,
deep in the diamond.
It looks almost like... a cat
A pink pussy.
Exactly
But Andre, I don't understand how you can
afford such a remarkable stone...
...on a police chief's salary
I don't. It's my wife's.
She has money in her family, you know.
Fortunately for me,
she has interests to keep her away from home a lot
And tonight my dear, the pink pussy...
...is all yours.
No. Tonight, the pink pussy is YOURS.
You sure know how to have fun when your wife's away?
She has her diversions, I have mine.
You're not gonna have them too much longer
if we don't clean up this sticky mess
I'll get a damp cloth
You know, you should feel honored to wear my...
wife's most prized jewel.
How interested most people,
but you know, you're different.
I judge you to be...
...gone.
And this is where I *** it.
On ze fruit salad?
No, you idiot?
She was leaning against the counter...
...eating a banana.
A banana?
This could be a very important clue.
How could the banana have to do with anything?
If there's a great deal to do with things,
Chief Superintendent ***
It tells me that she was a woman of wants
A woman of... passion
A woman who has not shared love...
...in the wrong *** ***
What are you talking about you fool?
We had just shared love moments before she vanished.
That is why it's so essential that
my wife not find out about this ***
That is frightening a concept as it may...
...sound, ***
My fate is in your hands
I am honored that you have chosen me
for this ***, superintendant ***.
us it is defective with Queen can
It is a re...
defective a fruit cream can...
...obviously, if you see, it is defective.
You're the only defective thing around here
Let me tell you something:
My wife is a very wealthy woman,
if she finds out I've been unfaithful to her,
She'll have my balls in a vice grip
If that happens to me,
I'll turn your head so far around...
...you'll have to walk backwards to see where you're going
Do not will it, Chief Inspector.
I will not rest...
...until I get my hands on this "Pink Puss...
...until I get my hands on this "Pink Pussy" of yours
You have my ***
Good news KY: I'm on the case.
Oh congratulations Inspector,
it will be a real feather in your cap if you solve it
And it's so *** if you do not
'afraid I don't follow, sir.
You don't need to.
Just drive me to the nearest fruit farm
b you stay
But why a fruit farm, Inspector?
You stay hunched I have KY,
the woman that I am after....
has a fetish for fresh fruit...
...and she'll be needing to lay low for a while
Yes then who is this log character she'll be laying?
She won't be laying anyone. She'll be hiding out
I see
Brilliant deduction inspector.
May I suggest the convent we past about ten...
...miles down the road.
The nuns there provide fresh fruits for the entire town
But of course!
What better way to elude the authorities.
- Drive on KY!
- Yes sir!
Why are we stopping here, sir?
The convent is still a quarter of mile down the road
And lose the element of surprise?
I would rather sneak in the back.
This kitty *** has proven herself to be a coming one
by outsmarting the superintendent
Yes, but Sir this convent it's called "The
Sisters Of The Holy Moly", you've got a
big one but you won't be putting it ***
It's made up of women who were at one time
or another wronged by men so...
...the women are separated from the men
It's something designated areas
You won't be getting in there they'll catch
you and they'll throw you out
My dear KY,
this kitty is not the only coming cat in the game
When I sneak, I become invisible.
You wait 20 minutes,
then come in with your handcuffs at ***
Yes sir.
Shall we synchronize watches?
Yes, of course.
How else will you know when I know it is 20 minutes?
Yes sir.
I have 10 minutes before one.
Uh... Actually sir,
it's 5 minutes after 11.
You sure?
Yes sir, see: when Mickey's big hand is
on the 11 and his little hand is on the 1
that means it's 5 minutes after 11, sir.
But the longer hand is on the fat
Longer is bigger
No sir, short one is the big one.
But, uh...
Fat is big, long is just... is just long, sir.
I think is you are wrong about this KY,
but we will have it your way
When Mickey's hand moves to the 5, you come in
Yes sir.
Are you sure you'll be alright in there, sir?
How could I not be around a bunch of silly bit nuns?
Any other woman may pose ***
You know KY,
the superintendant is in great trouble because of women
If you ever see me in trouble with another woman,
you pull me out KY. You undestand?
Understood sir.
Thank goodness
Farewell. I am off.
Sir are you alright?
I told you to fix that door.
Sorry sir but they were closed.
Unlock the door KY
Good luck sir.
Thank you
I appreciate you showing this to me, sister Teresa.
I have a great *** to learn
before I become a full fledged sister.
Do you think you'll be with us that long?
Only the Great Lord can give you that answer
That she can.
She is all-knowing and all-loving.
Tell me more about your order...
Well, we believe in the power of women.
To be self-sufficient and self-loving
In our religion,
we believe that love is the key to all happiness
and that the more a woman shares her love
the happier she will become.
We will show you all you need to know,
but you must have the strong wish to be enlightened
I hunger for it.
Enlighten me, Sister Teresa
First, you must take a vow of silence
Would you like to take that vow with me right now?
Shhhh
Sir!
Success KY!
I have located the thief.
Outstanding, sir!
But what about the Pink Pussy?
She wasn't wearing it.
she may have a habit huh
She may have hidden in her ***
She must have a stash somewhere in the convent
We can only got in there to search for it.
We can't... but I can wearing this
What is that sir?
It's a habit! Help me into it.
Oh KY, we are in a hurry!
Quickly
Have you *** ?
Lift up ***.
Never wore one of these before
***
only one day with a sisterhood and
you've already lost your habit
We let you join us Sister Kay to help rid you
of a few of your bad habits.
We had no idea your clothes would be one of them
Do you have anything to say for yourself?
Yes Mother Superior it was the most fun I ever had
Sister Teresa,
you will be in charge while I'm gone this weekend.
I'll be leaving in a few hours.
You came to us, Sister Kay,
you don't leave the clothes on your back,
and the possessions that are now in this box...
We know very little of you,
except that you are running for something
But that's what it has sent you to us,
we couldn't be happier.
Hey? Why so nosy, sister?
Wait a minute...
You aren't a sister, you're like a man to me
Oooh, what's this we have here?
***
*** get away!
KY, You idiot! What are you doing?
it's *** trouble ***
A moment, it's my pal,
can I skip me from your lips *** moment
Come on!
KY, You idiot! What are you doing?
I worried, ***, sir.
*** how do you know what I tell you?
Get out, idiot!
Back to work.
Follow me Madam.
What are you looking at?
Come on, come back with me, and do it again
Madam, I am an policeman work is first
Oh, just come back *** make a swirl
Heyp heyp heyp
There are things to do and I must do them
because no one can do them but me.
Success!
Voila. My little jewel.
Teresa, Kay, did you see them?
To get the vow of silence should ***
two men running around.
Men? Who are they?
Please!
Well let's find them quickly before
Mother Superior chases them out the property
Yeah,
You are lurking for this?
I have your robe and I have your Pink Pussy
I must warn you: anything you say
will be written down and used against
you in trial.
I should have *** her up
with anything she threw against me
could be used against her.
You're not one of my sisters
In fact you're not a sister at all.
How could you tell?
I think the bulge in your robe was a
dead giveaway, ***
Oh...
Perhaps the naked girl that ran through here had
something to do with that?
I assure you I didn't lay a hand on
that soft, cheaply, lovely body
Yes, but the bulge in your robe indicates
you were thinking of doing that.
The bulge was *** imperfections in
the material of ***
It doesn't seem to be an imperfection
Hell, you do that so well, Madam.
Call me Mother.
I do think that I would be comfortable
calling you ***
They even call me "Superior",
'cause honey, I am.
Come over here
But of course
Ouch, my back...
I seem to be stuck
Are you ok?
I'm fine, Madam
I see him!
Here he is! Don't let him get away!
***
What you girls want?
Oh hell...
***
*** women around there
I *** Superior
I want you now to suck my cock until
it shots in the mouth.
- N'est-ce pas?
- Hmm
Well, now that you got that out of the way,
who are you and what do you want?
They have what I came for:
The Pink Pussy.
Mean you came here to fuck me?
No,
this Pink Pussy.
You see, this woman named Kitty
that you have brought in
is the chief superinterdent's mistress
She stole these from him.
You don't say
Yes I do indeed say, Madam.
And if the Chief superintendent ***
*** to be caught or find out,
she would have his balls in a vise
Hmm. Would she ***?
Yes she would.
But luckily for me,
she will never know
the jewel will be returned
before she even finds out
You see, she spends a lot of time
away from the ***
that a woman's function.
She will be home this evening.
You see, when the cat's away,
the mouse like the Chief superintendent
will play.
Hmm, I can imagine.
Yes. But luckily for me,
she will never know.
So, if you will be so kind,
you've to excuse me, Madam.
Au revoir!
I think perhaps I can get your telephone number
I just call the convent?
KY? What are you doing?
Uh, I'm *** the witnesses, sir
You looks to me like you are making love
I never thought I would see the day when
KY and sex would go together.
Say "au revoir" to your friends.
We have what we came for,
the jewelry is most important
What about the girl couple?
I am sure Chief superintendent ***
will fulfill not to press charges on this matter
I let the girls go.
Au revoir. Uh.
Merci beaucoup.
Drive on, KY, right home.
KY?
Hey! Inspector!
I've becoming concerned. I expected
superintendent *** be pleased with
the return of the jewel but I kept
hearing him horrible screams of pain
what was happening in there? it seems the
It seems the Chief superintendent's wife arrived
just before we did.
It also seems the Cief superintendent's balls
were put into a vice grip.
Oh, that would explain the screaming
No, the screams you heard were me.
I see, yeah but why are you wearing
your clothes backward, inspector?
It is not my clothes that I worn backward,
it is my head.
Damn, fits it to you.
It seems that Chief superintendent's wife and
Mother Superior are the same person.
I may have recovered the stone,
but in the meantime,
I have let the cat out of the bag.
Or in this case, should I say the kitty.
Yes well,
your cases do seem to take an unusual turn, inspector.
Yes, yes. They do, don't they?
*** the door like this.
I don't know. ***
You idiot, I cannot open the door.
- Ouch!
- Sorry inspector.
I don't suppose you'll be needing your seatbelt, sir.
Yeah, I don't think I will be needing it either
We have more cases to solve, KY.
Yes, sir
We must trap on, KY.
Here we go!