=======================
Credits: (?)
Found somewhere on the web by
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
How many times do I have to say it,
I like to see you suck it.
I also told you
I can not do it with light.
Come on, you can do it.
Where are you going?
It's 2 a.m.
I'm leaving, baby.
You know...?
For years, every time we do it
It seems that it is your first time.
I hate you.
Every time I take you, it seems
I ask you a favor.
That good!
Just because you want to do it
with the light on.
That is the only reason in your life.
- Yes.
- Where will you go?
You go with your secretary Tyna.
- Yes.
- And what will you say to your son?
No no. Wait.
I'll tell him that his father's shit leaves us
for some kind of teenage slut.
Tomorrow put it on the phone and if you want,
Let him come with me and Tyna.
I have to do it. I have to do it.
See you never.
He will be away for a long time.
Mom will come back It's just a fight.
It happened before.
Forget it, it will not come back.
You must think if you want to live with him.
Oh mom, I want to stay with you.
No honey, it's already decided.
And I do not want to talk about that.
He will call you later.
Could work.
And of what?
You can not leave school.
You are not going to leave.
I will get a job.
Not exactly first.
Do not tell me.
3. 4
You are not in decadence.
Thank you, little sun.
- Hello?
Barbara.
What are you doing at this time?
Gyna, you will not believe me.
I do not believe it myself.
Chirs abandoned me.
- I do not believe you.
The son of a bitch left me
by Tyna, the secretary.
Are you looking for a job?
We had lunch?
Sure, it's fine.
Well, see you later.
It's time to wake up.
Gyna wants breakfast.
fifty
Hello darling, sit down.
Tell me.
You need a drink
Now tell me,
What the hell is wrong with Chris?
Go figure.
Even I can not believe it.
He abandoned his son
and me for a whore.
An opportunistic bitch.
Tell me about her.
I only know that she is a secretary.
1.70, 25 years.
As I said: "One moment you are up,
and to the short while down ".
Barbara, what you need
He is a new guy.
I'll find you a sexy young man.
No thanks. I have to think
much in my lost ego.
It is not necessary to
lose the feeling.
It is going to shrink you.
I insist I know a guy who
will please
I do not say it for me.
But it would be perfect for you.
How is the job search?
Are you kidding? If you have up
25, they do not even look at you.
Nobody wants to give me a job.
That is very bad.
Wait a minute.
Who was the one who helped me in crisis?
When I got divorced years ago
It came from the other side.
What was it called?
I was after you.
Jerry Morgan,
I had not thought of it.
And his office is nearby.
Could be.
I think I'll eat fish.
Now Barbara, tell me how is that
beautiful son of yours, Paul.
It must be really big now, right?
Stay still.
In what year was the Battle of Hastings?
Open your legs
and I tell you in what year.
- In what year was the Battle of Hastings?
- 1066
Wait.
In what year did Alexander invade Persia?
- 333 BC., And enough questions.
Oh Paul, you're so smart.
You know all the answers.
You deserve a reward.
Do they study history,
or sex education?
Porn is our hobby.
You were not going for a few copies.
You never told me it was so big!
Well, I'm leaving.
Wait, do not go.
Guess what. I will leave
try it a bit.
I let you eat it
if you promise to return it.
Promise it.
Well, but I will not give it back
as soon.
Paul, are you home?
Yes mom.
Dinner is almost ready.
How did it go?
I'm tired.
Honey, have you talked to your father?
Yes, we talk.
And good?
- You know I'll stay with you.
- Honey, I feel so happy.
You know mom. I was thinking...
I want to look for a job.
I already told you,
no way.
Your father is going to pay
the school.
- And besides, you know what?
- What?
- Today I found work.
- Are you kidding.
Of what? Where?
Well, do you remember Morgan?
He helped Gyna years ago.
Well, I went to see him today.
Your office is nearby.
And he found me a job.
I never thought he would help me.
Congratulations for your work.
Hi. I say Morgan.
It's me, did Charlie call you?
Are you going out tonight?
If he did.
And if I am.
Gyna, are you sure I should do it?
You could talk later,
This is very important.
Sure, Gyna, I'll leave you, I have
than write a letter.
Gyna, are you sure about this?
Barbara. Charlie walks
with other girls.
You are not going to church.
OK, I will go...
What's wrong Jerry ...
What's going on there?
Is Jerry raping you?
Leave me son of a bitch.
I do not want this, nor do I need it.
What are you doing?
Did you get your cock?
I want my money, I resign.
Jerry, I never thought about you.
After so many years.
Barbara, I do not want you to think
that...
I've always thought of you ...
Still being married.
Since I saw you...
Please, do not give up ...
Think about it.
Come tomorrow?
Promise me that you will think about it.
If you promise not to do it again.
Well, but this is why I will reduce you
The salary.
Oh my god, I'm very excited.
I thought he was raping her.
I'm so hot
Just play with my shell.
You know how I like it, do not you?
I know, I'm going to take off my pantyhose.
Is not it better?
Let me go down there so they can
give some of my attention.
Bring that nice sweet conchita
for here.
Sit over there, I'll see if
is mom
Hey Paul, look.
God, you're always so hot.
Paul, I did not know you were home.
Hi, Sherry.
- Hello, mrs. Scott.
- Honey, I'm sorry, I did not make dinner.
Your decrepit mom has a date.
- Do not worry.
- To a good time.
- Thank you.
What are you doing in that corner, baby?
Do I have bad breath or something?
I feel very comfortable here. Thank you.
Come on, come closer.
I thought you were swinger.
And I thought you were underfunded.
What did you say?
Nothing. Nothing important.
Gina told me that you just got divorced.
You must be ready to have
a little action, is not it, baby?
I had never been
given in that way.
You really turn on me honey.
Come on baby, cheer up.
It seems you do not like it.
What kind of party is this?
It is a great party.
Did Gyna never tell you?
No. Exchange of couples?
Orgy?
I think I'll go home.
Go home?
Trash.
You came with me,
and I will not let you go.
Maylene, baby.
I like to meet you.
Come here Charlie.
Come on, baby.
Enjoy the party.
I do not want to take part.
Fuck you, baby.
You have to wait for me.
By God, you could be my son!
Hey, you are very beautiful!
Please!
Let me see that you have
under the dress.
I just want to see a little.
Do not!
Why not? Just leave me
take a look.
Let's go.
Do you want me to ask you more
friendly?
Enough!
Let's go to another room.
You are very rigid.
Please.
Stop.
Fuck baby, I got tired
from this!
It was very good.
Great, baby.
They left me dry!
Well, I'm ready.
Let's go baby.
Do you want me to call you
next friday?
Save your time, Charlie.
Dear Paul. We lost our
heads last night
What happened was
terribly wrong.
We will talk tonight
When I get home.
With love. Your mother.
Barbara, can you answer the
phone please?
Ah, it's you Gynna.
I'm not in the mood to talk.
I'll call you later.
Charlie was an idiot.
And the party was terrible.
Everything is collapsing.
I'll call you later.
Are you okay honey?
What happens?
Nothing will make you feel better.
- Take the day off.
- But there's a lot to do.
I propose you something.
Let's take the day ...
We will go to lunch.
And maybe later you feel better.
Let's move on.
For the lady.
Thanks for this day Charlie.
You're adorable.
You already know me, I'm a good boy.
Let `s go inside.
We can not leave it that simple.
Maybe it will not happen again.
Not Jerry, not tonight.
You have been very sweet and the
I've had a good time
But ... What's wrong Jerry?
Better see you tomorrow, yes?
Now I have to go.
It's okay.
Paul, I arrived.
Yes mom. I'm here.
Hi Mom.
I have been waiting for you.
Paul, it's serious.
What happened was my fault.
I do not want you to feel guilty
of what I did to you
I thought we had done it together.
You were very adorable
Have my son in my arms again.
Like when you were little.
But it's wrong.
Look Mom. I do not think less
of none of us.
It happened.
And I have to tell you ...
I want it to happen again.
The Law has an ugly
word for this.
Nobody has to know.
Just you and me.
Paul, I'm talking about incest.
Shit, who could it be?
- I interrupt you?
- Not really.
I was just with my beautiful and young
male inside
And a young girl with the sweetest and most beautiful
vagina that you have tried.
But it's okay.
They are only orgasms.
But what happens?
Are not you still angry about
your date with Charlie?
No no.
I just want to talk to someone.
You always told me.
I told you. It's natural.
But what do you want to talk about?
I can not even see it.
I wonder what's wrong with me.
Just tell me who it is.
What's going on?
- Paul, Paul and I ...
- Paul?
Paul and you ...?
You say you took your son?
The worst of all is that I
I'm falling in love with Jerry.
Forget about Jerry.
Tell me about Paul.
When we touch
When his hands caress my body ...
I want to have it inside me.
Did he do it to you?
Your vagina ate you.
I did not let him, he just did it.
This is very exciting.
Did you suck it?
Did it end in your mouth?
Liters and liters of semen?
I'm finishing.
I can not believe it,
Gynna, I came to ask you for help ...
and all you do is have
orgasms throughout the room.
- What I am going to do?
- Do not worry.
What kind of advice is that?
And my best friend!
I'm sorry, Barbara.
I do not know what to tell you.
I never imagined anyone
fucking his own son.
I'd better see you later.
You're good?
Where are you going?
I do not know where.
See you later.
Imagine catching your own son.
Honey, what time will I eat?
In a few minutes.
No, Paul can see us.
Listen to this too,
maybe we will not open
What do you think if we travel?
- Travel?
- Yes, did not I tell you?
- I have to take care of something.
- No, you did not say it.
Why do not you come.
You bring your son.
You can join us
It sounds beautiful.
I can not, I'm very busy.
See you.
What happens?
You have not tried anything
What will happen to him?
You know how teenagers are.
Finally alone.
All this food and still
I'm hungry.
Come, I'll give you the dessert.
You must know, Barbra.
I was always in love with you.
I already noticed Jerry.
I hope you feel for me.
The same as I feel for you.
Do you want us to get married?
Jerry, you have made me very happy.
But please, do not pressure me.
I have to reorder my priorities.
What do you mean by that?
From now on, my life
it's my life.
I want to do things
my way.
And part of my way, is to conserve you
as my lover.
And what is the other part?