=======================
Credits: impaired963 (?)
Found somewhere on the web by
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
Clide, will I ever see you again?
Why sure honey.
Soon as this here bag is all filled up with money.
But for now...
I gotta go.  Thanks everybody.
You've just been robbed by Clide Barrow, OK?
Good day to y'all.
I want a divorce!
What the hell is this?
Uhm, I'm sorry sir.  It's not your day.
Oh, not any day.
There's not been more than $100 in this place since the crash.
Just come on over here, honey.
Right on behind here.
Now.  Not that I don't believe you or nothin', but...
How's about we take a looksee in there?  Huh?
God!
Damnit.  Told ya.
Hey, you don't need money anyway!
I'm just trying to break up the boredom in this shabby hotel.
We're 2 hard working girls.
Trying to earn a little extra green.
Maybe we can help you pass some time?
Why?  You think I need to pay for it?
You not man enough for the 2 of us?
We won't be paid for it.
Matter of fact, we won't even care that you are just one.
So, first thing...
...let's make sure we're not going to be disturbed.
Let's find out.
Let's see what you got.
That's pretty.
I'd say that's getting you $1/minute.  No overtime.
I gotta say.  That was a pretty nice...
...run on the bank.
But you know what?
If you want to make...
...more of this silly green stuff...
Theres just one thing you gotta do for me
What?
Next time this place is all full up.
You just let me know.  We gotta deal?
Uh huh?  We gotta deal?  We gotta deal.
In the meantime I guess.
That's all yours.
Now, I gotta fly.
I'm going to divide my heart like this dollar...
...between you.
I gotta hit the road.
Remember to tell 'em.  You just been stuck up by Clide Barrow, hisself.
Be sure to.
Damnit.
What in heavens is wrong with you now?
God!  Damnit.
Damn car!
Oh!  God!
Hey!
You trying to steal my momma's car?
I was just admiring it.  That's all.
You know.  Actually...
I'm thinking about getting me one of these myself.
You!  You don't have money for a car.
Maybe.
But I can buy you a coke.
Get on down here!
Who are you anyway?
Oh.
My name's .... Clide Barrow.
And I rob banks.
You do not!
What do you reckon this piece is for then?  Huh?
Wow!
See.
No!
Yeah baby.  You want to hold it?
I wanna hold it.
Touch it.
And shoot it!
You look mighty pretty with that
Thank you.
But hey!  You wanna be careful...
...when you get hold of a hot piece like this.
It might just go off on you.
So a....
What do you wanna do?
You wanna spend the rest of your life...
...serving the country boys?
Bringing them their hash?
Letting them try to get their mits all over you?
Is that what you want?
No!
You want something better right?
You wanna life where you can look at the stars and say...
...you belong to me.
I want to be a star.
Wow!
Between you and me...
...and this.  We can make that happen.
Hey!
Loaded!
I surrender baby!
Now.  How about I show you some of those stars?
Yeahhh!
Oh Clide!
Hey.  Your momma ain't gonna come down is she?
I don't care.
well if you don't care.
Your momma wanna keep you a virgin or what?
I know!
Let's have a look at this.
Oh my god.
Is that some Texas ass or what?
You never gonna meet a preacher man like that!  Hop on here.
Now let's have a look.
...at what Miss Bonnie's got.
Oh boy!
Yeah.  Park it up there baby!
Let the sunlight right in.  Oh yeah!
You sure do taste sweet.
And what have you got for me?
I've got a whole lot of lovin' for you.
Get me out of these clothes!
You know what my favorite fruit is?
What?
Peaches.
And I got myself a whole barrel load here, I reckon!
Damn!
OK, it's a stick up!
Yeah!
Hey.  That ain't my only weapon, you know.
Oh.  Look at this weapon.
I always keep this one loaded.
Oh!  I don't wanna lose no buttons.
Take it all off!  I don't like clothes.
I gotta show you the kind of intensive investigation...
...that the Federal Bureau is doing these days.
They get into body searches, and all that nonsense.
You would not believe it.
Gotta long ways to go.
You just wait right there.
Hurry?  We ain't in now hurry.
Hey, that's how you like it, huh?
Oh yeah!
Oh yeah, Miss Parker!
Just don't let your momma see that!
OK.
I'll be drivin'.  You come ridin'.
Uh uh!
If I'm comin'...I'm drivin'.
That's how it is with Miss Bonnie Parker, see?
Get in!
OK Beauty.
Wait for me now.  Let's go!
Marshall Frank Cameron sir?
Of course!  Bring his ass on in here.
Frank my boy, you are in...Good to see you.
Have a seat.  Have a seat.
So what is it you wanted to see me about?
Well, I hear you been doing a little freelancing on the side.
I figured you might be interested in a job that really pays.
I'm listening.
Here's the deal.  A few of my branches are getting robbed.
Times being as hard as they are,  i just can't afford it.
It's bad for business.
No I agree.
I can surely see you are suffering, sir.
Heres  my problem right here.
Goes by the name Clide Barrow, ex-con.
Goddamn small town!  But I did have to lay off the security staff.
He's making me regret that decision.
OK, and you want me to take him down, I get it.
It's gonna be like looking for a needle in a haystack.
NOT EXACTLY YOU SEE.
I CAN OFFER YOU $1000 UP FRONT.
Then another $10,000 when it's all over.
Man!
Do we have a deal?  Deal.
That's what I like to hear, Frank, by boy.
Always sharp as a tack.
I knew we could come to terms.
Excuse me sir.
Yes Janie.  Would you please be so kind as to send in tonight's entertainment?
Thank you very much.
Scotch?
Don't mind if I do.
Help yourself partner.
Ladies, come on in.
I'd like you to meet my boy, Frank Hamer.
Go say hello.
Hey you're gonna like it.
A little celebration is in order.
Would you help me with my sidearm?
Be careful.
You are so fucking good!
If feels so good sliding in there!
Howdy.  How are you folks doing today?
OK.
What can I do you for?
Just fill her on up.
Hey!  I've seen you.
No you ain't.
Yeah...The papers.  You're the bank robber!
We don't want no trouble, OK?
Fill her on up and me and my gal will be on our way.
Trouble?  Hell, I want in!
I'll even give you guys free gasoline if I can join your gang.
Hey Clide!  He could drive get-away for us.
You can drive boy?
Can I drive?  I can drive.  Mechanic.
Handle a steel.  I can do it all.
What other surprises you got?
I have lots of favorites.
You'd be surprised what people are willing to do for free gasoline.
You know, they say by the end of summer gasoline should be about 12 cents.
12 cents!
Ain't nobody ever paid no 12 cents for gasoline!
We get pretty much everything for fee, don't we?
Now then, what's your name?
CW. CW!  Pleasure to meet you.  Indeed.
And this here is...
Miss Bonnie Parker!
Oh wow!
The sexiest bank robber...
...in the West!
I have to agree with that.  Ain't it true.
Sorry.  I'm a little bit...
Clide you gotta stop doing that.
Nice to meet you.  My pleasure.
Don't take too long.  You know I hate waiting.
Oh Honey.
We won't be long.
Business can't take that long.
Anyway.
Behave.
Hey.
Wanna come see what I got?
Yeah.
I'm feeling mighty in the mood.
Come on boy.
You'll like this bit of business.
Woo Hooo!
Who's your friend?
This is Clide I'd like to introduce you to.
My name is Clide Barrow.
Pleased to meet you.
I do declare this place open for business.
You guys get started here.  I'll get my boots off.
You guys are spoiling me today.
He's so funny.
It's so lonely by ourselves.
Ain't that a shame.
Thank you kindly.
We got business to tend to.
Business ... for sure.
What about you?
Serving the first course!
You know what?
I'm going to show you an old trick.
Oh no!  Is that going to work?
Oh yeah, Texas Momma!  Let's see you get up on there.
It's what we call the Texas soda fountain.
You ride it.  I ride it.
Keep riding it 'til your throwed off.
CW!
Did I say, I was going to make you a star?
You sure did, Clide.
Now Darling, you got your pistol, we got a bunch of cash...
Why don't we have a party in here?
Sugar plum he just sang the right note.
Let's do it!
Detective Hamer please.
I think I know where that sexy bank robber is you're looking for.
If you're interested.
I want to taste that cock after it's been inside your pussy, OK?
Yeah.  Let me taste that cock.
Now that is country loving!
What's going on in here?
Let me have that cock in my mouth.
That is a party right there!
Ooohh yes!  Give me that dick!
I'm sure glad you got me to work today.
You know, I was going to have the day off.
You want to put those fingers deep inside my pussy?
Bonnie.  Hey Bonnie.  You going to be the star of the show?
Keep fucking me just like that.
Give me that big cum load!
Squirt it all over me.
You greedy girl!
I'm going to get you a cocktail.