=======================
Credits: impaired963 (?)
Found somewhere on the web by
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
He come on.  What's for dinner?
Who's hungry?  I'm hungry.
Couple sandwiches.
Yeah, CW's got a brand new special.
He and his passengers were 2 highway patrolmen...
...and a blind stenographer.  How's that?
That's great.  That's great.
Look at what we got here.
Don't even move a muscle.
Interrupting your little picnic, huh?
Say Marshall!
I ain't never seen shooting like that, Clide.
Yeah.
Good shot!
What do we got here?  Huh?
We ain't going nowhere.
Get his cuffs!
You ain't getting away with this!
You gonna pay for this!
What's going on here?
What you gonna do?  Huh?
Find out exactly what you're doing here.
This is Missouri.  What are you doing here?
I know.
You heard about the reward on the Barrow gang, right?
You heard about the reward.  You think it's OK?
You think you can come down here...
...pick yourself a mighty fine reward.  I can tell you, it ain't gonna happen.
Shoot him.  Shoot him.
You ain't gonna get away with it.
You know where you are?
It's Missouri.  You ain't got no laws around here.
We got the pretty girls.
They got the guns.  We got the guns.
We got the cars and we got a mind...
...to show you...
...that we ain't takin' it no more.
Don't do it.
Before I blow your brains into the next county, I want you to tell me something.
I want you to tell all us something.
Why you after us?
There's all them poor people out there you should be protecting.
Ain't enough people in Texas for you to look after...
...you got to come all the way across how many state lines?
Looking for us?
So what are we gonna do with him?
I got an idea.
What do you think Bonnie?
Well, I think we should take a few pictures of him...
...send them to the papers.  Show 'em how friendly we all are.
Woo hoo!  Sounds like an idea to me.
I got your camera right here.
There you go.
We're gonna get friendly.
His hair. His hat. His big gun.
Come on you gonna be a star!
Yoo hoo!  OK.
I got ya'.  Smile everybody.
Now can we kill him?
Now come on.  Look.
We're being all nice and friendly now.
OK?  So that's the Barrow gang.  That's how we are.
I say, we came out in this beautiful sunshine...
...with our beautiful gals for a picnic.
And a party.
We had a picnic, so...
Let's have a party!  Woo hoo!  Let's do it!
Get me out of these handcuffs!
Ha ha!  That's it.  That's the long arm of the law.
Come here.
These are mighty tight.
Are you gonna make me come?
Are you gonna make me come?  Come all over here.
That's a great ride, baby!  Oh yeah!
Throw him in the lake?  You up for that?  Sure.
I swear to god, you ain't seen the last of me!
Hey!  It's a turkey shoot!
Show what you got!
Do you hear something?  I can't hear nothing.
You ain't seen the last of me, Bonnie and Clide!
Can we help you with something?  Ummm.
Perhaps do you wanna get it on?
Uhh....the dress.
Oh.  Do you wanna see what it looks like?
I dunno.  Do you  think it's me?
Oh, I think it's totally you.
OK.
Oh my god!  Is that a gun?
Well, yeah.
Is it loaded?
It might be.  Do you wanna touch it?
Yeah.
What's your name?
My name...is Bonnie Parker.
What do you do?
Um...nothing.
Why do you have a gun?
I just, you know, like to keep myself safe.
Can I hold it?  There's like all sorts of perverts around.
You can touch it all you like.
You guys are like....You're so hot!
I wanna see more!  You get that off!
You gonna help me.  I'll help you.
You like that.  Keep teasing me like that.
Hey y'all!  Wow.
Now.
I guess you heard about the Barrow gang?
Well that's us!
Aw, come on now.  Don't be scared.  Gather round.
We ain't gonna steal from you.  You ain't got nothin'.
Look.  I'm Clide Barrow.
And this here... I'm Miss Bonnie Parker.
You heard of the Barrow Gang, right.  Yeah.
You know what you don't here of?
You don't hear from them laws.
About we here...shootin' our guns...
...and runnin' away in our automobiles...
...to give you money.
This is for you guys.  Come on.  Take it.
Take it.  That's right.
Cause we got a mountain of it!
That's all for y'all.
You ain't gonna be poor no more.  Not with the Barrow Gang.
And see what else we got for ya.
Miss Bonnie picked these out herself, right?
Look at that.
Now listen y'all, listen one second, OK?
We ain't here to do you no violence.
We're here to be part of you.
Because without you we ain't got no country.
When the laws come round that mountaintop...
...and they're surely gonna come.  You know that.
When the laws come round and they say...
You seen Bonnie and Clide?  You seen Bonnie and Clide?
You can tell 'em you seen us.  You can tell 'em you seen Bonnie and Clide.
You tell those suckers you seen us...
...and what we done here.
Just tell 'em we headed in that direction to Oklahoma, OK?
That all right?  You do that for us?
We want you to have a party, OK?
We want you to have a fine party.  Dress that goat.  But first...
I just want you to hear some words from my beautiful Bonnie.
Who wrote something for you guys.
You're gonna remember a long time.
Now I got it here for you honey, somewhere.
Now this here...
Was written by Miss Bonnie Parker, herself...
For you.  This here is a ballad...
...of Bonnie and Clide.
Listen up.
We each of us have a good alibi...
...for being down here in the joint.  But few of them are really justified.
...if you get right down to the point.
Now Bonnie and Clide are the Barrow Gang...
I'm sure how you all read how the rob and steal...
And those who squeal are found dying and dead.
There's lots of untruths to these write ups...
They're not so ruthless as that.
Their nature is raw.  They hate all law...
...stool pigeons and rats.
They call them cold-blooded killers...
...they say they're heartless and mean.
But I say with pride, I once knew Cllide...
...when he was honest, upright, and clean.
From heartbreak some people have suffered.
From weariness some people have died.
But all in all, our troubles are small...
...till we get like Bonnie and Clide.
If a policeman is killed in Dallas...
...and they have no clue or guide...
If they can't find a fiend, just wipe the slate clean...
...and hang it on Bonnie and Clide.
If they try to act like citizens, and rent a nice flat...
About the third night, they're invited to fight..
...by a sub guns, "Rat Tat Tat".
They don't think they're tough or desperate.
They know the law always wins.
They've been shot at before, they do not ignore...
That death is the wages of sin.
Some day they'll go down together...
And they'll bury them side by side.
To few it'll be grief, to the law a relief.
But it's death for Bonnie and Clide!
Now y'all go have a party!  Yeah!
Hey, you poor people.
Miss Bonnie is giving her verses?
Would you like to fuck my ass again?  Well fuck me then.
Would you like to fuck me?
I've got my ass wide open for you.
Alright gentlemen, listen up.
These Thompson guns are capable of firing 180 rounds per minute.
OK.
Shred a man to pieces.  Know what I'm saying.
Knock him clean down.
However, we're not going to use force to take down Bonnie and Clide.
We're gonna use stealth.
Who the hell are they?
Gentlemen, I call them Honeytraps.
Couple of sleazy broads gonna bring down Clide Barrow?
Gentlemen I assure you they can do more than fuck.
How much do they charge an hour?
More than you sugar.  Wanna see why?
Well, hello.
How you doing sweet thing?
I'm good how are you?
What ya' doing?
Just walking.
Uh huh.  Where to?
Well that all just depends.
On what?
Well where are you going?
Well here, me and my lady are just about deciding.
Thinkin' about finding some honeysuckle down in that wood.
Well their in bloom this time of year so you'll have some.
Absolutely.
Come and join the show.
I'll be you director.
It's a romance.  Yeah.  Now.
I've got to make me like one of them Hollywood directors.
Ain't never seen a film like that at the gold mine.
You're so not shy!
We really aren't around here.
Let's get these off.
Take that honeysuckle!
Let me give you a hand.
Thank you!
Oh.  Such a gentleman.
Oh, she definitely ain't got no concealed weapons in there!
I don't think so, but I might be hiding something else.
You know what?  Let's get these dresses.
Have a seat.
It's like a picnic.
You taste just like honey
And you're suckling, huh?
Yee ha!
That's ridin'!
You like that girlie!  Uh huh!
Do you like that?  See how much!
Put some honeysuckle right on that!
Who wants to come have a ride on good old Clide?
Who's first?
Miss Parker, I surely declare.
She's always first on the buggie.
Shall we take a looksee at that?
What a pretty place!
Lookee what I got.
Anybody want these?  Anybody want these?
Ain't that a mighty shame?
I can't go home without my knickers!
You surely can't.
How 'bout I give you a river view?  A river view?
If I slip y'all coming down with me.
My knickers are all ready down there.
If this isn't a girl's dream?
You wanna go?  You jealous?
Yes.
You come be my sunshine.
You look so good!
All right Clide, get her.
There you go.  Big Ben baby.
Nice to be at a little stop in the country!
That was delicious!
Hey, a little bit more honey for you baby!
What's going to be round the next corner?
Look, I gots me an idea OK?
What we gonna do...
...gonna get ourselves a nice little house.
On the other side of the state line, right?  Yeah.
And then, all the robbin' we doin'...
...we do it the other side of the state line.
The laws ain't never gonna catch us, right?
And you're gonna have you're own little garden...your place.
And we goin' a be safe.
Yeah.
Cause look, you know, we ain't doing this just for us.
We ain't doin' it just for the money.
Not about the gettin' anything.
It's about the getting away from everything.
Bein' free.
Let's go be free then.
Let's get away.  Let's go.
Come on!
I'm driving!
Oh no!  Oh yeah!
Can I be of assistance?
Yeah, uh, sir.
You think you can help me and my friend out?
Oh surely.  What's the matter?
I don't know.  Some engine trouble.
We also ran into this tree.
Oh my. Well...
Oh yeah, you surely got problems with your axle.
Yeah, look....
I ain't got much in the way of tools back there.
But you know what?
I got me a pile of dollar bills.
Why don't I go see what I can figure out.
OK.  Anything helps.
And that is the story of Bonnie and Clide.