Private Teacher
Sub DivxStation
M u s t a f a S a l e m
Starring
This is the promised land!
Los Angeles - California
City Solitude of milk and honey!
Millions of people have made their home here
Airport workers, movie stars, butchers,
priests, pimps, musicians ...
Is the original home
Mc 'Donald
Chinese Theater,
Space Observatory,
Albert Street,
Santa Monica Pier,
The Beverly Hills Hotel,
Teatro La Tosca of foreign films
Marina Del Rey
highway
Hot dog restaurant,
Angelus Temple,
Chinatown,
Union Station,
The Coliseum
Coca Cola Company,
Park,
Venesiai channels,
in Hollywood, if Hollywood
where everything is true and everything in general!
the beginning of everything.
Hollywood Boulevard, street of dreams and stars.
in a film city, which is now
given to people on the street ...
sex, drugs and rock'n'roll.
It is the combination of day and Saturday night.
can be straight, gay, lesbian ...
all one, all together
the revolution of America, where everyone is equal, free
independent of religion, sex, skin or
sexual condition.
the past away and the beautiful
Hollywood has opened the way
now you can go anywhere and if you want,
sex
all sex shops ofrcen maximum satisfaction.
and in the mountains north of Los Angeles
in the San Fernando Valley.
There are many communities Families
most Americans.
And here is the "normal" family.
"You've been a very very bad boy!
-Bips?
-If you've been, here you go!
"Shit!
"Here you've been a bad rabbit!
"Aha, you like, but do not say
"Oh, I love it!
"Arise!
"I'm a fucking guy!
"Ah, but you are the best?
"It was Tina, after being so stupid.
You can not have good ball
"But I'm the best ...
- What are you saying rat?
"The cheese, which I never ever smelled, bitch.
-? Of where you got this rodent?
Unl-of unhealthy environment.
"From the mousetrap?
-S í, only one problem, still alive.
"Oh yes, and I live to touch my pussy.
"Maybe capture,
and I'm going to eat.
"I'm going to eat, you need me.
"Oh, you enjoy your carrot.
-Debbie, Tina we stop playing
and back to reality.
"But you are wrong, that's weird.
"Down, boy!
"That happens, he lowered the ears.
"Lame.
"Lick my wet sex ... mmm
"It's so ... reality?
"This is a fantasy.
"Well, now you're hotter.
Hot guy? Ah, I understand,
hot guy, hot dick.
"Oho, adelantej.
"Oooo, stop it.
-A fun.
"Look at that ass ... do not touch,
lemme see.
"A hot ass?
"I want to touch it.
"I like to touch,
Quiros go in the hole?
"Jimmy, what do you est á s doing?
"I'm reading Aunt Diane.
"Jimmy opened the door.
"Please, t í Diane.
"That is happening there?
"No!
"I am calm!
-Reading!
"It's not excuse to close the door.
"Open the door!
"Well ... ya?
"I care about you, Jimmy.
- Why?
"I am your aunt and I have a right to worry.
"It's okay.
Exactly, you do not do anything
"All the time in your room.
"I only want to be alone.
"There's something suspicious,
do not try cheating.
"No!
"No, I'm not so sure ... No
were reading, I see no books.
"I save.
"Oh, back in an hour.
So let's keep talking.
"I have a surprise for you.
- 'I have a surprise for you'.
"Come rabbit, hop, hop ...
round the corner
"Let's fuck this rabbit!
"Yes!
"This very hard.
"Oh, let me suck.
"That good rabbit ...
Want to take out your ears?
"Ooo, so I like a big cock ... mmmm
"From when we share?
"The rabbit is not talking.
"This is your cock.
"You like?
"Uh put their fingers
in the coo. "Of course.
- What are you doing to me? Rabbit, take a look.
-? Know how it works Rabbit
"Of course.
"Open your mouth as wide as possible
and stick your tongue deep.
She does it very well!
"See, do show me now.
"Now the rabbit knows how to get
in the hole?
"Yes, the rabbit you know.
"Mmmm, my clitoris has grown.
"I love to catch with both
while
"I have only one cock.
"Are you sure? Give what you have.
"Just look at this hermoza coo, wet ... get out of here!
"If this wet.
"True, very wet.
"Put it there.
"He put the rabbit in the hole?
"Oh great!
"This is so funny ...
I love this game!
"I want my coo?
-Aja.
"You look very well from here í.
"It's great!
"You can not always get what you want.
"Oooh yeah ... look at this co!
-What are you doing out of it?
"You have a pretty coo narrow.
-Aja
"You're going to end?
just on my ass
-Mmm, I do not know, but anyway
I put my face next.
"If ya, right!
"I corrode.
"Jimmy, come?
"Jimmy, come to dinner
"Jimmy, you've been acting weird
these last weeks at home
"It is true that only
I am your aunt and not your mother
"But vivmos here, pay bills,
food, I have responsability
And your behavior has become very rare.
"Again it lol.
"No Jimmy, you're not the same,
you in your room for hours like a monk.
"Every morning you wake up late and sleepy
going to school, your teacher told me that you fall asleep.
"To get to school.
"Well, I would like to know you do in your
room, to spend many hours
"That happens, you will not say anything?
"I'm eating.
"Then why do not you tell me your problem?
-Masturbation.
-Masturbation?
"We can stop talking about that please?
"Of course.
Jimmy this is serious.
"Really? "Yes, I think you do not know,
happens to your alrrededor
"I do not understand the meaning of life.
"To act like a child normal.
"I only want more time for reading.
"No, not reading, something tells me you do not read books
that your reading is very quiet
Is abnormally quiet
Tell me what you're doing?
"Nothing.
Do not tell me anything!
"We have the same conversations every day,
if not fix the problem, I will take
serious action!
"I'm listening to?
"If Aunt Diane.
"Do not go for a walk,
Sport do not necessary
not going to the movies,
girls are not interested in you
not see the television!
The worst thing is that we have conversations,
we had before.
Spend time in your room,
you just do not feel you are a bit strange?
If yes, what is your reading Playboy magazine?
"No!
"So, what is?
"Nothing.
"Nothing? Young man, your nothing
á be converted into something!
"And when you can ask
professional advice.
"I'm going to my room ...
Thanks for dinner Aunt Diane.
"Why do not you see a movie with me?
"No thanks.
-? Some sweets for dessert?
"No!
"Damn, are no longer!
"Aha, there they are.
"Look at this ...
...? How about this?
"As this water?
"Great.
"See that fun foam, but not much?
"It's wonderful.
"I had fun with that rabbit ...
... Oh yeah. -If it was.
"You know what we do, have fun with
football player now.
"I love it when I'm wet!
"You want to fuck you?
"Okay as I do, you like?
"This delightful.
"I'm going to get the water ...
"You're so beautiful ... and delicate.
"You're going wrong? ...
I like what I taste them!
"Besame ... please.
"I'm all wet ...
"Oh yes, we'll play a while.
"Oh you wet ...
-That feels good.
"This good
"Wait, look now
"Now we are behind,
Now will the football player.
"But with the number 69?
"Attack!
Today's program Millonarios
will not be transmitted.
Instead we tranmit
a report from the White House
and the sexual revolution in America -
- Updated.
Today more and more people throughout
Fuck America.
One in ten families has a v í deo player,
The sexual content is now available to everyone.
From the elderly to young people, everybody
can see and teach about sexual pleasure
even in the living room.
All Americans
may have - Fun!
You can buy a sex magazine, just around the corner
But here everything is in 3D technology, which is
definitely good and healthy for you.
Of course, you can watch violence
broadcasting in other TV stations
but just look at this example of the new technology í a.
On this occasion will place the head
"As close"
and if you get close to the TV
Dare a presentation of how it works.
"Very well ...
up her skirt.
-So?
"Near the TV.
"I'll help.
So, yeah.
"Come nearer,
I see you have a co pink.
"That was good.
"Hey, could you fuck me from ahii?
"I think being í a á m á s f cil
if I go.
"Let me see you tomorrow, I will talk about
cyber scams
"Adieu.
-Jimmy, est á s awake?
"No, I'm asleep.
"Good evening.
"Nothing! ... Shit.
"It's time to get up Jimmy.
"Do not close the door.
"Sorry.
"Nothing.
"For me awake
so early on Saturday mornings.
I have no classes.
"Oh yes you will have.
- What do you mean?
"The school comes to you.
"My?
You look as if you were an emotional standstill.
As if you were in another world.
And I will not allow sick.
So I hired a private teacher.
She will be here and help you with
your problems and school problems.
Is a qualified profecional
and has many good recommendations.
"I do not need anyone t í Diana,
I'm fine!
"Yes, you talk a lot but
do nothing! always acting weird
"I just want to be alone.
All the time? I can not cheating!
"Good morning, you should be ...
"His teacher.
"Jimmy, come meet the
teacher, who will help.
"This is Ms. Foxword.
"Hi Jimmy.
"Please, go to the living room.
- What a beautiful house has!
"Thanks, we love the neighborhood
quiet, good neighbors.
"I said something funny, Jimmy?
"It reminded me of a joke.
"Well, at least you have not lost memory.
-Jimmy sure that your aunt
I said, why am I here.
-Diana, as I said
I have to work alone with him.
"Yes, I understand, I have a reunion in Palm Springs
So you can spend all weekend together
and address the problems of Jimmy.
"I have no problems!
"Jimmy, I think I will evaluate it
I have several degrees in psychology and í a
I have extensive experience in psychotherapy
If your t í to see the problem
I'm here to help.
"But I'm fine
I just want my privacy.
-Hmm, seems m á s grave that only your privacy.
- What you say?
"Exactly what you est á happening.
"Diana, I think the problem Jimmy
is not as severe
give me a few days and I am sure that
we can solve the problem of Jimmy.
"You're the boss.
"No, you're the boss, I'm a psychologist.
It is still very dependent on you.
Everything that happens in
environment, I will tell.
Thanks.
-? I can go to my room now?
"It's always like that!
"Yes, Jimmy, you go.
Then we talked.
"Adieu.
"I bring my bags, I will soon.
Have a good weekend Jimmy.
"Yes, of course
"This hard work will be Diana
Think so.
- What is the NIO est á doing boy?
No, his personality, but do not worry
I'm sure you'll find a way.
-Conf í or Foxword Miss you.
"Really? -Si.
"You just have to go and let your reunin
we are alone
Thanks. But est á s safe?
"Yes, conf í í a in m!
"Really, Thanks.
"I'm leaving, goodbye.
-Adis Diana, Have a nice day.
"Good luck.
"Wow.
"Wow, what?
í d-have been as busy.
You know what, I really thought
men are so passive.
You know, everyone thinks, we are ready,
to persecute us, and we conquer ...
I remember last week
We met on the beach ...
you know, that this lord, mysterious,
wearing a coat ...
í pod I do not believe, and when he dropped his pants,
and teaches that thing ... Yuck!
And his cock was just your thumb ...
he would say we're going to fuck all night ...
"I tom just two minutes ...
"All last only two minutes
I think that is an understatement.
I think these games are ours,
because otherwise we would not enjoy sex.
a real man should be
male and really take anything.
"You have to find it?
I do not know ... the rabbit has been.
"Ah, the rabbit ...
- How could í forget?
"But he is a fool, with
bunny suit, I can pick ...
"Hey, we, us girls bad
we have a reputation, and a hot coo!
"Therefore I do not like when you put the mask á m
to m á eye mask, what do you look like?
"You know
What do I need? their cocks.
you can have them, enjoy and go.
Masters-Duty í m á s something
We must do something more original.
But since I do not want á m s.
They say: Oh baby, I'll take all night
I'll lick your coo, well done.
this and that and when they get here í,
just fast!
"Come on, do something!
-Is coming, John?
"Yes, I think that will come with a friend
Jack or something.
"Then let's get ready!
"Of course, should be
here at any time.
"This time, we'll do something special
I have an idea, let's go.
"I think, you are not home.
"Do not worry, they're always here.
"Are you sure?
-How many times do I have to say,
sure they are, relax.
"I'm dying to fuck.
Oh, no, no, these girls are a little different I say,
you have to play with them to gain their coop.
"Sorry for being late
"Who cares.
"And we'll play today?
-Coop.
-Coop?
"Yes, a chicken coop, and your chicken.
"I have an idea, but prefer to be a p í á bird carpenter?
"That's silly Jack.
"Immediately the ground.
"You, too, Jack.
"Let's go!
"Now they are cows! Vamos!
Come on, cows!
"I'd rather have them roosters.
Somehow the climb.
"John, this is pretty stupid.
No you said you would do anything to fuck?
"Ok, ok, fine ... moo.
"Hey, let's ride
"Mmm, this is fun.
"Come, come!
"What do you think are Lipizzan or Arab?
"It's early to tell
"Come on.
"You are a Lipizzaner.
"I'll give my child?
"Sure, once you are ready.
"I'll say when, you know!
"Yes, of course.
"You like?
"Hmm.
Unbutton-shirt
... To see you.
"You know, I can ride a horse all night!
-Si.
"I will show,
if you hold so long
"You think you can?
"It seems so.
"This exactly how I want ...
... To start fucking.
I know you like.
-? Yes?
"Jimmy, you have to leave,
to talk
"Not now!
"I've come so far
so I would not worry about you.
"Well.
"Come, come to the living room,
and talked
-Ok.
"Sit down, Jimmy.
"Thanks, but this is my home.
"If it is, but do you want?
"My tai asked
come here ...
"Yeah, so is therefore going to talk
I know you lie, and that
not answer the questions.
Hidden something to your aunt.
And well, you're not mentally ill.
You got a secret
And in all likelihood
your aunt is not aware of this mystery,
but you can share it with me
"It is no secret.
- Did you like your aunt, Jimmy?
"Of course, it's perfect.
"What school are you going?
-Central College
"You have a problem?
-No.
"Well, no secrets and no problems.
That's right. I can go to my room now?
"Yes, of course.
"And now they are robots!
-Quiro to move slowly
"We will show
how.
"So, from a pocoi ... of Revelation.
"Oh, well!
"Slow, slower,
must play the game
"I like your cock.
"A robotic love?
"Oh, of course.
"How is your robot?
"I think you need to learn
to work slower.
"Do you work more slowly!
"Slower! if you do not follow
rules of the game, you will be deleted!
"You understand?
-Si.
- On your knees! have to show ...
do not touch me!
"And now receive
surprise!
-Daj da Vidima tvojega Kurc.
-Are you ready for grinding him up?
"Very good ... ooh love me, do not waste time!
"Look at this beautiful pink coo for you
lick it, put your tongue deep ...
-Quiros cum in my
face, my tongue in my mouth?
"I need some
"Or if, as I run ...
-You scamper anywhere,
that has been a good boy.
"I will run, on your tits.
"Where you want.
"Baby, you're going to run ...
-Are you ready?
"Oh mojaste me whole.
"Jimmy, I have to talk to you.
"Just a minute ...
"The door was open.
Jimmy, you have a problem?
"Ne, I jam the zipper.
"Well, I can help.
"No!
"That may be a problem.
"No, no!
"So we have no problems?
"No!
"Finally we have a common language.
-O is a lie
"Therefore, when you have a
emotional or physical problem,
then it should go well at school
-Shakespeare?
-Shakespeare, one of the
best British playwrights.
Their work can help your mind.
"This is outdated.
-Lee.
-Speaking of speech, please, too,
as I have given lectures:
smoothly flowing language
"No, no, Jimmy, you can not understand
if you put more feelings.
Speaking of speech, please, too,
as I have given lectures:
smoothly flowing language
if you spoke with him in all languages
since many of those who play,
also is
they say the lines.
Nor hands relaxed,
if not, but rather light at work:
that in the middle of the storm
as mentioned, creates the passions
must have and maintain a moderation,
which gives sensitivity.
Oh, the depths of the soul
painful to hear,
how life is unfair
passion in all things ...
Read more.
"Confidence. The honor
"I do not know why, but
maintains its reasons:
customize the words, word, gesture
special care not to distort the natural:
Since everything is exaggerated,
And away from the purpose of theater ...
... Which shows the features, ...
... Their time and how it is done. ...
... Oh, and I have seen players play
or listen, as others were doing, ...
... Had no voice, no distinction,
pagan, pagan or even human,
therefore in the streets,
who perished, as if it were the
Mother Nature working for the people,
shown, however, so disgusting.
"Waiting, show
overcome.
"Oh, absolutely correct.
And those who play with you
do not let them talk more, ...
... Well, prep á rate.
"I'm ready.
"Just relax.
"Mmm, this is fantastic.
-You enjoy it, right? -Si.
"He wants to lick you,
your eggs? -Si.
"So you were shy
"Fuck me gently and slowly. -Ok.
"We have plenty of time.
Here is my co-
"I'll give you a massage.
"Ohh, with those strong hands, no problem.
á jate rel-Slo ...
"Believe me, I am relaxed.
"You're a little tense here.
"You á fant hands up here.
"Ok, turn around.
"As you feel it?
-Super.
Hey, did not see you on television?
"Perhaps, in my show
tv.
"I knew, I had seen
your face before.
"Hm, I'll make a repeat
A little cream.
Please Diana, my work is just massage.
"Every muscles need a massage.
that you should know.
"Hm, may have reason.
"I look like, sexy?
-Aja.
"I think, any method
different for you.
"Well, let's see.
"Ooh, I Guasta Jimmy.
"Yes? "Yes, I love it.
"Oh, oh, ... no, do not stop!
So do not stop.
Your tongue is fast.
If so, squeeze my tits.
"Ooh, take me!
"Yes, Press it, bite you ...
"Bite? "Yes, biting gently.
"You make me feel so good.
-See how they react?
"They are hard.
"Oh, yes, you do it right.
"That soft, how good it feels ...
"Oh, fuck me!
"Turn around
"I like to fuck?
"Oh baby, want to, I run.
"I'm going .... I would run me!
"Gimme, gimme!
"Yes, yes, I'll run your ass!
? Y t think that this is not a massage?
"I am free!
"You know, one day, you will not be alone.
Each morning, he opened his eyes
I was afraid of the world, in which I live.
It was not the way I wanted it to be;
Better to have the world as your
have it in your room.
But that does not satisfy me,
I prefer to deal with other people.
And I have to look at these people and help them.
It's pretty simple. You'll see.
"I do not want that. I want to be with you!
We'll be together!
"No Jimmy, I'm your
Private teacher,
uan professor now.
After not need me anymore.
"Diana, do not worry about Jimmy is fine.
"Really, it seems that you have made a miracle.
-Um, maybe.
- Is it really safe á going to be okay?
"You can see it and call me in a few days.
And your salary?
"The agency sends you the bill.
"Yes, thanks, I really wish you well.
-Aunt Diana!
"Yes, Jimmy?
"That you have for dinner?
"We can go out to dinner.
"Oh, well, Se?oritas Foxword, will join us?
"Sorry Jimmy, I'll be busy this weekend,
I need to feed the cat. "
-Ok.
"Oh, Jimmy, do not forget Shakespeare.
"I will never forget.
Beds and adultery ...
And every time I stir action
pollutes the heart
and not act against the mother,
free in heaven
and a thorn in your heart,
convened by the skeletal injury
Now hello!
appears close to the morning,
and pale and weak.
Bye, bye, bye,
and remember me!
"What was that?
"I do not understand í as ...
mm, or maybe you.
"Hey kid, what do you est á s doing?
"My name is Jimmy, I live ...
- What? Come here í.
? What est á s doing?
"My name is Jimmy, I live in front.
"If so what?
"I know you do things,
I have seen things with my telescope.
-Have you seen?
"Yes, exciting animals, really sexy.
-Oh yeah.
"Well, it's very nice, huh?
-S í, it is very nice.
So we've been watching?
-Si.
-Quiros fun?
"That's what pensabal.
"I like to play in the dark?
-Dark?
"Now, we'll show you.
Oh well ...
I told you so,
this is too!
Go!
Moron ...
"I like fast, that's good.
"Jimmy had ever fucked
"Oh this is really good.
Fuck me ...
... Fucks like a rabbit.
"Oh baby.
"You're going to run ... oh yeah.
So Jimmy!
- Is it safe á s í this here?
"I saw through the window!
A few hours ago, when I saw the TV.
"He never stays out too late.
"Diana, you have problems with it?
"Yes, but I thought it í room to fixed.
I mean, never left his room.
"And do not return home.
"Who lives here í?
"Two flight attendants, who seem to be
quite normal.
"I do not seem to be at home.
"The door is open á, come on, let's take a look.
"Look at this, asleep.
-Jimmy, Jimmy wake
"Look, Diane, his hard cock.
"Oh, can not be.
"We have to put in place
if you wake up will be very embarrassed
"No, I will not touch it.
"But it is for their sake.
"But it is my nephew.
-Um, he is older, does not affect you.
-Cbrelo, take a pillow ... do something.
"Well, something I do, because you are a coward.
-? Coward?
"This too hard, I moisten
a little, and you can save more
-March, you know what you're doing?
"Yes, of course, since I do this often!
"Go back to sleep, Jimmy.
"I'm sucking cock, boy.
"Oh, it can be.
"I like to sit on.
-Marcha no, is my nephew.
"It is m í o! And it's a nice guy.
Jimmy, do not do this.
"It's so delicious Aunt Diana!
"Oh yes, I know.
"Fuck me like if you did not do another cosai.
"As it all his cock in me
I'm so wet
"As soon I saw that cock
hard I wanted to fuck.
"Diana, you can also enjoy
your dick, want to try
"Let's aunt Diana, I have always wanted.
-? Really?
"Oh, Diana, try
Total Well, everything is in familiai.
And so, when the sun goes down,
slowly in the west
say goodbye to Los Angeles,
land of milk and honey
orange sun
full of smog
land of opportunity, where anything can happen
And usually happens!
24 hours a day!
Sub DivxStation
M u s t a f a S a l e m