I've really enjoyed this time together
guys but Amy nice meeting you
Linda I gotta go hi Marge
let's go great I want you to focus more
and I'd like to but it's getting dark
and there's this TV commercial that
comes on its time every night and
there's a handsome guy on the shade
commercial and I got us it's a month
I'm sorry absolutely Greg thanks a lot
[Music]
he's my dream I love look at that body
gosh I'd love to be in that commercial
it would be great instead of shaving him
she'd be fucking him I could just
imagine my Chi
oh I know what you're gonna say
I've been using world lights for years I
love it but this this is a new world
blade almost looks like the old Phil of
the old one please
like the old one but let me prove it to
you right now it's not like you're one
mm yes
I love for my man he is world blades not
only don't want to kiss my cheek but I
want to sit on his face
[Music]
you