you've women and your diamonds I almost
got killed for that and for what for you
to have pretty shiny rock you idiot
this is not just a diamond it's no
ordinary stone it is one of five the
mystical gems need it for this what is
that once the remaining stones are in
place the box will unlock its powers and
I will know the secrets to the universe
whoever has control of this box will
have world domination how do you expect
to find these stones
Boris Boris always underestimated me so
you know location of stones not all of
them yet but my flowers are on the case
one of the stones has been locked in an
Austrian Museum safe for over 50 years
rose and violet or in Vienna now well
you seem to have everything figured out
they're leaving so soon what else could
you possibly want for me I think you
know exactly what I want
I thought you said you hated me
ha
Oh
Wow
yes we've crossed the border into
Austria perfect go tell the captain set
sail for Miami
money here's your gun
try not shooting yourself again I can't
thank you enough sir
don't thank me I had my way he's sitting
right over there at that desk well you'd
be safe where we would all be safe
listen I just I just want to get back on
the job sir
listen you know I know you want to put
me out a big case but I think I need a
beat I think I need to kind of you know
oil myself up and in a squad car
something with mites oh well good first
let the LEDs well first I want to meet a
new partner the department 8 apart I've
always wanted a partner hey nice to meet
you no it isn't Murphy here was
transferred from Boston the department
there thought Florida would be a good
place for him now you two let's get to
work Spring Breakers are going to be
here soon
it's not gonna go away so what you doing
Boston traffic
detective Oh homicide no no no narcotics
Special Victims Unit right right you
guys got a lot of world champions man
I'm really really jealous
yeah hop on in buddy yeah so display
graduating from the Academy with top
honors
I still got put on a desk duty for like
three years I mean how am I supposed to
know that the gun was loaded I mean that
how packer was fast I couldn't even get
it out of my holster vest you know you
should think about coming home for
dinner Sam makes a great pot roast Sam
who is Sam ah yes I didn't know that gay
marriage is legal in Florida no but
you're not gay
oh no a woman married you yeah al this
is what kind of game coffee black please
okay um you know non-fat whip yep you
got the carob chips we do because I came
to chop up Y sores oh yeah we got those
okay and you don't suck dick there you
go what Thanks Oh No your money's no
good here officer free coffee entreat oh
yeah
because her amazing
you read that is just tired isn't that
kind you'd be safe out there Upson well
thank you
that was a night guard I'll take care of
him I'll meet you at the rendezvous
point
Ivy yes we have an issue
give me the inter on the night guard
his name is Elias born and raised in
Vienna birthday is October 10th 1973 one
sibling brother Felix no children
mentioned he was divorced last week
perfect I'll use that one stop please
don't shoot Elias
I'm so sorry if I scared you who are you
and what are you doing here Felix sent
me your brother
you know my brother yes he said he just
got a divorce he thought you might want
to celebrate your newfound freedom
celebrate you know with a little company
this is a joke
no but if you're not interested I can
just go remember you can tell Felix
though that my fee is non-refundable I
wouldn't want my brother to waste his
money that's a good boy
Oh
ah
yeah
Oh
[Laughter]
ah
Oh
Wow
yeah
Oh
yes we have the stone excellent news
there's a private jet waiting to bring
you to Miami I'll see you here tomorrow
the hell are we doing here anyways
the third stone is in possession of
socialite London Radisson she's here in
Florida vacation with her boyfriend on a
private island just how do you plan to
get on to private island anyways still
underestimate any worse
Lily you're not stalking are you
no no no well
aren't you having fun man this was so
much fun man God tickets yeah thrilling
pulling people over get up my wife she
had a tarot card reading she said that
something exciting was gonna happen in
my life
damn it what Tara card
she's a clairvoyant more like psycho so
come over for dinner today nope nope
they have to be in the car with you for
eight hours I could be the drink for 10
you want to give me a lift in the
nearest bar sure yeah ya know what hey
is this excellent first day love your
moves want to learn more
pretty fuckin shitty if I do say so
myself really what do you do I work in
sales
the hottest ever seen
[Laughter]
Oh
so can I get my gift now your gift how
did I get your gift we just met shit is
your birthday you know my donation my
fee ah the money for the sex you're a
hooker you told me you worked in sales I
do I just sold you my asshole oh wait
did you think this was free oh my god
shit
Murphy what the fuck give me your
weapons
I guess it's back to writing a desk
I don't you writing yes desk no you got
to be fucking kidding me
really
welcome to Miami my little flowers
you guys remember Lily you have
something for me we do
two down three to go
which brings me to why you're here the
pink diamond is in possession of London
Radisson the ditzy hotel heiress yes
this will be like taking candy from a
baby
yeah roses right why do you need me uh
you see they're staying on a private
island and the only way on or off is by
boat so I need a woman with your special
talents
I need me to shoot them no I need you to
steal a boat and I thought you had a
boat no I have a yacht why can't you
just lie about because it's a paper
trail
don't explain everything to you guys and
there you'll find all the information
about the house and everyone who works
for London Radisson tomorrow no one
who's scheduled to be there except her
and her boyfriend you mean this guy yeah
yeah it claims to be some sort of
aspiring rapper or some shit
seems like her taste in men is as
questionable as our wardrobe yeah and in
your folder you will find the
coordinates to a shipwreck it's a few
miles off the coast it's the pirate ship
remains of the wicked storm there's a
chest and inside you'll find the Ruby
being our underwater expert I figure
shouldn't be a problem for you of course
not
right let's go do some reconnaissance
Lily leaving so soon
is that code for something of course it
is I see you are interested in a little
more than my boat hijacking skills
something like that
oh my god
[Laughter]
Oh
yes
oh fuck everything
next time use a pooper scooper or a fag
trying to keep the beach really clean no
respect is this fun this is this one
we're like out of their bikes and we're
exercising you're amazing beautiful hey
let's go
oh okay well I just won't tell the
captain that you like but what's key
here is coffee nice table is all right
two iced teas and two glazed doughnuts
until the way all right peach peach is
like it's like effervescent cool
it'll be 10:50 please I thought coffee
and treats are free for fire management
police yeah because I don't have a gun
listen you need to worry about getting
pants first then worry about the gun
okay these are aerodynamic skins okay go
I love it they can get our perps faster
oh it's gonna be ten there we go
yeah how no fifty cents Oh kids called
you know we'll call it you owe me 50
cents
hello good what can I get you I'll have
an iced tea oh okay rap tune in place
yep and fun coffee okay I'll get this
way okay I always have to be different
thank no no there there I'll get these
around me it's awesome little minute
did you hear him well these are all a no
charge
it's not fair to quote my mother life
it's not fair
see that yeah hey honey
no no no no I'm just sitting here having
tea with a partner maybe this isn't the
best place to talk yeah
you're joking right you really think
those guys are real cops you're right
oh all right so here's the file she said
everything should be in here so let's go
over it and make plan yep
all right so looks like miss London
Radisson is with her new fiance puff
Dickie weird ah on an island Oh perfect
that's right up my alley okay but how
are we gonna find the diamond well maybe
one of us can go undercover good idea
sounds like we have a plan
let's go still a diamond
I told you shoo psychic
my instincts tell me we should follow
those girls hello anybody instincts you
mean your penis no I mean my gut listen
man they R up to something but they're
up to something big
well hasn't your big thing gotten into
enough trouble I heard them talk about
rod of this chick right here
London Radisson yes huh
well if that's the case man we gotta
look to cap no no it should not why not
because this is a chance for us to
redeem ourselves and not be the
laughingstock of the department you may
be accustomed to it but I am NOT let's
go okay bring my doughnut
get away
take this you take this month but isn't
stealing no it's not stealing when the
cops are crazy
come on I'll make it anything without
that
this is gonna be way too easy
I have you sure to let me shoot them
when I had a chance I would have been
doing a public service agreed but that's
not the plan okay so what's the plan
violet will pretend to be a massage
therapist as they celebration good for
their recent engagement are you kidding
me
let me guess it's because I'm Asian
isn't it once violet distracts them you
and I will go in and steal the stone all
right fine
just you know this is super racist
oh damn shorty looking good I didn't
order no Chinese I'm actually the
massage therapist Radisson publicist
thought it might be a nice romantic
thing for you to holla and I mean
nothing you got me on my knees baby oh
snap I just came up with a ROM I got a
like that shit down you know saying look
at my bling yo you're my girl that this
believe what engagement gifts all right
oh yeah heavy lovely
that financier great shit right there
look at all good and shit yeah she's n
let's go
did you know I'm saying like what get to
like a happy ending is shit you linger
like let's get all happy how you do that
shit
it's massage show did tell a baby even
whatever you want
she's such a media coming
Oh
fuck
Miami police we need to come in we think
they're about to be robbed say who may
y'all even real cops man I ain't lettin
y'all in my crib you got that essential
documental shit we are two real cops no
but you're letting a hot asian cat
burglar first of all she was a massage
therapist a second of all I didn't go to
fucking cat man oh yeah where's your big
dancing pink diamond where'd she go the
Chinese lady Oh
what happened I don't know what fucking
cigarette out of gas how can you run out
of gas
it's all mine according to the GPS it
says the ship is right below us
I got this
did you get it
got it can you two imbeciles explain to
me why the Coast Guard had to tow you in
I was following a hunch a hunch since
the same hunch that told you was all
right to steal a waverunner ie
I didn't steal it I commandeered it for
official police business with tell him
you're on official police business
you were assigned to the boardwalk yeah
except for you two opted to go on a
lovely romantic sightseeing tour now I
have a beach that is riddled with glass
containers and dog poop captain I'm not
good get out of my office
Kenny showers
if we could just get those diamonds back
then I know we could redeem ourselves
I just figure out where there's bikini
bitches behind
heaven it always just ask my why why
would we ask her oh that's right
she's chlamydia Claro voyant
yeah that's what I meant
nice work
thank you guys so uh what are these
jewels for anyway you'll find out soon
enough
now if you excuse me I need to pack
where are you going now Egypt of course
I'm on my way
do you think he can help honey I will
try I can break out my crystal ball and
see if the spirits are willing to
communicate up is this an arranged
marriage or something oh you're so funny
Teddy said he was so funny he's talking
about you
Teddy yeah well she calls me that I
really don't like that I prefer to be
referred to by my given name Theodore
the Theodore Engelberg yeah there's so
much better there it is
okay let's give this a try it's been a
few days
okay I see something according to the
crystal would you seek is in a land far
away I see sand great pyramids a desert
daddy get me a pen and paper what's this
the coordinates of what you seek yeah
gosh anything for my love muffin but I'm
sorry baby I need to replenish yeah
we want me to make some coffee or
something
no my wife and I are going to make love
now Murphy like to ask you to leave
close the door behind you
[Laughter]
I've been eating healthy you have
religious cookie
hey buddies right single book but fuck
you're doing here do you think I was
gonna let my own partner come out here
all alone you're crazy
we're not partners sure we are the
captain said we're partners man you're
looking a little red man I think he knew
little sunblock here come on get the
fuck away from you that much shit damn
it
where you going oh is that yours
oh man oh I want one you got lights on
yours here get some sunblock Danny for
your shoulders I'll put it on here get
away from you that's a long shot
it says it's right around here according
to the GPS the door is this way
the first we have company you get the
stone I'll take care of this
nice day isn't it laughter I'll take
care of this you go get it
you want me to go down there yeah you go
okay
right right
you