you feminine your diamonds I almost got
killed for that and for what for you to
have pretty shiny rock you idiot this is
not just a diamond it's no ordinary
stone it is one of five the mystical
gems needed for this what is that
once the remaining stones are in place
the box will unlock its powers and I
will know the secrets to the universe
whoever has control of this box will
have world domination how do you expect
to find these stones Boris Boris always
underestimated me so you know location
of stones not all of them yet but my
flowers are on the case one of the
stones has been locked in an Austrian
Museum safe for over 50 years
rose and violator in Vienna now well you
seem to have everything figured out in
leaving so soon what else could you
possibly want for me I think you know
exactly what I want
I thought you said you hate
school
yes we've crossed the border into
Austria perfect so tell the captain set
sail for Miami mana
here's your gun try not shooting
yourself again I can't thank you enough
sir
don't thank me I had my way he's sitting
right over there at that stuff will
you'd be safe where we would all be safe
listen I just uh I just want to get back
on the job sir listen you know I know
you want to put me out a big case but I
think I need a beat I think I need to
kind of you know oil myself up and in a
squad car something with Mike what well
good first that's the LEDs well first I
want to meet your new partner in a
partner hate apart I've always wanted a
partner hey nice to meet you no it isn't
Murphy here was transferred from Boston
the department there thought Florida
would be a good place for me now you two
let's get to work
Spring Breakers are didn't be here soon
it's not gonna go where so what you
doing Boston traffic detective Oh
homicide no no no narcotics Special
Victims Unit
right right you guys got a lot of world
champions man I'm really really jealous
yeah hop on anybody yeah so despite
graduating from the Academy with top
honors
I still got put on a desk duty for like
three years I mean how was I supposed to
know that the gun was loaded I mean that
how packer was fast I couldn't even get
it out of my holster fast you know uh
you should think about coming home for
dinner Santa makes a great pot roast Sam
who is Sam ah yes um I didn't know that
gay marriage is legal Florida but buddy
oh no no Samantha's members are what
wait you're not gay
oh no a woman married you yeah okay else
is what kind of gay
coffee black please okay um hopefully no
mm-hmm not that what you got the carob
chips to do because I came to chop a
flyswatter
oh yeah we got those okay and you don't
suck dick there you go
but thanks over oh no your money's no
good here officer free coffee encourage
oh yeah
because her amazing you read that is
just tired
isn't that kind you'd be safe out there
up and we'll thank you
we're inside
that was my car I'll take care of him
I'll meet other on every point
Ivy yes we have an issue
give me the intel on the night guard
his name is Elias born and raised in
Vienna birthday is October since 1973
one sibling brother Felix no children
mentioned he was divorced last week
perfect I'll use that one stop please
don't shoot a life I'm so sorry if I
scared you who are you and what are you
doing here
Felix sent me your brother you know my
brother yes he said he just got a
divorce he thought you might want to
celebrate your newfound freedom
celebrate you know with a little company
this is a joke no but if you're not
interested I can just go remember you
can tell Felix so that my fee is
non-refundable I wouldn't want my
brother to waste his money
that's a good
you
okay
yeah
Oh
ah
oh yeah
Oh
yes we have the stone excellent news
there's a private jet waiting to bring
you to Miami I'll see you here tomorrow
the hell are we doing here anyways
the third stone is in possession of
socialite London Radisson she's here in
Florida vacationing with his boyfriend
on a private island just how do you plan
to get on to private island anyways
still underestimate any worse
Lily you're not stalking your ex
boyfriend again are you No
well she toid boshy until I have a
control did you want her guilty aren't
you having fun man this was so much fun
man God writing tickets yeah thrilling
pulling people over you know my wife she
had a tarot card reading she said that
something exciting was gonna happen in
my life damn it she write best what
tarot card
she's a clairvoyant she's a second
before she was seems more like psycho
so coming over for dinner today nope no
path to be in the car with you for eight
hours I could be the drink for 10 you
want to give you a list of the nears bar
sure yeah yeah you know what let's
second best I'm gonna walk my partner
well hey is this excellent first day
love your moves want to learn more
birthday pretty fuckin shitty if I do
say so myself
really what do you do I work in sales
who's the hottest thing I ever seen
Oh
[Laughter]
oh-oh-oh
yeah
Oh
oh my god
so can I get my gift now your gift how'd
I get your gift we just met
she's your birthday hmm you know my
donation my feed ah the money for the
sex you're a hooker you told me you
worked in sales I do I just sold you my
asshole hey oh wait Auri did you think
this was free oh my god
Murphy what the fuck give me your weapon
I guess it's back to writing a discount
you riding yes
desk no you got to be fucking kidding me
really
yeah welcome to my little College
you guys remember Lily you have
something for me
we do
two down three to go
which brings me to our your hair the
pink diamond is in possession of London
Radisson look dizzy hotel heiress yes
this will be like taking candy from a
baby
yeah roses right why do you need me uh
you see they're staying on a private
island and the only way on or off is by
boat so I need a woman with your special
talent I need to shoot them from a
thousand yards and no I need you to
steal a boat and I thought you had a
boat no I have a yacht why can't you
just sigh about because it's a paper
trail do I've to explain everything to
you guys and there you'll find all the
information about the house and everyone
who works for London Radisson tomorrow
no one is scheduled to be there except
her and her boyfriend you mean this guy
yeah yeah it plans me some sort of
aspiring rapper or some shit seems like
her taste in men is as questionable as
our wardrobe yeah and in your folder you
will find the coordinates to a shipwreck
it's a few miles off the coast it's the
pirate ship remains of the wicked storm
there's a chest and inside you'll find
the Ruby being our underwater expert I
figure shouldn't be a problem for you of
course not all right let's go do some
reconnaissance
really leaving so soon is that code for
something of course it is I see you are
interested in a little more than my boat
hijacking skills something like that
you
oh my god
ah
Oh
[Laughter]
oh bugger ether
Oh
huh
next time use the pooper scooper or a
bag trying to keep the beef really clean
no respect is this fun this is this one
we're like out on our bikes and we're
exercising and remaining beautiful shirt
great
hey let's go give me a coffee fuck
oh okay well I've spoke tell the captain
that you like whiskey your coffee my
stop is all right
yep uh - I seasoned uh - glazed donuts
looked all the way Pete peaches like
it's like effervescent delicious yep
cool that'll be 1050 please Lua and
dollars he says I thought coffee and
treats are free for fireman and police
yeah yo no bill because I'll have a gun
minimal listen you need to worry about
getting pounds first then worry about
the gun
okay these are aerodynamic skins okay go
I love it they could get our perps
faster oh it's gonna be ten there we go
yeah how no um fifty cents
Oh kids call it you know we'll call it
you owe me fifty says oh one more
all the money I had believed that hello
hi hey dude okay what can I get um I'll
have an iced tea okay rep tuna please
yep and one coffee okay I'll get this
way I always have to be different there
Thanks another I'll get these around me
it's awesome little film in it okay did
you hear him please all night no charge
it's not fair to quote my mother life's
not fair
see that yeah I'm looking at it
oh shit back hey honey ah no no no no
I'm just sitting here having tea with a
partner maybe this isn't the best place
to talk yeah you're joking right you
really think those guys are real cops
you're right
oh all right so here's the file she said
everything should be in here
so let's go over it and make plans yep
all right so looks like miss London
Radisson is with her new fiance puff
Dickie weird ah on an island Oh perfect
that's right up my alley okay but how
are we gonna find the diamond well maybe
one of us can go undercover good idea
sounds like we have a plan
let's go still a diamond I told you shoo
psychic my instincts tell me we should
follow those girls hold on but innocence
you mean your penis no I mean my gut
listen man they're up to something but
they're up to something big well hasn't
your big thing gotten into enough
trouble I heard them talk about rod of
this chick right here
London Radisson yes uh-huh
well if that's the case man we gotta
alert the captain no you know what
should not why not because this is a
chance for us to redeem ourselves not be
the laughingstock of the department you
may be accustomed to it but I am NOT
let's go mom I don't look let me stop
covering my doughnut come on
trying to get away
oh hey girl you take this month but is
it hot dealing knows not stealing or the
cops are crazy
I'll get everything over
you
this is going to be way too easy
IV sure let me shoot them when I had a
chance I would have been doing a public
service agreed but that's not the plan
okay so what's the plan
violet will pretend to be a massage
therapist as a celebration get for their
recent engagement are you kidding me
let me guess it's because I'm Asian
isn't it
once violet distracts them you and I
will go and steal the stone all right
fine such a few No this is super racist
oh damn shorty looking good
I didn't order no Chinese I'm actually
the massage therapist Radisson publicist
thought it might be a nice romantic
thing for you to holla
and I mean nothing
got me on my knees baby snap I just came
up with a wrong I got a like that shit
there I know I'm saying
looking at my bling you know you're my
girl that this to me money days when
gets pretty tired right huh she's heavy
lovely
that fine Africa great shit right there
look at all good and shit oh don't start
there yeah Suzanne let's go
you
Oh sweetheart you're not saying like
women don't get to like happy anything
shit you're a mean girl let's get all
happy I don't do that shit
massage show did tell a baby even
whatever you want my object
baby such a mean dick coming
Oh
ah
good girl yeah
Oh
yeah
Oh what
Oh
yeah
so fuck Miami police we need to come in
we think about to be robbed say who may
yell even real cops man
ain't lettin y'all in my crib you got
that essential documental shit
we are two real cops no but you're
letting a hot asian cat burglar first of
all she was a massage therapist a second
of all I don't even own a fucking cat
man oh yeah where's your big dancing
pink diamond
where'd she go
who the Chinese lady oh I think she's
Hawaiian she just blew ships go bitch
took my chain
what happened I don't know it fucking-a
ran out of gas
how can you run out of gas Oh mine we're
stuck stop fuck
according to the GPS it says the ship is
right below us I got this
did you get it
got it
can you two imbeciles explain to me why
the Coast Guard had to tow you in I was
following on a hunch since the same
hunch that told you is all right to
steal a waverunner
I you I didn't steal it I commandeered
for official police business with kelan
you weren't on official police business
you were assigned to the boardwalk yeah
except for you two opted to go on a
lovely romantic sightseeing tour now I
have a beach that is riddled with glass
containers and dog poop captured I'm not
good get out of my office
kick ass hours
if we could just get those diamonds back
there I know we could redeem ourselves
I just figure out where those bikini
bitch slide
Yemen it always just ask my why why
would we ask her
oh that's right she's chlamydia
Clare oh boy and yeah that's what I
meant
nice work thank you guys so uh what are
these jewels for anyway
you'll find out soon enough Alec excuse
me I need to pack where are you going
now Egypt course I'm on my way
I just Corre
hmm do you uh do you think it can help
honey I will try I can break out my
crystal ball and see if the spirits are
willing to communicate up is this an
arranged marriage or
I really lost a bet or something oh
you're so funny
I'm sad you said he was so funny he's
talking about you hmm
teddy yeah well she calls me that I
really don't like that I prefer to be
referred to by my given name Theodore
the Theodore Engelberg yeah that's so
much better
there it is
okay let's give this a try it's been a
few days
oh gosh okay I see something according
to the crystal would you seek is in a
land far away I see sand great pyramid a
desert
daddy get me a pen and paper what's this
the coordinates of what you seek Thank
You Sasha helping us I took a little
yeah oh gosh anything for my love my
honey but I'm sorry baby I need to
replenish everyone yeah
we want me to make some coffee or
something would know my wife and I are
going to make love now orgy I'd ask you
to leave
close the door behind you
inside
too much
baby
Oh
really
I've been eating healthy know how
delicious cookie
hey buddies farcical book what fuck you
doing here do you think I was gonna let
my own partner come out here all alone
you're crazy
we're not partners sure we are the
captain central partners man you're
looking a little red man I think he knew
little sunblock here come on you let's
get the fuck away from you there what
shit damn it
are you going oh is that yours
oh man look I want one you got lights on
yours
here hit some sunblock need it for your
shoulders I'll put it on you get away
from you that's a mock shot
it says it's right around here according
to the GPS the door is this way
the first we have company you get the
stone I'll be courteous
you
nice day is it not for you I'll take
care of this you go get her what you
want me to go down there yeah you go
down there now go ah
you
okay
stay right here right
you