is this on
we're recording oh okay
hi my name is Bob and well this is my
story
one hole
Tanner's a fine bitch oh fuck
bring the pussy over here I'll eat it
right so many more I got it put those on
the shelf
this girl is smokin yo this cullism Wow
look at this yo dog won't you stop
talking black man yo man I'm just
keeping it real dog you real white man
shit shit all I know is meeting this
girl right here we gonna have a date
tonight
it's gonna be me her and foxy-woxy right
yeah I'll be looking at her but I'll be
fuckin foxy Oh
yo Don you got some lotion on the Baxter
yeah man I'm on with crystal stairs
that's gross
hey come on is that motherfucking G like
a 9 year old man did you mom make this
if we I made it you'll make up our sum
that lotion no dawg yeah man don't use
it all
Oh
why is your shirt so fucking wrinkled
sorry mr. Josh shit and you quit jerking
off in that back bathroom on my cock
o'clock o'clock
I'm already ducking your pay for hours
for last week if you do it again you're
fired
yes sir and you keep up the good work I
would love to beat that motherfucker
down the street
why don't we put any
oh but yeah tell me I'm the sickest
woman in the world tell me I'm fucking
beautiful
good fucking cock shit I'm gorgeous boy
like that being a filthy little whore
Oh
ah
the forecast plenty of sunshine through
today with seasonal temperatures we
should reach our normal high of about 82
degrees by this afternoon clear skies
tonight with a low near 70 increasing
cloudiness tomorrow sticky and humid
with a high of 96
in the or ever make resolutions Reza huh
resolution you know that shit at the
begin of the year self-improvement shit
oh yeah restitution yes well my peeps
are supposed to be getting dog I
resolved to do more charity work man you
are
charity work shit that's it
what yo
hey dude I know I said to say that
you've never gotten laid right course I
have silly my right motherfuckin
testicle that you still a virgin
44 year old virgin record I got the
world record man you guys there's a new
hot we check it out cheer you gonna have
to wait I want the gloves now wait up
another bourbon on the rocks on make
that to both on me
you buy me a drink just thinking about
it
look buddy I don't swing that way
I'll get my own drink thank you you
dissing me man what you're trying to sit
I'm sort of pull smoker look bite I
don't care what you are
that'll be 850 clean you want you to
talk your buttons on that there blouse
slide your hand in there you can keep
the change
say one more inappropriate word Dora
pencil dick and I'll have you thrown out
on your ass so will some of that PB&J
men squid that peanut butter and jelly
man and now you're talking yeah
so much for that new year's resolution
dog I'll try to buy that dude over there
a drink man and you thought I was a
motherfucking pole smoker hey that's a
motherfucking shit
can I get your drink order you guys
ready to eat milk I would like a
passionfruit ice tea with a sweetener on
the side and your house salad just
iceberg lettuce though please with
Italian dressing on the side
haha
meatloaf for pussy pie pussy excuse me
Popeye so he said he said Popeye I can
loser are too gritty shit dog get a hold
of yourself
hey wait a second actually supposed to
be manning the story standing the store
you think I'm scared Ron I can take him
down one hand tied behind my back
do you know what the difference is
between X double X and xxx no actually I
don't but don't you work here
yeah that's really not my department
okay um well don't you at least watch
them you know what I'm on break
great II could help you though he
watches them all time I heard you would
watch adult movies um do you know the
difference between X I'm sorry perhaps I
could be of assistance to you sure yo
Dawg she said over here she's talking to
me and you come in like a bonus fuck she
was looking at me over there man what am
I looking at you she don't want the aid
in his service you want the ten-inch
servers she don't want to be pounced on
like a fucking cougar she want to be
heard on like myself you're not even a
black panther you're more like the white
shadow and shit you I'm always talking
the world type of shit man I wasn't born
this world man I can't even be leaders
they don't got a black dog
hey get your little ass up and come out
with me come on mama
it's Thursday night and you're young
and creeping styles are you kidding me
Stiles is amazing yeah for a geriatric
Hey look drop the dead guy and come out
with me as your boss I insist you can't
do that I can and I did
come on I give you ten minutes and put
something but I don't have anything
something nice
yo man I thought I told you to fucking
dress nice oh shit I did I went out and
I bought this new shirt and everything
till dark
look if you wouldn't know hung up on me
I was trying to tell you that I don't
have a bunch of nice clothes in my
closet now man relax
fuck enjoy yourself little bit cuz shit
son I really appreciate you guys
inviting me out and all but I just feel
comfortable in a place like this no no
you ain't going nowhere we should toast
toast toast to the boys night out wait
what is this tequila I can't why not
cuz it's gonna make my stomach upset
yeah but it's gonna make your head
fucking feel fantastic yo
I don't like places like this why I
guess you never know until you find out
look consider yourself a pet project of
mine there's a big smooth side he's
screaming to get out and I'm gonna free
her and this is just less than one I'm
gonna show you how to own yourself I'm
sorry
well what are we own in here it's
amateur night hon I'm gonna dance and
you're gonna see the way that all these
guys are worshipping you mean you're
gonna get naked you're gonna take your
clothes off oh you're gonna see what
you've been missing staying at home at
night reading
Ethan Agron dog paw it's Edgar Ethan
style whatever you're gonna see what
owning yourself can really do for you
well what sit up straight and take off
those damn glasses well if I do that
then I can see you owning yourself okay
good point contact lenses will come next
no no just say I want to tap it it i
want to tap that ass
[Laughter]
hey buddy just buy you a special dance
the VIP room special dance mm-hmm hero
VIP no you guys VIP room dark in there
animals that have been run over on the
road the Vietnam War my grandmother said
Wow
see how guys go crazy when you own your
own sexuality girl it's amazing isn't it
yeah now I want you to loosen the top
three buttons but they I want you to
take your hair down Vince and I want you
to take those glasses off I can't see
can we get two more shots of sex on the
beach please and can you bring us each
dry martini as well
just um so how's that feel I mean
they're never ever you're joking right
well um except in my dreams my dreams
are little not naughty just a little bit
well no a lot I'll tell you what a
little makeup on you some contact lenses
spike your confidence pinching some sexy
clothes and you'll feel it too okay you
really have never had an orgasm before
never huh these are good
and there she was my Aphrodite the girl
of my dreams god I think I'm gonna be
sick yo dog get up there and we went out
tonight got a party so he rollin with us
or we going
party she's gonna beat it oh she a girl
from the bar man
Aphrodite don't think about it let's go
down
sorry
tonight innocent one we're gonna go out
and we're gonna get you lead I listen
thanks come on
I'm gonna fix you up I'm gonna just see
to the nines I'm gonna make up your face
in your hair I'm gonna make you look
stunning
I don't know it's okay you don't have to
know cuz I do
see mama it's all in the attitude the
way that you carry yourself is more
important than being aesthetically
beautiful you can either walk like this
okay or you can walk like this hey wait
a minute wait a minute what am I
supposed to say to her now what dog it's
how oh excuse us
look man you got to make her feel
uncomfortable so that you don't exactly
why would I want to make her feel
uncomfortable though it's either you are
her dog you or her
works every time I don't know if I feel
comfortable acting like that you guys
what if she's a nice girl like a cool
man it's a game dog life's a game like
there's two types of parties and I know
this party's the winners and then
there's losers who do you want to party
with the winners winners yeah well it
all sounds so confusing you guys look I
know what you're talking about you I
mean take me for instance I used to
treat these bitches all nice and shit
they would walk all over me so I pushed
it up my game and shit with now I got
these bitches eating out my head you too
man right
we're kind of gonna get here man hey
Dawg yo hey
hi I'm a I'm Bob mm Bob you look look
nice tonight Bob I do don't I
you look nice too
smoking as a matter of fact oh thanks um
you work it the video store right yeah
when I'm not doing better things you
know I've had the hots for you since the
titty bar you look almost as good as the
girls that work there you're making me
feel really uncomfortable right now is
this a test because if it is I'll leave
you know what let me finish that for you
I all right I'm an asshole that's what
you are
whoa wait wait wait wait I'm sorry this
is bad this is very bad it's wrong I
think that the guys told me to to act
this way I have very little like no
experience actually at this to be honest
with you I like you whom I thought for
you to like me that I had to be just
stupid and stupid
we try this again
the I'm a kebab damn girl fly out hey
shit head up on my bedroom floor though
but you no more mine my fuck out
really alright but we got to go to my
house I need a change of clothes
Jimmy's and some styling products
okay let's take all that crease damn
yeah
Oh
oh do what'd you do that for the bad
advice
screwed everything up bad advice and
that was damn good
all right I'm sorry
sorry buddy I don't blame you from
hitting me
I just don't hit me so fucking hard me I
don't think you realize how strong you
are
you just can't treat women like pieces
of meat you know not the ladies they
have feelings too you know they're just
like me and you how many women do you
get anyway get a lot yeah a lot of women
see I don't think so
otherwise you wouldn't be in the back
masturbating half the day like that all
right all right someone get a lot honey
I mean I get so I just have a problem
keeping them well maybe if you treated
him with a little more respect you know
took an interest in things that they
like where they like to shop music they
like the food to eat you serious yeah
I'm serious
maybe if you looked at a woman like she
had something more than just genitals I
mean like the tittie
yeah like no you know Bob it's pretty
smart for a virgin straight up do ya
all right thanks
here it's for you
so after that night we never left each
other's side
dance walks
spending every waking moment together
I want to do it to it like Joe well sure
I'm sure
well I mean it is it's been six months
and and you're the only one I care about
and I really want you to be my first and
my last I mean if there's okay yeah I
got it and it looks let's do it d do you
have a condom
um yeah
get a couple actually okay like a year
supply
well that that works it's great
mmm can we go freshen up okay yeah yeah
okay
I'll be right back okay all right all
right
I've never worn one of these before
let me help you with that Wow
you look great but first
and
Oh Eddie
Oh
jeez
he tastes good though
yeah yeah yeah
Oh
oh wow baby
oh wow
Oh God wow this feels so good I need it
hard now because it's so good Oh
Oh
yeah
so in the end it was all about finding
the right one and not just about getting
laid but connecting to someone who could
love me for me there's far more
important to experience love for the
first time it happened I found love
come to Daddy papa are we going on to
the club man she's gonna be there who's
she
the fag the one that's the hermaphrodite
between excuse me shorty yep
perhaps you'd like some assistance how
long it's you Oh
talkin to me yo fuck she's talking to
you she's looking at me over there man
she wants my help
Dawg I'm sittin trying to help but you
don't want the 10 inch service I'm
jerking off to this paint color bitch
right my grandmother saggy boobs shit Oh
quite first kitty that hyung it's all
shit turn
[Laughter]
you