is this on
we're recording oh okay um hi my name is
Bob and well this is my story
fart hole
fuck
bring the pussy over you eat it right so
many more I got it put those on the
Shelf is smoking yo this colors look at
this
yo Dawg won't you stop talking black man
yo man I'm just keepin it real dawg you
real white man shit shit all I know is
meeting this girl right here we gonna
have a date tonight
it's gonna be me her and foxy Roxy right
yeah I'll be looking at her but I'll be
fuckin foxy oh yo Don you got some
lotion on the Baxter yeah man I'm on
with crystal stairs that's gross
hey come on like a 9 year old did you
mom excessively I made it go make up our
sum that lotion no dawg yeah
you
oh boy
why is your shirt so fucking wrinkled
sorry mr. Josh shit and you quit jerking
off in that back bathroom on my cock
o'clock o'clock
I'm already ducking your pay for hours
for last week if you do it again you're
fired
yes sir and you keep up the good work I
would look like beep dead motherfucker
down the street
why don't we uh oh
but yeah tell me I'm the sickest woman
in the world tell me I'm fucking
beautiful
good fucking cock shit gorgeous
ah
the forecast plenty of sunshine through
today with seasonal temperatures we
should reach our normal high of about 82
degrees by this afternoon clear skies
tonight with a low near 70 increasing
cloudiness tomorrow sticky and humid
with a high of 96
in the are ever make resolutions Reza
huh resolution you know that shit at the
begin of the year
self-improvement shit oh yeah
restitution yes what my peeps are
supposed to be getting dog I resolved to
do more charity work man you are
charity work shit that's it what yo
hey dude I know it's safe to say that
you've never gotten laid right course I
have silly my right motherfuckin
testicle that you still a virgin 44 year
old virgin record I got the world record
man you guys check it out cheering you
gonna have to wait I want the glutes
now wait up
another bourbon on the rocks on make
that to both on me
you buy me a drink just thinking about
it
look buddy I don't swing that way
I'll get my own drink thank you you what
you're trying to sit oh I'm sort of pole
smoker look bite I don't care what you
are
that'll be 850 clean you want you to top
your buttons on that there blouse slide
your hand in there you can keep the
change
say one more inappropriate word or
pencil dick and I'll have you thrown out
on your ass so will some of that PB&J
man squid that peanut butter and jelly
man and now you're talking yeah so much
for that new year's resolution dog I'll
try to buy that dude over there a drink
man and you thought I was a
motherfucking pole smoker hey that's a
motherfucking shit
can I get your drink order you guys
ready to eat milk I would like a
passionfruit ice tea with a sweetener on
the side and your house salad just
iceberg lettuce don't please with
Italian dressing on the side
for pussy boy pussy huh excuse me Popeye
Saudi he said he said Popeye fucking
loser dr. Grady shit dog get ahold of
yourself
hey wait a second
she's supposed to be manning the store
in the store do you think I'm scared of
Ron I can take him down one hand tied
behind my back
do you know what the difference is
between X double X and xxx no actually I
don't but don't you work here
yeah that's really not my department
okay um well um don't you at least watch
them you know what I'm on break
grade II could help you though he
watches them all time I heard you and
watch adult movies um do you know the
difference between X I'm sorry perhaps I
could be of assistance to you sure yo
Dawg she sent over here she's talking to
me and you come in like a bone it was
looking at me over there we're not
looking at you she don't want the 8 inch
never seen with the 10 inch servers she
don't want to be pounced on like a
fucking cougar she want to be heard on
like myself you're not even a black
panther you're more like the white
shadow and shit always talking the world
up with Shimin I would have warned this
world man I can't even be leaders they
all got a dog
hey get your little ass up and come out
with me come on mama
it's Thursday night and you're young
and creeping styles are you kidding me
Styles is amazing yeah for a geriatric
hey like drop the dead guy and come out
with me as your boss I insist you can't
do that I can and I did
come on I give you ten minutes and put
something sexy but I don't have anything
sometimes
oh man I thought I told you to fucking
dress nice oh shit I did I what happened
I bought this new shirt and everything
yeah if you wouldn't have hung up on me
I was trying to tell you that I don't
have a bunch of nice clothes in my
closet now now relax
fuck enjoy yourself a little bit cousin
I really appreciate you guys inviting me
out and all but I just feel comfortable
in a place like no no you ain't go
nowhere
we should toast toast toast to the boys
night out wait what is this tequila I
can't why not cuz it's gonna make my
stomach upset yeah but it's gonna make
your head fucking feel fantastic yo
little wee-wee
I don't like places like this why I
guess you never know until you find out
huh
look consider yourself a pet project of
mine there's a big scene inside you
screaming to get out and I'm gonna free
her and this is just less than one I'm
gonna show you how to own yourself I'm
sorry
well what are we own in here it's
amateur night hon I'm gonna dance and
you're gonna see the way that all these
guys are worshipping you mean you're
gonna get naked you're gonna take your
clothes off oh you're gonna see what
you've been missing staying at home at
night reading
Ethan Agron dog paw it's Edgar Ethan
style whatever you're gonna see what
owning yourself can really do for you
well whatever
sit up straight and take off those damn
glasses oh if I do that then I can see
you owning yourself okay good point
contact lenses will come next no no no
just say I want to tap it it i want to
tap that ass
hey buddy just buy you a special
definitely IP room special dance mm-hmm
VIP no you guys VIP room dark in there
animals that have been run over on the
road if you had not wore my grandmother
seg
Wow
Wow see how the guys go crazy when you
own your own sexuality girl it's amazing
isn't it yeah now I want you to loosen
my top 3 buttons but they I want you to
take your hair down meats and I want you
to take those glasses off I can't see
can we get two more shots of sex on the
beach please and can you bring us each
dry martini as well
um so I feel I have never never ever
you're joking right
well um except in my dreams my dreams
are little not naughty just a little bit
well no a lot I'll tell you what a
little makeup on you some contact lenses
spike your confidence pinching some sexy
clothes and you'll feel it too okay you
really have never had an orgasm before
these are good
and there she was my Aphrodite the girl
of my dreams god I think I'm gonna be
sick
yo dog get up there and we're goin out
tonight go to party so are you rolling
with us or are we goin party she's gonna
beat it pushy girl from the bar man
Aphrodite don't think about a let's go
down tonight innocent one we're gonna go
out and we're gonna get you lead I know
that Thanks come on I'm gonna fix you up
I'm gonna just see to the nines we're
gonna make up your face in your hair I'm
gonna make you look stunning
I don't know it's okay you don't have to
know cuz I do
see mama it's on the attitude the way
that you carry yourself is more
important than being aesthetically
beautiful you can either walk like this
okay or you can walk like this hey wait
a minute wait a minute what am I
supposed to say to her now
what dog its how huh excuse us
look man you got to make her feel
uncomfortable so that you don't exactly
why would I want to make her feel
uncomfortable though it's either you or
her dog you or her
works every time I don't know if I feel
comfortable acting like that you guys
what if she's a nice girl cool man
it's a game dog life's a game like
there's two types of parties and I know
this party's the winners and then
there's losers who do you want to party
with the winners winners yeah what all
sounds so confusing you guys look I know
what you're talking about you I mean
take me for instance I used to treat
these bitches all nice and shit they
would walk all over me so I pushed it up
my game and shit with now I got these
bitches eating out my head you too man
right what kind of gonna get here man
hey dawg Hey
[Laughter]
hi I'm a I'm Bob you look nice tonight
Bob I do don't I
you look nice too smoking oh thanks um
you work it the video store right yeah
when I'm not doing better things you
know I've had the hots for you since the
titty bar you look almost as good as the
girls that work there you're making me
feel really uncomfortable right now is
this a test because if it is I'll leave
you know what let me finish that for you
I all right I'm an asshole that's what
you are no wait wait wait wait were you
I'm sorry this is bad this is very bad
it's wrong I think that the guys told me
to to act this way I have very little
like no experience actually it does to
be honest with you I like you oh I
thought for you to like me that I had to
be I'm stupid
we try this again the I'm made of a bob
damn girl wow thanks shit better up on
my bedroom floor though you know why
mine MA
really alright but we got to go to my
house I need to change your clothes
Jimmy's and some styling products
Oh
oh do what'd you do that for the bad
advice I can screwed everything up bad
advice
and that was damn good all right I'm
sorry
sorry Bob I don't blame you from hitting
me
I just don't hit me so fucking hard me I
don't think you realize how strong you
are
you just can't treat women like pieces
of meat you know I'm not the ladies they
have feelings too you know they're just
like me and you how many women do you
get anyway get a lot yeah a lot of women
see I don't think so otherwise you
wouldn't be in the back masturbating
half the day like that all right all
right
someone get a lot honey I mean I get so
I just have a problem keeping them well
maybe if he had treated him with a
little more respect you know
took an interest in things that they
like where they like to shop music they
like the food to eat you serious yeah
I'm serious
maybe if you looked at a woman like she
had something more than just genitals oh
you mean like the titties yeah what no
you know Bob he's pretty smart for a
version straight up do ya all right
thanks
here it's for you
so after that night we never left each
other's side days walks spending every
waking moment together
I want to do it to it
like do it
are you sure well I mean is it's been
six months and and you're the only one I
care about and I really want you to be
my first and my last I mean if there's
okay yeah I got him and it looks deep do
you have a condom
um yeah
get a couple actually okay like a year
supply
well that that works it's great
mmm can I go freshen up okay
yeah yeah okay
I'll be right back okay all right all
right
I've never worn none of these before
let me help you with that Wow
you look great but first
and
Oh Eddie
jeez
he tasted
yeah yeah yeah
oh oh baby
baby Oh
Oh
Wow
oh wow this feels so good
I need it hard now because it's so good
Oh
so in the end it was all about finding
the right one and not just about getting
laid but connecting to someone who could
love me for me was far more important to
experience love for the first time it
happened I found love
come to Daddy papa are we going on to
the club man she's gonna be there who's
she
the fag the one that's the hermaphrodite
between excuse me shorty yep perhaps
you'd like some assistance how long it's
you Oh talking to me
yo fuck she's talking to you she's
looking at me over there man she wants
my help
dog I'm still trying to help but you
don't want the 10 inch service I'm
jerking off to this pink color bitch my
grandmother saggy boobs shit Oh quite
first kitty that hung itself you should
[Laughter]
turn
you