The Beatress (A woman who makes birds or
wild animals come out from the bushes,
so that hunters can shoot them.)
If it's as dumb as you say,
then why are you leaving?
Well, I'm not leaving, my darling...
I'm being shipped away.
It's what they call "promotion"...
Robert, there is a favor
I would ask of you.
It's partly for me,
but mostly for Jocelyne.
Relax, she already knows about this.
It's the reason we're having lunch together.
So you two could get acquainted.
I would like you to take care of her,
while I'm away.
She's a very nice girl, you'll see!
Her problem is that
she doesn't know anyone here.
She would be lost without you...
If she needs anything at all,
she can call me.
You don't understand.
I'm asking you to take her home with you.
As a lodger.
Robert!
Do I really need to elaborate on this?
But...
You know, my place is really small!
Oh, but she takes up very little space.
And the space she keeps...
She keeps really, really well.
Isn't that true, my darling?
She really needs to take care
of someone to be happy.
Come on, you don't really mean to say...
that Jocelyne and I...
while you're away...
Well, why not?
You'll enjoy the very special qualities
of our little friend here.
Oh, Greg, please!
Okay, lucky guy.
I'm leaving you with the tab.
I guess it's worth it, right?
No, stay seated.
I hate farewells.
But don't forget.
I'm leaving Jocelyne in your care
while I'm away.
But I fully intend to have her back
when i return.
Okay?
Understood.
Look around you, Robert.
And tell me which woman you would like
to have at your place tonight.
You, Jocelyne!
Of course.
But...
Here, what about that one?
She's very beautiful.
What time would you like us
to be at your home?
For dinner?
Oh, er, yes... for dinner.
Dinner would be good.
Let's say, at 8 pm?
Today's forecast includes some fog.
That could lead to frost on the roads.
During the day, the sky will be cloudy
thoughout the nation.
With some rain and snow.
Rain showers will reach the Alps and
the Central Mountains in the afternoon.
While blustery weather is expected
from Brittany to the Paris Basin.
This is my friend Inge,
a stewardess.
Inge, this is Robert.
Good evening.
This way.
We're lucky that you're free tonight.
I had dinner plans with some friends
but i canceled, no problem.
Are they appetizers?
Yes.
In my home, appetizers...
are like this.
It seems more appropriate to me.
But, one need not exclude the other.
Let's get down to serious business.
What do you think, darling?
I mean, we should start dinner.
Dinner is also a serious business.
What are you talking about?
Your pleasure.
It's really difficult to eat
under these conditions.
Do you want to know
what she just told me?
No, let's just keep eating.
That will be better.
How do you like it?
You're gonna drive me crazy,
both of you.
I hope so.
- Are you satisfied?
- Shouldn't I be?
I want to do whatever
makes you happy.
Ask me anything you like.
Well, choose a shop and
I'll buy you a present.
A present? For no reason?
Indeed, for no reason...
I'd like some pretty lingerie.
There is only one condition.
You must choose them for me.
I must see you wearing them.
To know if they fit you.
You're right, sir.
We have a little lounge
at your disposal.
And madam will be able to try
them on, undisturbed.
Follow me, please.
- Who is that lady?
- A pain in the arse.
And you know what else?
She's the Countess of Mortmolle.
She wants to dress
like a young boy.
Oh, that's lovely.
It's a new model, madam.
Absolutely lovely.
No?
This is the latest creation
that's just come in.
The cut is classic.
The clips are very simple.
And above all, these lovely little hearts
emphasize the breasts.
You should try it on.
So you can feel how soft it is on your skin.
Just one thing...
You mustn't wear anything else.
Especially no bra.
This design doesn't require one.
What do you think, darling?
What I've always thought...
A semi-dressed woman is a thousand times
more desirable.
Could you please wear this lingerie.
That way, I can have a better look.
Certainly, madam.
You know, you're very pretty.
You're very beautiful.
Maybe, madam but i prefer
when told so by a man.
Did you hear that, Robert?
Well, I'll tell you miss.
I'm telling you, you're very beautiful.
They're so small, it's hardly worth
wearing them.
But it seems that
they're very special.
And men love them a lot.
Are you wearing any?
Oh no sir.
I'm wearing pantyhose.
Oh, how awful!
Better to wear nothing than pantyhose.
Look.
I find panties indecent.
Stockings and garter belt, okay.
But no panties, please.
Could you please model them for us?
By seeing them on you,
maybe we'll change our minds.
Am I right, darling?
Very well, madam.
Is it too much to ask of you sir
to turn your back, while i remove my pantyhose.
Yes, it's too much to ask,
but how could i refuse?
Oh! No way madam.
Oh no, i can't do that.
Yes you can, miss.
And you'll do this for me.
I don't want to upset you, but i think
we've gone a little too far this time.
Oh! Not at all, darling.
You know very well that
the challenge always excites me.
And as promised,
tonight she'll be here.
Completely naked under her dress.
And ready to fulfill
all your desires.
Submissive and perverted
like a hooker.
Well, we can only hope.
If it's like you say,
then anything is possible.
Anything is possible!
You only need ask and I shall do.
How do i look?
Very beautiful.
Very well.
We'll be here tonight at 9 pm.
Ah good evening, your Ladyship.
Robert, I'll permit you to call me Géraldine.
Oh! A Kandinsky!
I already feel good here,
my dear Robert.
Please come in, your Ladyship.
It's lovely.
Oh! It's wonderful!
It's really lovely.
What a wonderful apartment
you have, Robert.
Countess, would you like a drink?
Yes please, my dear.
A Whiskey Coke, if you have one.
Of course.
Géraldine please,
all in good time.
Would you like to dine now?
My dear Robert,
I'd prefer to dine later.
As you wish.
Do you collect them?
No, not exactly.
They're birthday presents.
From many birthdays.
What a great idea!
Now I know what present I'll give for
the birthday of my dear François Xavier.
That's my husband.
Oh! This one is so funny!
It'll be funnier when
you get it up the ass.
Aah! That's where this little thing goes?
My dear Robert, you must never get bored
with all these items?
But Robert uses other things.
These items are here
just for decoration.
Too bad!
If you want we can bring them out,
to give them some fresh air.
These little things included.
No, Countess.
You know that you should not
make the first move.
You promised me.
You're here to do everything
my master asks of you.
And to do it well.
I'm sorry Jocelyne but
I have a fiery temper.
Then, suck me Countess.
With pleasure.
Undress me, Countess.
Your Ladyship, I am pleased to announce
that you're about to get fucked.
And that's a promise.
Promise me Robert. But above all, do it.
You're really just a big slut.
Oh yeah, baby. It seems that
I'm one of a kind.
You like that huh?
I just phoned our dear Countess.
She had a hard time
explaining away her little escapade.
Especially considering her condition
when she got home.
That's her problem.
Was she satisfied, at least?
So much so, that
she wants to see you again.
Well, to see us again.
Out of the question!
Once is fun, but twice, no!
I'm counting on you in this, okay?
As you know, part of my mission is to prevent
them from "breaking your balls," as you say.
Do you think they're mother and daughter?
The only way to know for sure,
is to ask them.
Tell me, do you like them?
They are charming.
And you want both, of course?
If they're really mother and daughter,
that would seem difficult.
Nope... not a problem, my dear.
- Let's say, 9 pm?
- You're crazy.
Yes, crazy about you.
Come on, get lost.
Hello, yes.
Ah, it's you!
So, is there a problem?
They really were mother and daughter.
And you're calling me to tell me,
it's not working.
You've finally hit a snag, honey.
You're losing your touch.
Come home, I'm waiting for you.
What are you saying?
Yes, let me write it down.
Street...
Yes.
At what time?
All right, I'll finish my shower
and come over right away.
A surprise?
At least, tell me what it is?
Hello?
Shit.
Good evening, darling.
Will you tell me what's going on already?
Come in and I'll tell you everything.
What is this place anyway?
Have a little patience, my darling.
I told you it was a surprise!
Come on, follow me.
- I don't believe it!
- Yes, it's true.
Allow me to introduce Edith
and her daughter Émilie.
Good evening Robert.
Welcome to our home. Please excuse
us for insisting you come here.
We feel cosier at home.
And it is proper for the ladies
to be receiving, anyway.
So, it seems nothing is impossible
after all, sweetheart?
All three of us are here
for your pleasure...
- It's your favorite brand.
- Correct.
You see, thanks to Jocelyne,
we know everything about you.
You should feel at home here.
Just ask and we shall do as you please.
They know everything about you.
But you too must known certain things.
Especially about Émilie.
To your health, Émilie.
Émilie is a virgin.
Well... almost.
She has never made love with a man.
And I'm very happy that you'll be
the first one to take her, Robert.
And what does Émilie think of this?
Since it must happen at some point...
I would like it to be with you...
If you agree, of course.
Émilie is young.
But she's a real woman already.
Look!
And her legs...
She knows many things.
And you can ask almost anything of her.
Unless you prefer that Edith show the way.
I have a feeling that wonderful things
are going to happen here.
What do you think, Edith?
Just ask, Robert, just ask!
I would really like Robert to take me now...
Émilie is getting impatient.
She would like you to take her now!
Maybe it would be best
if we moved to the bedroom.
I like that black girl very much.
Can I at least finish watching the movie?
Of course.
My name is Baron da Marie.
- And you? Are you Robert?
- Yes, I'm Robert.
- And her, she's Jocelyne.
- Yes, we already know each other.
Oh, you have a beautiful house.
This is the kind of house
I would like to have.
May I touch?
Yes, you may touch.
What do you do for a living?
Nothing very interesting.
So, you do nothing.
Well, i'm an usherette.
I place people.
That's really pleasant.
And they are always nice with me.
- Do you go to the movies?
- Sometimes.
I watch all the movies with
Mr. Jean-Paul and Mr. Alain.
- Jean-Paul Belmondo and Alain Delon.
- Ah, Yes.
- And do you like them?
- Oh yes! They are beautiful.
And they are so nice.
But they're always in trouble.
I'd like to kiss them everywhere.
Can you arrange that?
Robert can do a lot of things,
if you ask nicely.
I'll do anything you want me to do.
If you can arrange it.
And if i can't?
It doesn't matter,
I'll still do anything.
How does this machine work?
Make it work for me.
Turn off those lights
and I'll dance for you.
I want this one naked
under a black raincoat.
Stockings and garters?
Black stockings and black garters.
I'll see you at home.
Hi beautiful. It doesn't work every time, eh?
Lost your touch, maybe?
Oh, no I didn't,
and it still works!
Come in!
Allow me to introduce Robert.
And this is Nadine.
Good evening, Nadine.
Good evening.
Please come in.
Darling, it does still work,
but there is a small problem.
Really? Is she maybe menstruating?
No sir, but i can't spend
the entire night here.
She must return home fairly early.
A jealous husband, perhaps?
Not yet...
Well, actually, I'm getting married
tomorrow morning, at ten!
Last evening as a single woman?
This calls for a party!
Nadine, believe us.
Jocelyne and I are going to outdo ourselves!
Champagne!
Music!
Where are they?
My darlings, the Champagne is ready.
You can't watch, wait for us out there.
But the Champagne?
Keep it fresh.
Please, let us prepare
for your pleasure.
Panties or no panties?
No panties.
It's more beautiful for a bride.
Yes, but tomorrow I'll wear them.
Or else my Albert
will not understand.
For him, a bride must be
all in white.
Shit! What is it?
Maybe a wrong number.
- Maybe an ex-girlfriend?
- Yes, maybe.
I'll go.
No, you stay here and
take care of our bride.
Sorry to bother you, sir.
Her Ladyship saw the light on.
She wants to know if
she could visit now.
She would be very pleased.
Send her up.
She'll be properly welcomed.
I have no doubt about it.
I'll tell her right away.
- Have you ever fucked the Countess?
- You can't be serious?
Yes or no?
Unfortunately, no sir.
Do you at least know
how to behave?
Almost as well as you do, sir.
Okay, take this key and
make a discreet entrance later.
It will be done.
As you say, sir.