well this my grandfather jebediah
Jackson this is his place
and I can't believe it's actually been a
year since gone he'll bring back a lot
of memories place excuse me Crete would
you find it strange that the executor of
the estate sent you a letter from your
grandfather a year after he died that
can only be opened in his house
nevertheless in the grave cookie I say
we don't stay here I mean it's what
makes me feel like a kid again well you
should we go through the weather bed
knucklehead we make this a quick visit
okay okay there he is
my grandpa jebediah Jackson why he was
the greatest storyteller ever I mean he
could tell you about historical bits
just like he was actually there he's the
greatest is this him - I know no that
was his grandpa General Jeb Jackson he
rode with robert e lee with old Virginny
yeah back in the old war you know with
the southern independence she had why
grandpa used to tell me that he had
quite a reputation about why when he
would go on to the battlefield the
Yankees would take one look at him and
turn tail and run
oh yeah he was great and of course after
the war is quite an engine fighter he
names would see him and Shake in their
moccasins mm-hmm this is a family
resemblance
you know it's weird you feel a ZZ Top
looks and these guys look exactly the
same
yeah you know you're right but other
than that similarities with you look
that's all if they had in common I mean
great grandpa why he was a great war
hero and an engine fighter in grandpa
here well he was a scientist and an
inventor what an eccentric one at that
what happened to you hey being a
chiropractor is a noble occupation why I
why I aligned may inform people
you know what they say if you're not
properly aligned don't you know but I'm
sure you're about to tell me when your
tires go bald your rear end shakes but
enough about that tell you what why
don't I take you to the most important
room grandpa's laboratory Wow look Ellis
stuff what is he working on I don't know
I mean he's real secretive about his
last project didn't want it to fall in
the wrong hand
something about comic spies being
everywhere what a good I guess some
Sandhya's for read Perry could be too
much chlorine in the gene pool how do
you open that letter soon here Randall
if you're reading this that it means
that your old grandpa's gone I have
something to tell you that you're going
to find hard to understand this thing's
our story that I told you when you were
a kid were not passed down actually
lived them that's right
I was the ancestor that was in King
Arthur's Court I crossed the ocean with
Columbus bought the revolution and yes
the truth is the truth is now is also
the old general an Indian fighter your
real ancestors were nothing but
bootleggers and horse thieves
so I single-handedly had given you a
family tree that you could be proud of
what size straightjacket did you say
your grandfather wore a sham I've
invented a time machine
a time machine yes a time machine
Einstein's theory states time is not
consistent but flexible with this
machine there is no longer any
distinction between three-dimensional
time and space I have proven that they
are fused in a four-dimensional time and
space continuum of course I just it just
makes perfectly good sense and that's
why I went to college I should know this
perfect sense you have heard of the
fourth dimension no now the fifth
dimension I've heard of you know the age
of
damnit this is serious I mean just
imagine that you could be transported
into the past or into the future I'm not
just incredible
wait there's me okay you'll find the
time machine hidden under a drop cloth
here in the lab okay here the
instructions use this machine wisely
face dire consequences Oh higher
consequences haha
is this proof enough this this is your
proof this only proves you had a
crackpot in Center for a grandfather so
can we go now
Oh fine if you're gonna be like this and
I just won't tell you what the rest of
the letter says oh don't tell me
your grandfather was officer than me on
the grassy knoll that's not funny
okay PA so please find a bank statement
book with your name on it yeah back in
the 1890s I picked up a few bags of gold
nuggets in Alaska and next thing you
know we'll Jeb's a millionaire but with
today's market the balance should exceed
1 million dollars spend it wisely
your loving grandfather check the diet
Jackson $1 I knew I had a good feeling
about all this and that grandfather of
yours
did I not say genius then give me that
bank most recent one new uclan yes now
let's celebrate
there's something about money that makes
me feel so yeah testing
Oh
well oh it's good what is worth about
five hundred thousand
I've heard down yeah that's all
Wow huh I mean it was good oh he was
more than good but that's it serious
blow job
no no if you're gonna want the whole
million then I I think we're gonna have
to get a little bit more creative Mac
start again
where's the PM letter with the
inscription where did you put it okay
really big joke where the hell are we oh
man hey look down the hill there's a
town well what's out of there what the
hell year is it well according to an
annual magnetron is 1882 great 1882 well
with Kidd now that you've watched the
instructions how are we going to get out
of here
that's easy all you have to do is adjust
the magnetron Cohen sis with capillary
balancing out the developers and sliding
up the discombobulated er I mean anymore
I could figure it out well then you
ought to know well thanks for load of
confidence hey what's that time say um
cripple creek cripple creek okay
hey cripple creek 1882 hey that's the
same year that my grandfather was
telling me deputy old generals in or
that my grandfather's in or vice versa
or anyway listen this if we can find my
grandfather then maybe he can help me
figure out how to run this contraption
come on let's go down attack
so they driver it's a trip the license
please don't okay come on just touch the
graveyard oh this is good
this welcomes everyone yeah we're cross
am ii fish yeah no wonder they call this
cripple creek nice friendly town it has
a lot of love in that news okay see what
I'm going this trading post
give me a Western that I can blend in
with the locals
welcome to once you go over the hotel
over there get us a room welcome back to
you when it's safe with a woman's home
fine to care if you don't get yourself
rope necktie
that's great you're gonna do great
ah barkeep give me a four fingers worth
of Rhetta win it no I might be killing
someone today so you better go all the
way it's good huh little information
Oprah now you're don't cotton to
strangers going around and asking
questions if you look harmless so true
sir
plus one you see ya lookin for a man
Mike wins
my name's Willie Bell thank you well Lou
he will how much fun you win his heart
of the hymns and handful of bumblebees
all right I'll just shooting in the back
as he walks by and you can't do that
you're the deputy I want this to be a
fair fight
I'll shoot them with that one now I know
it of course really nice that's enough
Tenderfoot
hey you walk around these boots all day
any left enemy to his home yeah I got
news for you I was at ruling lion scare
nobody listen bud this hair ain't big
enough for the both of us
come on you yeah and down back something
that is the correct time right well now
2:15 I'm waitin on you do that oh you do
that side one butch went polecat
that polecat is deputy really cause
button and then she's brother
sheriff Chester Kasbah
they're the two best shot in this
territory you're mighty brave man take
on you so you don't understand yeah I'm
not exactly gonna be in a gunfight with
those two no see I'm a very dilute
threshold for death okay
and my doctor specifically told me do
not have any bullets under this body
while ism didn't recognize you stand now
speaking of lying horizontal I don't
think our stranger here once get in a
gunfight with me but I can understand
you coming alone oh we're trying to
convince me not to kill him mummy you
love your brother and such right nope
but I'm used to wherever I've seen your
face before right here now
take the whiskered way say you're a
spitting image and general Jeff Jackson
oh he's my grandpa he's about patty yeah
I'm looking for him know where I'm
fighting maybe you wrote out in here
about two weeks ago
Sancho that renegade shy and cheap Sigma
go on to the school bone path from what
I understand ah well thanks for the info
sure you know when it's knockers - you
little bell ah
hope you find a stranger he's a fine
fellow and a hell of an engine fire
Randall what's this I hear you're gonna
be in a gun fight
no no not me sister no listen I got some
good news though I think I found out
where my grandfather is I'm gonna go
ahead and try to find him and meet him
why don't you go ahead and meet me by
the time machine first thing in the
morning
well that's just typical of you always
running away from confrontation I do not
and I don't have to stand here and take
this
come on this is the old web I want to
see a real gun fight with shivery I
traded in for a Buick hey Brendon ah
listen I got to go I got about as much
creature here the snow man yeah hey it's
brewing see in st. Louie
okay
hillbilly strong to beat it out of town
too cluttered up I want to blast that
barn why'd I leave him alone here want
to brush your bills gang anyway he
didn't look like him I sure wasn't known
that he was one a Jeff Jackson kid
that's what he said and he won't want
Adele dead - and kids that's for sure
what would you two Cowboys know about
kids well I sure do know that when
you're kids you didn't have a doll to
play with you got a rat and you still
got one right up in your tail oh yeah
well how would you two like to play with
my rattler got the nerve
Oh
ah
I
yes
little squaw keepo to run keep me back
where the great chief co-editor noisy
neighbor saw you day saying bumper
Watoto warm up what that mean don't come
knocking it to be wrong
Oh
oh oh oh
like that
Oh
hiya babe is this the Chiefs tepee how
does white man know that well it was the
chief that just left or some man with
the chicken for a hat my name little
quack al Oh little quail tail or is it
quail or can I just call your tail well
enough for that listen I was wondering
if you could help I'm looking for a
frontiers man by the name of Jeff
Jackson I'm his grandson I wonder if you
can help me find him
little crow will tell you and trade for
kiss okay so you're going to lose out on
this deal
what what a kiss huh hiya chief you got
my squaw city moves angry do not like
what white man does hey if you don't
like the way we do things in this
country don't you go back to where you
came from
let me move scalpel whoa hey I didn't
come here for a scalp treatment white
men talk too much like chief heap mad no
no no white man red man friend
no white man wants to be read brothers
friend and read sister to anyway want to
get a canoe and I'll paddle you later
white man speak with forked tongue what
is that supposed to mean old Indian
saying all old Indian say it why are you
insinuating that the white man is in the
red man's friend why who was it who
swindled you out of Manhattan Island for
24 bucks why man
yeah Sarah who was it who turned you
into Ward and stuck you in front of a
cigar store why man and who was it who
put your head on a nickel and took the
nickel away slot machine why man is son
of heap big tell face warrior Jackson
yeah tell face Jackson killed 50 best
warriors I think we take white man's
legs time to horses and make a wish hey
sounds like you want to part my hair all
the way to my balls and I don't think so
Geronimo hey hey hey oh no I'm not gonna
get a hatchet job
good throw chief xeo pepper Randall
Randall he stuck his finger in my plum
he stuck his finger in your what hi
he must have Indian in with the Village
People Randall Randall you okay hi
there's three of you yeah I'm the one in
the middle
Oh have your two friends let's get out
of here what now genius okay I got this
thing off to get out there the reason
why we can't find my grandfather is
because basically you cannot duplicate
the same time space continuum brilliant
I'm fine what the hell does that mean
what that means is that the time machine
cannot be in the same place at the same
time twice oh well that clears it up
don't worry don't worry I got it all
figured out okay all I have to do is
just punch in 1996 then hit enter then
after that all I have to do is hit the
engage switch from we're gone
we're out of you let's go okay
1996 right in judge
good you're in then hurryin yes hello
who is it oh no fuck oh well who would
do something like this ah cute it's all
over my new sandals ah apparently we
were attacked during the night sir
attacked by whom vandals sir
vandals captain vandals barbarian hordes
that sacked and pillaged during the
waning years of the Roman Empire the
nomadic tribe that expanded eastward
during the Celtic expansion in the late
century AD enough of this nonsense on a
full report very well sir
well it appears we have several pairs of
badly soiled sandals ten walls have been
spayed painted with graffiti and the
worst news of all sir your chariot is on
cement blocks and well so the wheels are
missing Centurion
yes Marcus funny the whole legions been
egged sir egged yes apparently the
Legion was repulsive with rotten eggs
that's not funny
someone's I could have been put out the
Vandals think it's funny sir destroying
property endangering lives
I'll show them funny find those vandals
I want their heads on poles in front of
the camp for the whole empire see ha
here we are
1996 you imbecile it's 196 you forgot to
put in the other nine you sorry
somebody show me come on straight get
out get out go go
look captain those bastard vandals stole
the wheels off this chariot - here they
have the most unusual chariots indeed we
better take it back to Centurions
Celsius oh well they can't do that what
are you gonna do about it it's their
country whoa we'll contact the American
Embassy in case you haven't noticed it's
196 their Romans America hasn't even
been discovered yet well then you think
of something smartass okay I got it
we'll go down to the Roman camp I mean
if you want to catch the big game you
got to go down where the watering hole
is come on
okay stay here I got an idea
Leena yeah yeah yeah okay put these on
I'm gonna go do as the Romans do
Centurion yeah Centurion hey what
infidels the nerve to disturb some
journey back some Celsius hiya max
listen I hear yet you have a little bit
of problems keeping the old wheels on
the chariot well I got a deal for you
you see I happen to have this pew of a
chariot amp used to be owned by a little
old lady he's only drive it once a week
that's down the temple over at Babylon
now fine-looking chariot like that
normally you'd go for something like
four hundred shekels over at madman
Ramses lot but none with me I can let
you have it for no money down and of
course you'd have to trade in that
funny-looking chariot over there with no
wheels on it you do that we got a deal
use chariot sales may I despise you
chariot salesman my first wife ran off
for the use trade sale
guards arrest the sand flea
hey you know I gotta get myself a cheap
lawyer would you like us to do with him
Sir
the punishment shall be fit his low
stature first we'll have wild horses
drag him around the arena then we will
feed him to the Lions and what's left
feed to the crocodiles huh yeah right
you and what army huh huh Oh Oh Queen
Nefertiti quit now Oh widow of a bear
Rutten da doorbell couldn't take it huh
Oh a pleasant surprise my queen you know
this son of a goat unfortunate as it
seems he's my servant Achilles the heel
yes taco taco tell men I'm lining this
up like that something I want to go back
go back to Egypt you know where it's
nice and safe and you know and now I
want to be back with the pyramids that
stands so pointing in erect like a young
supple breast of a sorority pledge did
your wish but I spare this dog I can I
get back to you on that mmm-hmm yeah I
jet um just have him wash your chariot
I'm ready to go thanks thanks a lot
come your highness would you like to
partake in food and wine hmm sounds good
to me
I haven't eaten in two thousand years
hey baby
okay okay yeah you know we got Tigers in
my time to rethink its spell okay I'm
cleaning I'm cleaning nice stuff
hey what the a thousand pardon Centurion
I was mesmerized by a lucky fruit and
I'm bewitched by your beauty enchanted
and I'm mortified
kiss me max
more than a mile of course
come on Queen Nefertiti time to go time
is money
about a million bucks worth well I guess
it's true time wounds all he'll see a
man I've got a flight to catch
what let's go come on okay
and we enter 1996
again okay Nimrod make this thing off
like a roman candle ready yeah the name
of Zeus
what manner of devil tree is this so
tell me did your Centurion go off like a
roman candle - don't start with me
shithead I did what I had to to keep you
from becoming the main course for a
crocodile yeah that's a crock all right
what are you fucking goofy why is well
be oh now you've done it
what you're not this full till we're out
of time and into space well now we're
fucked
that means we're in a time warp that
means we're in danger of everything from
being hit by a meteor falling into a
black hole in space
oh man return return oh this is you Nina
where'd you go oh this is great
step into the light earth creature
oh yeah well fuck you I don't think so I
got to stop this thing and find me she's
not where the hell am i 12 years 25 25
oh great a winner if man is still alive
well I'm gonna save woman I guess I'm
gonna have to find her stop you human
rat yes your stinking paws off me you
damn filthy
I've always want to say that anytime
anywhere
missed him by that much
what's the story boy finds gorilla boy
loses girl where the hell am I going I'm
according to this I've traveled
backwards and the time again but how far
oh ok ok well this looks just as good in
a spot as any of the land and go ahead
and get my bearings now the hell is that
smell
oh my chopping absortion a planet of
bedrock
excellent
an anatomically correct human female
flesh pod
hey big green creep I can't move my arm
of course not the light you were
involuntarily consumed by was a
neutralizing beam but fear not the
effect is merely temporary great oh who
the hell are you
where the hell am I on behalf of His
Majesty space Navy I am Admiral for dork
you are a space cruiser somewhere in the
ford galaxy destination is our home
planet Zee Borg a planet your kind
called Pluto Pluto that's tiny planet
it's not the size of your planet that
counts it's how you use it how are you
doing did you rape me sadly I do not
possess the proper sexual organs
necessary to have intercourse with earth
creatures when this was revealed imagine
my disappointment oh yeah I know how you
felt it's like the time I found out that
Kermit the Frog was nothing but a big
piece of Phelps mishandle but do you
have to do that it is merely a rectal
probe I am an alien it is what we do
excellent you will be sufficient for my
experiment spare me
my theory is female humans are
essentially party organisms and will
have intercourse with the same sex of
their or similar species at will
I shall observe and what makes you think
I'm gonna cooperate this peep show you
see this device what that stupid lava
lamp until it's human this is not merely
a lamp but the uranium q-36 space
modulator it has the explosive power to
destroy the entire planet Earth
cooperate with us or it will be hurtling
toward Earth at the speed of warp factor
six okay dork give it your best shot
wise choice earth creature sure I'll go
home with you hey what the boy dork
is that you galaxy no I have a job for
you
your big static cleaner I just had a
line on an executive from Spacely
sprockets okay and this guy was gonna
put me up in a luxury penthouse on the
tropical moon of mutual galaxy no you
owe me who paid for your flesh orbs and
asteroid augmentations
okay well let's make it quick so I can
give back to your anus lounge and my
future man okay just check the victim
precisely
procede females clean each other
procede let's do a sister Barbarella I'm
sure are cute I'm going to enjoy this
yeah I think you will I think I was
yeah
god
Oh
yeah
why do i order you can system
yeah P over on my opinon make sure you
drop by
will do oh whoa - were scared the
bejeebers oh look we love fuck oh man
hey girls I'm just call me hump my name
weena this is Mookie oh yeah you look
like you like Nikki know me we know this
is Nikki yeah well I think I got it
right the first time I say to you Frank
it looks like the governor kind of party
near 32nd definitely flip the switch
it's birdsnest heritage what's up you
say that's the okay girl say tell me did
you just come around the rocker from
under it
well hunk be our new man we tired of old
ones
they never white feet when coming to
cave never put seat down on toilet rock
always hit us overhead with club where
they want to fool around
well my college anthropology class
didn't really prepare me for this but
I'm what anthropology ah that's a study
of men erect yeah well I just come on
over there and I'll show you look at
this posture lucky for you I'm a
chiropractor
oh let me help you - yeah oh oh we not
feel better
mm-hm you die makewi no way
we make Zug Zug here hit us on head okay
if you insist
give me the lizard wow what a pajamas is
this oh yeah this is boot she's friendly
little minx aren't you no we just don't
talk anymore
mmm
Oh
yeah oh yeah
yeah
are you mm-hmm oh yeah oh oh oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah that's it oh yeah
oh oh oh oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
that's so good oh oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah
oh yeah
Oh No there comes ugh and ugh they are
back from hunt OOP his first name
wouldn't happen to be ally would it no I
couldn't be you know the last time I saw
a mug like that I had a string of
numbers underneath it
uh-oh kill hug and that if I can help it
ah that's it some poison gas here girls
put on your gas masks here my little
friend see al you catching the funny
papers I gotta get out of here before
I'm serving wait a minute I gotta go
find Nina
okay the computer should have a record
of where Nina was the last time before
she disappeared okay passion departed
window in space 73 55 between the Milky
Way in the Ford galaxies okay all I have
to do is go back and go through that
window wait a minute there's a chance
that I might lose the time machine
that's your chance I'm gonna have to
take okay
the year is 73 55 ad and the correct
coordinates you know I think I'm
starting to figure out the hang of this
thing okay now engage almost there
53 55 64 bits by 7,000 well grandfather
thanks for the time machine and the
adventure here we go
73 55 in the window
hey you frog fit stole my woman you've
worse thief
greetings male earth creature it was
foolish for you to have come here
you should have abandoned the female
unit I have studied your species and I
found that man is not meant to go on
seeing the same woman forever oh you
keep saying I like what hey it is
fortunate for me you have materialized
here at this time the employer needs
slaves to mine titanium on the planet
below Pia you shall do nicely
she's right he didn't have any phases
anything is no alien bone danger Will
Robinson danger Will Robinson if the
earth creature drops the uranium q-36
space modulator all life-forms here will
be terminated listen Tao unless you want
to be a Martian jigsaw puzzle you better
send us back to earth that's Cleveland
Ohio USA 1996 and do it now affirmative
you shall return to your beloved earth
in ten seconds now return the uranium
q-36 space modulator to its rightful
owner
oh no problem here catch
oops baby we made it
Wow ah what an adventure yes some
adventure pretty damn scary if you ask
me well my series when you forget the
flush that's not funny hey this is what
I've been waiting for come on let's go
shopping and spend some of that million
you got all the time in the world
hmm I guess you're right