you
well if my grandfather jebediah Jackson
this is this place and I can't believe
it's actually been a year since gone you
know free back a lot of memories this
place gives me the creeps
don't you find it strange so the
executor of the estate sent you a letter
from your grandfather and year after he
dies that can only be opened in this
house maybe that's like a letter from
the grave spooky
I say we don't stay here I mean this
place what makes me feel like a kid
again
what do you say we go upstairs and wet
the bed ah you should see knucklehead we
make this a quick visit okay Hey there
he is my grandpa jebediah Jackson why he
was the greatest storyteller ever I mean
he could tell you about historical myths
just like he was actually there is this
him - I know no that was his grandpa
General Jeb Jackson he rode with robert
e lee with the old Virginny yeah back in
the old war you know with the southern
independence yeah why grandpa used to
tell me that he had quite a reputation
about it why would he would go on to the
battlefield the Yankees would take one
look at him and turn tail and run oh
yeah it was great
and of course after the war he was quite
an engine fighter you names would see
him shaking their moccasins mm-hmm see
the family resemblance you know it's
weird
it really ZZ Top look these guys look
exactly the same
yeah you know you're right but other
than that similarities with their looks
that's all if they had in common I mean
great grandpa why he was a great war
hero and an engine fighter in grandpa
here well he was a scientist and an
inventor what an eccentric one at that
what happened to you hey being a
chiropractor is a noble occupation why I
why I aligned may important people what
you know what they say if you're not
properly aligned don't you know but I'm
sure
tell me where your tires go bald and
your rear end shakes but enough about
that
why don't I take you to the most
important room grandpa's laboratory Wow
look at all this stuff
what was he working on I don't know I
mean he was real secretive about his
last project didn't wanted to fall in
the wrong hands
something about commie spies being
everywhere
I guess insanity is hereditary could be
too much chlorine in the gene pool there
you open that letter see here Randall if
you're reading this that it means that
your old grandpa's gone I have something
to tell you that you're gonna find hard
to understand these things are stories
that I told you when you were a kid were
not passed down I actually lived them
that's right I was the ancestor that was
in King Arthur's Court I crossed the
ocean with Columbus bought the
revolution and yes the truth is the
truth is now is also the old general an
Indian fighter your real ancestors were
nothing but bootleggers and horse
thieves
so I single-handedly had given you a
family tree that you could be proud of
what size straightjacket did you say
your grandfather wore which we shall
I've invented a time machine
a time machine yes a time machine
Einstein's theory states time is not
consistent but flexible with this
machine there is no longer any
distinction between three-dimensional
time and space I have proven that they
are fused in a four-dimensional time and
space continuum of course I just it just
makes perfectly good sense I mean that's
why I went to college I should know this
perfect sense you have heard of the
fourth dimension no now the fifth
dimension I've heard of you know the Age
of Aquarius
damn it this is serious I mean just
imagine the queue
be transported into the past or into the
future every not just incredible wait
there's more okay you'll find a time
machine hidden under a drop cloth here
in the lab okay here the instructions
use this machine wisely face dire
consequences is this proof enough this
this is your proof this only proves you
had a crackpot inventor for a
grandfather so can we go now
Oh fine if you're gonna be like that
then I just won't tell you what the rest
of the letter says oh don't tell me your
grandfather was awesome than me on the
grassy knoll that's not funny okay PS so
please find a bank statement book with
your name on it
yeah back in the 1890s I picked up a few
bags of gold nuggets in Alaska and next
thing you know Jeb's a millionaire but
with today's market the balance should
exceed 1 million dollars spend it wisely
your loving grandfather jebediah Jackson
$1.00 I knew I had a good feeling about
all this and that grandfather of yours
did I not say genius then give me that
Bank lemme see one new you clamp yes now
let's celebrate there's something about
money that makes me feel so yeah
well oh it's good what is worth about
five hundred thousand five hundred
thousand yeah that's all
Wow huh I mean it was good oh it was
more than good what that's serious blow
job no no if you're gonna want the whole
million then I I think we're gonna have
to get a little bit more creative format
start again
[Laughter]
many big joke where the hell are we oh
man hey look down the hill there's a
town what the hell year is it well
according to the annual magnetron is
1882 great 1882
well whiz kid now that you've lost the
instructions how are we gonna get out of
here that's easy all you have to do is
adjust the magnetron cowan system with
the capillary balancing out the de
laboratorio and sliding up the
discombobulated ER I mean anymore I
could figure it out well then you ought
to know well thanks for the load of
confidence hey what's that sign say um
cripple creek cripple creek hey cripple
creek 1882 hey that's the same year that
my grandfather was telling me that the
old generals in or that my grandfather's
in or vice versa anyway listen listen if
we can find my grandfather then maybe he
can help me figure out how the one
that's contraption come on let's go down
to town
sir they driver did you get the license
please off that guy come on
second-fastest know why they call this
cripple creek it's friendly town it has
a lot of lovin etnies okay see why I'm
going this trading posting give me some
western death so I can blend in with the
locals why don't you uh once you go over
the hotel over there get us a room
welcome back to you when it's safe with
a women-folk fine don't get yourself a
rope necktie
- grades aren't gonna do for you ah
barkeep give me a four fingers worth of
red wait no I might be killing someone
today so you better go all the way it's
good missing little information folks
around here don't cotton to strangers
going around asking questions if you
like harmless so shoot sorry boss what
you see yeah I'm looking for a man
my name's Lou the Bell
you mean how much fun you mean handful
of bumblebees it's alright and you can't
do that you're the deputy I want this to
be a fair fight I'll shoot them in the
back
well now I know it's course really meant
that's enough Tenderfoot
hey you walk around these boots are they
any deputy to listen this town ain't big
enough for them back Sunday that is a
correct time right oh you do that side
one looks wedding bouquet
that polecat is deputy really called
funny
and that's his brother
sheriff Chester Cogburn they're the two
best shot in this territory you're a
mighty brave man take on you see you
don't understand me I'm not exactly
gonna be in a gunfight with those two
okay and my doctor specifically told me
do not have any bullets and here this
body you stand now speaking of lying
horizontal I don't think our stranger
here wants get in a gunfight I can
understand you coming on a weird trying
to convince me not to kill him I mean
you love your brother inside right nope
but I'm used to him
where have I seen your face before right
here now
take the whiskers away let's say you're
a spitting image and general Jeff
Jackson yeah I'm looking for him know
where I can find him maybe you rode out
of here about two weeks ago he's on the
trail that renegade shine and chief
Sitting moose going up to the school
ball pass from what I understand well
thanks for the info sure you know when
it's knockers too you little bell hey
hope you find a stranger he's a fine
fella and a hell of an engine fire
Randall what's this I hear you're gonna
be in a gunfight no no that means sister
yeah
listen I got some good news though I
think I found out where my grandfather
is I'm gonna go ahead and try to find
him and meet him why don't you go ahead
and meet me by the time machine first
thing in the morning well that's just
typical of you always running away from
confrontations I do not and I don't have
to stand here and take this come on this
is the Old West
I want to see a real gunfight mister
shibori I traded it in for a Buick Hey
ah listen I got to go I got about as
much future here as a snowman
yeah Billy Strunk beat it out of town
they put on dust I don't want to blast
that burn while I leave him alone
he ain't want to brush it bills gangs
anyway he didn't look like him I sure
wouldn't have known that he was one of
Jap Jackson kids that's what he said he
won't want to jail Jeff Jackson kids
that's for sure
what would you two Cowboys know about
kids well I sure do know that when you
were kids you didn't have a dog to play
with you got a rat and you still got all
its right up into your tail
oh yeah well how would you two like to
play with my rattler got the nerve
chief go I had to tell noisy neighbors
oh you taste saying bumper Watoto one
model what that mean don't come knockin
it t be wrong
oh yes
Oh
little quail like that
hi-yah big is this the Chiefs teepee how
does white man know that well either I
was the chief that just left or some man
with the chicken for a head my name
little quick al o little tail or is it
quail or can I just call your tail well
enough of that
listen I was wondering if you could help
I'm looking for a frontiers man by the
name of Jeff Jackson I'm his grandson I
wonder if you can help me find him
little crow will tell you and trade for
kiss okay you're gonna lose out on this
deal
what a kiss
hiya chief you got my squaw city moose
angry do not like what white man does
hey if you don't like the way we do
things in this country why don't you go
back to where you came from
let me move scalp you oh hey I didn't
come here for a scalp treatment white
men talk too much
make chief heap mad no no no white man
red man's friend white man wants to be
read brothers friend and read sister to
anyway wanted to get a canoe and now
paddle you later white man speak with
forked tongue what is that supposed to
mean old Indian saying all old Indian
say it why are you insinuating that the
white man is in the red man's friend why
who was it who swindled you out of
Manhattan Island for 24 bucks why man
yeah Ana who was it who turned you into
Ward and stuck you in front of a cigar
store why man and who was it who puts
your head on a nickel and took the
nickel away slot machine why man it's
son of heat big tell face warrior
Jackson yeah
pale face Jackson killed 50 best
warriors I think we take white man's
legs time to horses and make a wish
hey sounds like you want to part my hair
all the way to my balls and I don't
think so Geronimo hey hey oh no I'm not
gonna get a hatchet job
good throat cheat that's the old pepper
Randall Randall he stuck his finger in
my plum he stuck his finger in your what
hey you must have been union with the
Village People Randall Randall are you
okay hi there's three of you yeah I'm
the one in the middle Oh have your two
friends let's get out of here what now
genius okay I got this thing off to get
out fit the reason why we can't find my
grandfather is because basically you
cannot duplicate the same time space
continuum brilliant Einstein what the
hell does that mean what that means is
is that the time machine cannot be in
the same place at the same time twice oh
well that clears it up don't worry don't
worry I got it all figured out
okay all I have to do is just punch in
1996 then hit enter then after that all
I have to do is hit the engage switch
and we're gone we're addy
let's go 1996 right
since you're in Centurion yes hello who
is it
Oh No fuck Oh who would do something
like this you fell over my new sandals
apparently we were attacked during the
night sir
attacked by whom vandals sir
vandals captain vandals barbarian hordes
that sacked and pillaged during the
waning years of the Roman Empire the
nomadic tribe that expanded eastward
during the Celtic expansion in the late
century AD enough of this nonsense I
want a full report very well sir
well it appears we have several pairs of
badly soiled sandals ten walls have been
spray-painted with graffiti and the
worst news of all sir your chariot is on
cement blocks and well so the wheels are
missing Centurion
yes Marcus funny the whole legions been
egged sir egg yes apparently the Legion
was posted with rotten eggs that's not
funny
so once I could have been put out the
Vandals think it's funny sir destroying
property endangering lives
I'll show them funny find those vandals
I want their heads on poles in front of
the camp for the whole empire to see
here we are 1996 you imbecile it's 196
you forgot to put in the other nine
somebody's coming somebody's coming get
out get out go go
look captain those bastard vandals stole
the wheels off this chariot - yeah they
have the most unusual chariots indeed we
better take it back to Centurions
Celsius well they can't do that what are
you gonna do about it it's their country
whoa we'll contact the American Embassy
in case you haven't noticed it's 196
their Romans America hasn't even been
discovered yet well then you think of
something smartass okay I got it
we'll go down to the Roman camp I mean
if you want to catch the big game you
got to go down where the watering hole
is come on
okay stay here I got an idea
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay
put these on
I'm gonna go do as the Romans do
Centurion yeah Centurion hey what
infidel is the nerve to disturb some
journey Maxim Celsius hiya max listen I
hear yet you're having a little bit of
problems keeping the old wheels on the
chariot well I got a deal for you
you see I happen to have this view of a
chariot yeah used to be owned by a
little old lady used to only drive it
once a week that's down the temple over
at Babylon now
fine-looking chariot like that normally
you'd go for something like four hundred
shekels over at madman Rameses lot but
no no with me I can let you have it for
no money down and of course you'd have
to trade in that funny-looking chariot
over there with no wheels on it you do
that we got a deal Hughes chariot sells
me are you spies your chariot salesman
my first wife ran off with a used trade
sales guards arrest the sand flea you
know I'm gonna get myself a cheap lawyer
would you like us to do with him Sir
the punishment shall be fit his low
stature first people have wild horses
drag him around arena then we will feed
him to the Lions and what's left feet of
the crocodiles Yeah right
you and what army huh Oh Queen Nefertiti
Queenie the Nile Widow a rootin tootin
couldn't take pleasant surprise my queen
you know this son of a goat unfortunate
as it seems he's my servant Achille the
heel yeah talk to Tucker don't man I'm
rhinos and stuff like that found that I
want to go back go back to Egypt you
know where it's nice and safe and you
know and now I want to be back with the
pyramids that stands so pointing in
erect like a young supple breast of a
sorority pledge
is it your wish that I spare this dog I
can get back to you on that mmm-hmm yeah
I just um just have him wash your
chariot so I'm ready to go thanks thanks
a lot come your highness would you like
to partake in food and wine
mmm sounds good to me I haven't eaten in
two thousand years hey easy guys easy
okay okay yeah you know we got Tigers of
my time to rethink its spell okay I'm
cleaning I'm cleaning nice stuff
hey what a Thousand pardons Centurion I
was mesmerized by a lusty fruit and I'm
bewitched by your beauty enchanted and
I'm mortified
kiss me max
uh no denial of course
yes
Oh
[Laughter]
come on Queen Nefertiti it's time to go
time is money about a million bucks
worth well I guess it's true time wounds
all heals see you man
I've got a flight to catch what let's go
come on okay and we enter 1996 again
okay Nimrod make this thing go off like
a roman candle ray in the name of Zeus
what manner of devil tree is this so
tell me did your Centurion go off like a
roman candle - don't start with me
shithead I did what I had to to keep you
from becoming the main course for a
crocodile yeah that's a croc all right
what are you fucking goofy huh now
you've done it
you're not this full-tilt we're out of
time and into space well now we're
fucked that means we're in a time warp I
mean for a danger of everything from
being hit by a meteor falling into a
black hole in space oh man return return
oh this is you Nina you know where'd you
go oh this is great
what the hell step into the light
earth creature oh yeah well fuck you I
don't think so I got to stop this thing
and find Nina she's not where the hell
am I
well here's 25 25 oh great
I wonder if man is still alive well I'm
gonna save woman I guess I'm gonna have
to find her
stop you human rat get your stinking
paws off me you damn filthy eh
I've always wanted to say that anytime
anywhere go go
missed him by that much
what's the same story boy finds gorilla
boy loses girl what the hell am I going
I'm according to this I've traveled
backwards and the time again but how far
oh okay okay
well this look just as good as a spot as
any of the land and go ahead and get my
bearings easy now the hell is that smell
shit I planted a bedrock
excellent
an anatomically correct human female
flesh pod hey creep my arms of course
not
the lights you were involuntarily
consumed by was a neutralizing beam but
fear not the effect is merely temporary
great am i on behalf of his majesty
space Navy I am Admiral or dork you are
a space cruiser somewhere in a ford
galaxy destination is our home planet Z
Borg a planet your kind calls pollute oh
it's not the size of your planet that
counts it's how you use it
sadly I do not possess the proper sexual
organs necessary to have intercourse
with earth creatures when this was
revealed imagine my disappointment oh
yeah I know how you felt it's like the
time I found out that Kermit the Frog
was nothing but a big piece of folks
mishandled what do you have to do that
it is merely a rectal probe I am an
alien it is what we do excellent you
will be sufficient for my experiment
spare me
my theory is female humans are
essentially party organisms and will
have intercourse with the same sex of
their or similar species at will
I shall observe and what makes you think
I'm gonna cooperate with this peep show
you see this device stupid until it
human this is not merely a lamp but the
uranium q-36 space modulator it has the
explosive power to destroy the entire
planet Earth cooperate with us or it
will be hurtling toward Earth at the
speed of warp factor six okay dork give
it your best shot
wise choice earth creature
sure go home with you hey what the boy
dork is that you Galaxy no I have a job
for you your big static Klingon
I just had a line on an executive from
Spacely sprockets okay and this guy was
gonna put me up in a luxury penthouse on
the tropical moon of mutual our galaxy
no you owe me who paid for your flesh
orbs and asteroid augmentations okay but
let's make it quick so I can give back
to your anus lounge and my future man
okay this chick the victim precisely
procede females clean each other
procede let's do it sista Barbarella
sure are cute you might enjoy this yeah
thank you
Oh
yeah
you can system yep you're over on my
planet make sure you drop by will do
whoa were scared the bejeebers oh hey
girls
just call me hunk my name we know this
is Mookie look like you know me we know
this Mookie
yeah I think I got it right the first
time I say it looks like the governor
kind of pardon near 30 seconds after
they flip the switch that's birdsnest
heritage did you just come around the
rocker from wondering will hunk be our
new man we tired of old ones they never
wipe feet when coming to cave never put
seat down on toilet rock always hit us
overhead with Club what they want to
fool around
well my college anthropology class
didn't really prepare me for this but
that's the study of men erect yeah well
I just come on over there and I'll show
you look at this posture lucky for you
I'm a chiropractor
oh let me help you kill ya oh oh we not
feel better yeah dude I'm a queen oh
wait
we make zags ugh
here hit us on head okay if you insist
give me a good lizard what APIs Janus is
this hey oh yeah
this is booty friendly little minx
aren't you you know we just don't talk
anymore
uh-huh
yeah oh yeah
yeah
Oh
oh yeah yeah oh yeah oh yeah
Oh No there comes ugh and ugh they are
back from hunt poop
his first thing wouldn't happen to be
ally would it
no you know the last time I saw a mug
like that I had a string of numbers
underneath it uh-oh kill hug and that if
I can help it
ah that's it some poison gas here girls
put on your gasps max city al you
catching the funny papers I gotta get
out of here before I'm serving wait a
minute I gotta go find Nina okay the
computer should have a record of where
Nina was the last time before she
disappeared okay passionate departed
window in space 73 55 between the Milky
Way and afford galaxies okay all I have
to do is go back and go through that
window wait a minute there's a chance
that I might lose the time machine
that's your chance I'm gonna have to
take okay the year is 73 55 ad and the
correct coordinates you know I think I'm
starting to figure out the hang of this
thing okay now engage almost there
53 people five sixty four-bit by 7,000
well grandfather thanks for the time
machine in the adventure here we go
73 55 in the window
hey you frog fit
stole my woman you were Steve readings
mail earth creature it was foolish for
you to have come here
you should have abandoned the female
unit I have studied your species and I
found that man is not meant to go on
seeing the same woman forever hey it is
fortunate for me
you have materialized here at this time
the implant needs slaves to mine
titanium on the planet fallopian
you shall do nicely she's right
danger Will Robinson danger Will
Robinson if the earth creature drops the
uranium q-36 space modulator all
life-forms here will be terminated
listen pal unless you want to be a
Martian jigsaw puzzle you better send us
back to earth that's Cleveland Ohio USA
1996 and do it now affirmative you shall
return to your beloved earth in ten
seconds now return the uranium q-36
space modulator to its rightful owner
oh no problem yeah we made it
Wow what an adventure it's some
adventure oh pretty I'm scary if you ask
me
well my series when you forget to flush
that's not funny hey this is what I've
been waiting for come on let's go
shopping and spend some of that million
I guess you're right