you
well this my grandfather jebediah
Jackson this is his place and I can't
believe it's actually been a year since
Oh God you know free back a lot of
memories place excuse me creep
I just find it strange that the executor
of the estate sent you a letter from
your grandfather a year after he died
that can only be open in his house
nevertheless the grave cookie I say we
don't stay here I mean it's what makes
me feel like a kid again well you should
we go through the weather bed all right
knucklehead we make us a quick visit
okay okay there he is
my grandpa jebediah Jackson why he was
the greatest storyteller ever I mean he
could tell you about historical bits
just like he was actually there he's the
greatest is this him - I know no that
was his grandpa general Jeff Jackson he
rode with robert e lee with old Virginny
yeah back in the old war you know with
the southern independence yeah
why grandpa used to tell me that he had
quite a reputation about why when he
would go on to the battlefield the
Yankees would take one look at him and
turn tail and run
oh yeah he was great and of course after
the war is quite an engine fighter he
names would see him and shaking their
moccasins mm-hmm see the family
resemblance
you know it's weird you feel Azizi top
looks and these guys look exactly the
same
yeah you know you're right but other
than that similarities with their looks
that's all if they had in common I mean
great grandpa why he was a great war
hero and an Injun fighter in grandpa
here well he was a scientist and an
inventor what an eccentric one at that
what happened to you hey being a
chiropractor is a noble occupation why I
why I aligned may important people
what you know what they say if you're
not properly aligned don't you know but
I'm sure you're about to tell me well
your tires go bald your rear end chicks
but enough about that tell you what why
don't I take you to the most important
room
grandpa's lavatory Wow with all its
stuff what is he working on I don't know
I mean he's real secretive about his
last project didn't want it to fall in
the wrong hand
something about commie spies being
everywhere what a good I guess I'm sandy
it's the red fairy could be too much
chlorine in the gene pool how do you
open that letter seems appalling here
Randall if you're reading this that it
means that your old grandpa's gone I
have something to tell you that you're
going to find hard to understand this
thing's our story that I told you when
you were a kid were not passed down
actually lived them that's right I was
the ancestor that was in King Arthur's
Court I crossed the ocean with Columbus
bought the revolution and yes the truth
is the truth is now is also the old
general an Indian fighter your real
ancestors were nothing but bootleggers
and horse thieves
so I single-handedly had given you a
family tree that you could be proud of
what size straightjacket did you say
your grandfather wore Risha I've
invented a time machine
a time machine yes a time machine
Einstein's theory states time is not
consistent but flexible with this
machine there is no longer any
distinction between three-dimensional
time and space I have proven that they
are fused in a four-dimensional time and
space continuum of course I just it just
makes perfectly good sense and that's
why I went to college I should move this
perfect sense you have heard of the
fourth dimension no now the fifth
dimension I've heard of you know the age
of
damnit this is serious I mean just
imagine that you could be transported
into the past or into the future I mean
not just incredible wait there's more
okay you'll find the time machine hidden
under a drop cloth here in the lab okay
here the instructions use this machine
wisely
face dire consequences Oh higher
consequences haha is this proof enough
this this is your proof this only proves
you had a crackpot in Center for a
grandfather so can we go now
Oh fine if you're gonna be like this and
I just won't tell you what the rest of
the letter says oh don't tell me your
grandfather was off of the me on the
grassy knoll that's not fun okay PA so
please find a bank statement book with
your name on it
yeah back in the 1890s I picked up a few
bags of gold nuggets in Alaska and next
thing you know we'll Jeb's a millionaire
but with today's market the balance
should exceed 1 million dollars spend it
wisely your loving grandfather check the
diet Jackson $1 I knew I had a good
feeling about all this and that
grandfather of yours
did I not say genius now give me that
bank let me see one new you clamp yes
now let's celebrate there's something
about money that makes me feel so yeah
testing
Oh
well oh it's good what is worth about
five hundred thousand I burnt down yeah
that's all well huh I mean it was good
oh he was wanted good but that's it
serious blow job
no no if you're going to want the whole
million then I I think we're going to
have to get a little bit more creative
than that start again
where's the damn water with the
inception okay ready
big joke where the hell are we oh man
hey look down the hill there's a town
well went out of there what the hell
year is it well according to the annual
magnetron is 1882 great 1882 well with
Kidd now that you've watched the
instructions how are we gonna get out of
here that's easy all you have to do is
adjust the magnetron Cohen sis with
capillary balancing out the de
laboratories and sliding up the
discombobulated er I mean anymore I
could figure it out well then you ought
to know well thanks for load of
confidence hey what's that sign say
um cripple creek cripple creek say
cripple creek 1882 hey that's the same
year that my grandfather was telling me
deputy old generals in or that my
grandfather's in or vice versa
anyway listen this if we can find my
grandfather then maybe he can help me
figure out how the run this contraption
come on let's go down to town
Oh so they driver did you get the
license plate okay come on touch the
graveyard oh this is good
this welcomes everyone cross their
second fish yeah no wonder they call his
cripple creek nice friendly town it has
a lot of love in that knee okay see what
I'm going this training person give me
questions I can blend in with the locals
why don't you once you go over the hotel
over there get us a room I'll come back
to you when it's safe with a woman's
hope fine the care if you don't get
yourself rope necktie
that's great you're gonna do way ahh
barkeep give me a four fingers worth of
Rhetta wait no I might be killing
someone today then you better go all the
way oh it's good huh little information
Oprah now you're don't cotton to
strangers going around asking questions
if you look harmless so shoot their
plus-one you see yeah I'm looking for a
man legend
I don't live it down
thank you whoa what Lou
you win how much would you win first
kisses
she is harder to him than a handful of
bumblebees thought I'll just shoot in
the back as you walk by and you can't do
that you're the deaf you I want this to
be a fair fight I'll shoot them in the
back
well now I know it's horse really meant
that's the milk Tenderfoot
hey you walk by a new boot oh then you
left it at me - oh yeah I Got News for
you I was a true lion scare no lie
listen partner this hair ain't big
enough for the bus come on you get down
back Sunday that is the correct time
right well now to dictate I'm waitin on
you do that oh you do that side one book
sweat Poquette that polecat is deputy
really cause funny
and then she's brother
sheriff Chester Kasbah
there's a two best shop in this
territory
you're a mighty brave man take on you so
you don't understand yeah I'm not
exactly going to be in a gunfight with
those two no see I'm a very dilute
threshold for death okay and my doctor
specifically told me do not have any
bullets under this body while Lou didn't
recognize you stand now speaking of
lying horizontal I don't think our
stranger here wants get in a gunfight
but I can understand you coming on oh
we're trying to convince me not to kill
him I mean you love your brother inside
right nope but I'm used to where have I
seen your face before right here now
take the whiskers away and say you're a
spitting image and general Jeff Jackson
oh he's my grandpappy yeah I'm looking
for him know where I am planning maybe
you wrote out in here about two weeks
ago
Sancho that renegade Cheyenne cheap
Sigma go on to the school ball pass from
what I understand well thanks for the
info sure you know when it's knockers -
you little bell hope you find a stranger
he's a fine fellow and a hell of an
engine fire Randall what's this I hear
you're gonna be in a gun fight no no not
mean sister
nah listen I got some good news though I
think I found out where my grandfather
is I'm gonna go ahead and try to find
him and meet him why don't you go ahead
and meet me by the time machine first
thing in the morning
that's just typical of you always
running away from confrontation I do not
and I don't have to stand here and take
this
come on this is the Old West I want to
see a real gunfight mr. shibori I
treated in for a Buick hey Brenda ah
listen I got to go I got about as much
future here as a snowman
hey it's growing C in st. Louie okay
hillbilly Strunk beat it out of town a
cloud of dust
I want to blast that barn why'd I leave
him alone here want to brush your bills
gang anyway he didn't look like him I
sure wasn't known that he was one of
Jeff Jackson kid that's what he said he
walked one in jail dead - and kids
that's for sure
uh what would you two Cowboys know about
kids well I sure do know that when
you're kids you didn't have a doll to
play with you got a rat and you still
got all right up in your tail oh yeah
well how would you two like to play with
my rattler got the nerve
ah
Oh
and
little squawk more to run keep you back
where the great chief go register noisy
neighbor so you day saying bumper Watoto
warm up what that mean don't come
knocking it to be wrong
Oh
like that
hey babe
is this the Chiefs tepee how does white
man know that well it was a cheap that
just left or some man with the chicken
for a hat my name little quail Oh
little quail tail or is it quail or can
I just call your tail well enough of
that listen I was wondering if you could
help I'm looking for a frontiers man by
the name of Jeff Jackson I'm his
grandson I wonder if you can help me
find them little crow will tell you and
trade for kiss okay
so you're going to lose out on this deal
what what a kiss huh hiya chief got my
squaw city moose
angry do not like what white man does
hey if you don't like the way we do
things in this country let's go back to
where you came from
let me move scalpel whoa hey I didn't
come here for a scalp treatment white
men talk too much
my chief heap mad not only a white man
red man's friend no white man wants to
be red brothers friend and red sister
too anyway I want to get a canoe and
I'll tell you later
white man speak with forked tongue what
is that supposed to mean old Indian
saying all old Indian saying why are you
insinuating that the white man is in the
red man's friend why who was it who
swindled you out of Manhattan Island for
24 bucks
why man yeah Anna who was it who turned
you into Ward and stuck you in front of
a cigar store my man and who was it who
put your head on a nickel and took the
nickel away slot machine why man is son
of heap big tell face warrior Jackson
yeah pale face Jackson killed 50 best
warriors I think we take white man's
legs time to horses and make a wish Hey
sounds like you want to part my hair all
the way to my ball I don't think so
Geronimo hey hey hey oh no I'm not gonna
get a had to jump
good throw chief xeo pepper Randall
Randall he stuck his finger in my plum
suck his finger in your what hi you must
have been union with the Village People
Randall Randall you okay hi there's
three of you yeah I'm the one in the
middle holding have your two friends
let's get out of here what now genius
okay I got this thing all figured out
fit the reason why we can't find my
grandfather is because basically you
cannot duplicate the same time space
continuum brilliant Einstein what the
hell does that mean what that means is
that the time machine cannot be in the
same place the same time twice oh well
that clears it up don't worry don't
worry I got it all figured out okay all
I have to do is just punch in 1996 then
hit enter then after that all I have to
do is hit the engage switch somewhere
guard
we're out of here let's go okay
1996 all right engage
you're in Centurion
yes hello who is it oh no fuck oh well
who would do something like this ah cute
it's all over my new sandals ah
apparently we were attacked during the
night sir
attacked by whom vandals sir
vandals captain vandals barbarian hordes
that sacked and pillaged during the
waning years of the Roman Empire a
nomadic tribe that expanded eastward
during the Celtic expansion in the late
century AD enough of this nonsense
on a full report very well sir well it
appears we have several pairs of badly
soiled sandals ten walls have been
spayed painted with graffiti and the
worst news of all sir your chariot is on
cement blocks and well so the wheels are
missing Centurion
yes Marcus funny the whole legions been
egged sir
egged yes sir apparently the Legion was
repulsive with rotten eggs that's not
funny
someone's I could have been put out the
Vandals think it's funny sir destroying
property endangering lives
I'll show them funny find those vandals
I want their heads on poles in front of
the camp for the whole empire see here
we are 1996 you imbecile it's 196 you
forgot to put any other 9u5 somebody
show me come on straight get out get out
go go
look captain those bastard vandals stole
the wheels off this chariot - here they
have the most unusual chariots indeed we
better take it back to Centurions
Celsius well they can't do that what are
you gonna do about it it's their country
whoa we'll contact the American Embassy
in case you haven't noticed it's 196
their Romans America hasn't even been
discovered yet well then you think of
something smartass okay I got it
we'll go down to the Roman camp I mean
if you want to catch the big game you
got to go down where the watering hole
is come on
okay stay here I got an idea
leave yeah yeah yeah okay
put these on
I'm gonna go do as the Romans do
cinterion
yeah Centurion hey what infidel is the
nerve to disturb some journey back some
Celsius hiya max listen I hear yet you
have a little bit of problems keeping
the old wheels on the chariot well I got
a deal for you
you see I happen to have this peel of a
chariot amp used to be owned by a little
old lady he's only drive it once a week
that's down the temple over at Babylon
now fine-looking chariot like that
normally you'd go for something like
four hundred shekels over at madman
Rameses lot but none with me I can let
you have it for no money down and of
course you'd have to trade in that
funny-looking chariot over there with no
wheels on it you do that we got a deal
use chariot selznick I despise you
chariot salesman my first wife run off
for to use trade salesmen
guards arrest the sand flea hey you know
I gotta get myself a cheap lawyer would
you like us to do with him Sir
the punishment shall be fit his low
stature first we will have wild horses
drag him around the arena then we will
feed him to the Lions and what's left
feed to the crocodiles huh Yeah right
you and what army huh huh Oh Oh Queen
Nefertiti quit now Oh widow of a bear
Rutten Dada fell couldn't take it huh
Oh pleasant surprise my queen you know
this son of a goat unfortunate as it
seems he's my servant Achilles the heel
yes talk to Tucker tell men I'm varmints
up like that something I want to go back
go back to Egypt you know where it's
nice and safe and you know and now I
want to be back with the pyramids that
say I'm so pointing in erect like a
young supple breast of a sorority pledge
did your wish but I spare this dog I can
I get back to you on that mm-hmm
yeah I just um just have him wash your
chariot I'm ready to go
thanks thanks a lot
come your highness would you like to
partake in food and wine hmm sounds good
to me
I haven't eaten 2,000 years hey baby
okay okay yeah you know we got Tigers in
my time to rethink its spell
okay I'm cleaning I'm cleaning nice
stuff
hey what's up a Thousand pardons
Centurion I was mesmerized by a lucky
fruit and I'm bewitched by your beauty
enchanted and I'm mortified
kiss me next
more than a mile of course
come on Queen Nefertiti time to go time
is money
about a million bucks worth well I guess
it's true time wounds all heals CMS I've
got a flight to catch
what let's go hunt okay and we enter
1996 again
okay Nimrod make this thing go up like a
roman candle ready yeah in the name of
Zeus
what manner of devil tree is this so
tell me did your Centurion go off like a
roman candle - don't start with me
shithead I did what I had to to keep you
from becoming the main course for a
crocodile yeah that's a crock all right
that's it what are you fucking goofy why
is well be huh oh now you've done it
what you're not this full till we're out
of time and into space well now we're
fucked
what that means we're in a time warp I
mean for a danger of everything from
being hit by a meteor falling into a
black hole in space
oh man return return oh this is you Lena
where'd you go oh this is great
step into the light
earth creature oh yeah well fuck you I
don't think so I gotta stop this thing
and find me she's not where the hell am
i well here is 25 25 oh great
a winner if man is still alive well I'm
gonna save woman I guess I'm gonna have
to find her stop you you been rat yes
your stinking paws off me you damn
filthy
I've always want to say that anytime
anywhere go go go
missed him by that much
what's the story boy finds gorilla boy
loses girl ax where the hell am I going
I'm according to this I travel backwards
in the time again but how far oh okay
okay well this looks just as good as a
spot hasn't even landed go ahead and get
my bearings now the hell is that smell
like chopping and sword shit I planted
in bedrock
excellent
an anatomically correct human female
flesh pod
hey big green creep I can't move my arms
of course not the light you were
involuntarily consumed by was a
neutralizing beam but fear not the
effect is merely temporary great would
hurt you where the hell am I on behalf
of His Majesty space Navy I am Admiral
or dork you are a space cruiser
somewhere in the ford galaxy destination
is our home planet z borg a planet your
kind called Pluto Pluto that's tiny
planet it's not the size of your planet
that counts it's how you use it how are
you doing did you rape me sadly I do not
possess the proper sexual organs
necessary to have intercourse with earth
creatures when this was revealed imagine
my disappointment oh yeah I know how you
felt it's like the time I found out that
Kermit the Frog is nothing but a big
piece of Phelps mishandle but do you
have to do that it is merely a rectal
probe I am an alien it is what we do
excellent you will be sufficient for my
experiment spare me my theory is female
humans are essentially party organisms
and will have intercourse with the same
sex of their or similar species at will
I shall observe and what makes you think
I'm gonna cooperate this keep show you
see this device what that stupid lava
lamp until it's human this is not merely
a lamp but the uranium q-36 space
modulator
it has the explosive power to destroy
the entire planet Earth cooperate with
us or it will be hurtling toward Earth
at the speed of warp factor six okay
dork give it your best shot
wise choice earth creature sure go home
with you
hey what the boy dork
is that you galaxy no I have a job for
you you big static cleaner I just had a
line on an executive from Spacely
sprockets okay and this guy was gonna
put me up in a luxury penthouse on the
tropical moon of meets our galaxy no you
owe me who paid for your flesh orbs and
asteroid augmentations
okay well let's make it quick so I can
get back to your anus lounge and my
future man okay
is it check the victim precisely proceed
females clean each other
proceed let's do it sister Barbarella
I'm sure are cute I'm going to enjoy
this yeah I think you will I think I was
Oh
yeah
one day i order you to system yappy over
on my opinon make sure you drop by
will do oh well those ants were scared
the bejeebers em look we love funk oh
man
hey girls so just call me hunk my name
weena
this is Mookie oh yeah you look like you
like Nicky no me weena
Dave Mickey yeah well I think I gotta
write the first thing I say ya know your
Frank Joe looks like the governor kind
of pardon near 32nd doesn't it flip the
switch that's birdsnest heritage what's
up you say that's the okay girl say tell
me did you just come around the rocker
from under it
well hunk be our new man we tired of old
one they never wipe feet when coming to
cave never put seat down on toilet rock
always hit us overhead with club where
they want to fool around
well my college anthropology class
didn't really prepare me for this but
I'm what uncle Pat thank you ah that's a
study of men erect yeah when I just come
on over there and I'll show you look at
this posture lucky for you I'm a
chiropractor
oh let me help you - yeah oh oh we not
feel better
mm-hmm you die makewi no way
we make suds ugh here here this on head
okay if you insist
give me your lizard wow what a pajamas
is this oh yeah
this is booty she's friendly little minx
aren't you and then we just don't talk
anymore
I
haha
Oh
oh yeah oh yeah
thank you
Oh
yeah
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
that's it oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah
oh yeah
Oh No there comes ugh and ugh they are
back from hunt OOP
first thing wouldn't happened to be a
lead with it
no I couldn't be you know last time I
saw a mug like that I had a string of
numbers underneath it
uh-oh kill hug no not if I can help it
ah cut it some poison gas here girls put
on your gas masks here my little friend
see ya Leo catch you in the funny papers
I gotta get out of here before I'm
serving Raymond I gotta go find Nina
okay the computer should have a record
of where Nina was the last time before
she disappeared okay pastor departed
window in space 73 55 between the Milky
Way in the ford galaxies okay all I have
to do is go back and go through that
window wait a minute there's a chance
that I might lose the time machine
that's your chance I'm gonna have to say
okay the year is 73 55 ad and the
correct coordinates you know I think I'm
starting to figure out the hang of this
thing okay now engage almost there it's
three through five 64 bits by 7,000 well
grandfather thanks for the time machine
and the adventure here we go
73 55 in the window
hey you frog fit stole my woman you've
worse thief
greetings male earth creature it was
foolish for you to have come here
you should have abandoned the female
unit I have studied your species and I
found that man is not meant to go on
seeing the same woman forever oh you can
see my necklace Hey it is fortunate for
me you have materialized here at this
time the implant needs slaves to mine
titanium on the planet below Pia you
shall do nicely she's right you didn't
have any phases anything bone danger
Will Robinson danger Will Robinson if
the earth creature drops the uranium
q-36 space modulator all life-forms here
will be terminated listen Tao unless you
want to be a Martian jigsaw puzzle you
better send us back to earth that's
Cleveland Ohio USA 1996 and do it now
affirmative you shall return to your
beloved earth in ten seconds
now return the uranium q-36 space
modulator to its rightful owner
oh no problem here catch baby we made it
wow what an adventure
it's some adventure uh preview if you
ask me
well my series when you forget to flush
that's not funny hey this is what I'm
waiting for
come on let's go shopping and spend some
of that million you got all the time and
hmm I guess you're right