well this is if my grandfather jebediah
Jackson this is this place and I can't
believe it's actually been a year since
gone you know free back a lot of
memories this place gives me the creeps
would you find it strange to the
executor of the estate sent you a letter
from your grandfather a year after he
dies that can only be open in this house
made nothing a letter from the grave
spooky I say we don't stay here I mean
this place what makes me feel like a kid
again
well you see we go upstairs and wet the
bed you should knuckle head
we make this a quick visit okay fine Hey
here he is
my grandpa jebediah Jackson why he was
the greatest storyteller ever I mean he
could tell you about historical myths
just like he was actually there is this
him - I know no not with his grandpa
General Jeb Jackson he rode with robert
e lee with the old Virginny yeah back in
the old war you know with the Saturday
independence yeah
why grandpa used to tell me that he had
quite a reputation about why when he
would go onto the battlefield the
Yankees would take one look at him and
turn tail and run oh yeah he was great
and of course after the war he was quite
an engine fighter you names would see
him shaking their moccasins mm-hmm
family resemblance
you know it's weird it really ZZ Top
look these guys look exactly the same
yeah you know you're right but other
than that similarities with their looks
that's all if they had in common I mean
great grandpa why he was a great war
hero and an Injun fighter in grandpa
here well he was a scientist and an
inventor or an eccentric one at that
what happened to you hey being a
chiropractor is a noble occupation why I
why I aligned may important people what
you know what they say if you're not
properly aligned don't you know but I'm
sure
tell me where your tires go bald and
your rear end shakes but enough about
that tell you what why don't I take you
to the most important room grandpa's
laboratory Wow look at all this stuff
what was he working on I don't know I
mean he's real secretive about his last
project didn't want it to fall in the
wrong hands
something about commie spies being
everywhere I guess in Sandhya's for rent
ferry could be too much chlorine in the
gene pool there you open that letter
sweetie here Randall if you're reading
this that it means that your old
grandpa's gone and I have something to
tell you that you're gonna find hard to
understand these things are stories that
I told you when you were a kid were not
passed down I actually lived them that's
right I was the ancestor that was in
King Arthur's Court I crossed the ocean
with Columbus bought the revolution and
yes the truth is the truth is I was also
the old general an Indian fighter your
real ancestors were nothing but
bootleggers and horse thieves
so I single-handedly had given you a
family tree that you could be proud of
what size straightjacket did you say
your grandfather wore which we shall
I've invented a time machine
a time machine yes a time machine
Einstein's theory states time is not
consistent but flexible with this
machine there is no longer any
distinction between three-dimensional
time and space I have proven that they
are fused in a four-dimensional time and
space continuum of course I just it just
makes perfectly good sense I mean that's
why I went to college I should know this
perfect sense you have heard of the
fourth dimension no now the fifth
dimension I've heard of you know the Age
of Aquarius damn it this is serious I
mean just imagine the queue
be transported into the past or into the
future I mean that's just incredible
wait there's more okay you'll find the
time machine hidden under a drop cloth
here in the lab okay here the
instructions use this machine wisely
face dire consequences haha is this
proof enough this this is your proof
this only proves you had a crackpot
inventor for a grandfather so can we go
now
Oh fine if you're gonna be like that
then I just won't tell you what the rest
of the letter says oh don't tell me
your grandfather was awesome than me on
the grassy knoll that's not funny okay
PS son please find a bank statement book
with your name on it yeah back in the
1890s I picked up a few bags of gold
nuggets in Alaska and next thing you
know Jeb's a millionaire but with
today's market the balance should exceed
1 million dollars spend it wisely your
loving grandfather jebediah Jackson $1 I
knew I had a good feeling about all this
and that grandfather of yours
did I not say genius then give me that
Bank let me see one new you clamp yes
now let's celebrate
there's something about money that makes
me feel so yeah
Oh
well oh it's good what is worth about
five hundred thousand five hundred
thousand yeah that's all
Wow huh I mean it was good oh it was
more than good but that's been serious
blow job
no no if you're gonna want the whole
million then I I think we're gonna have
to get a little bit more creative than
that start again
[Laughter]
Ramy big dope where the hell are we oh
man hey look down the hill there's a
town well what kind is it what the hell
year is it well according to the annual
magnetron is 1882 great 1882
well whiz kid now that you've lost the
instructions how are we gonna get out of
here that's easy all you have to do is
adjust the magnetron Cohen sis with the
capillary balancing out the de
laboratorio and sliding up the
discombobulated er I mean anymore I
could figure it out well then you ought
to know well thanks for the load of
confidence hey what's that sign say um
cripple creek cripple creek hey cripple
creek 1882 hey that's the same year that
my grandfather was telling me that the
old generals in or that my grandfather's
in or vice versa
anyway listen this if we can find my
grandfather then maybe he can help me
figure out how the one this contraption
come on let's go down to town
sunday driver if you get the license
plate of that guy
come on graveyard oh this is good
this welcomes everyone cross am
second-fastest yeah no wonder they call
this cripple creek it's friendly town it
has a lot of love in that news okay um
see what I'm going this trading post me
give me some western death so I can
blend in with the locals why don't you
uh once you go over the hotel over there
get us a room welcome back to you when
it's safe with a woman's home fine care
if you don't get yourself a rope necktie
that's great you're gonna do play ah
barkeep give me a four fingers worth of
Rhetta wait no I might be killing
someone today so you better go all the
way it's good
missing little information folks around
here don't cotton to strangers going
around asking questions if you look
harmless so shoot their boss what you
see yeah I'm looking for a man
my name is literally Bell thank you
doing well Lu you will how much fun you
win first kisses
it's harder than him a handful of
bumblebees it's alright I'll just shoot
in the back as he walks by and you can't
do that you're the deputy I want this to
be a fair fight I'll shoot them in the
back well now I know it's course really
meant that's enough
Tenderfoot hey you walk around these
boots are they any left n dirty - I was
a fool ain't scared nobody listen boy
this town ain't big enough for the damn
back something that is the correct time
right well so now 15 mm oh you do that
side 1 books wet poke it that polecat is
deputy really Todd funny and that's his
brother
sheriff Chester Cogburn
they're the two best shot in this
territory you're a mighty brave man take
on you see you don't understand with you
I'm not exactly gonna be in a gunfight
with those two no see I'm a very the
lower threshold for death okay and my
doctor specifically told me do not have
any bullets under this body right now
you stand now speaking of lying
horizontal I don't think our stranger
here what's get in a gunfight with me
but I can understand you coming on a
weird trying to convince me not to kill
him I mean you love your brother and
such right nope
but I'm used to where have I seen your
face before right here now
take the whiskers away let's say you're
a spitting image and general tell
Jackson yeah I'm looking for him know
where I can find him
maybe you rode out of here about two
weeks ago he's on the trail of that
renegade Cheyenne chief sidman's
going on to the school ball pass from
what I understand well thanks for the
info sure you know when it's knockers -
you little Bell hey hope you find a
stranger he's a fine fella and a hell of
an engine fire Randall what's this I
hear you're gonna be in a gun fight no
no that means sister no listen I got
some good news though I think I found
out where my grandfather is I'm gonna go
ahead and try to find him and meet him
why don't you go ahead and meet me by
the time machine first thing in the
morning well that's just typical of you
always running away from confrontations
I do not and I don't have to stand here
and take this come on this is the old
web I want to see a real gun fight with
shibori
I traded in for a Buick Hey ah listen I
got to go I got about as much future
here the snow man he's out of town put
on desk I don't want the blast that
barbed wire I'll leave him alone
he ain't want to brush it bills gangs
anyway he didn't look like him I sure
wouldn't have known that he was one of
Jeff Jackson kids and that's what he
said yeah he won't want to jail Jeff
Jackson kids that's for sure
what would you two Cowboys know about
kids well I sure do know that when you
were kids you didn't have a doll to play
with you got a rat and you still got
home it's right up into your tail oh
yeah well how would you two like to play
with my rattler that's the nerve
Oh
squawk brave chief go I have to tell
noisy neighbors oh you taste same bumper
Watoto warm up what that mean don't come
knockin it t be wrong
Oh
yeah
Oh Oh chief like
Oh
little coil like that
oh yeah babe
is this the Chiefs tepee how does white
man know that well either I was the
chief that just left or some man with
the chicken for a hat my name little
quail Oh little quail tail or is it
quail or can I just call your tail well
enough of that listen I was wondering if
you could help I'm looking for frontiers
man by the name of Jeff Jackson I'm his
grandson I wonder if you can help me
find him
little crow will tell you and trade for
kiss okay you're gonna lose out on this
deal
what what I kiss hiya chief look at my
squaw city moose angry do not like what
white man does hey if you don't like the
way we do things in this country don't
you go back to where you came from move
scalp you whoa hey I didn't come here
for a scalp treatment white men talk too
much like chief heap mad no no no no
white man red man's friend white man
wants to be read brother's friend and
read sister too anyway want to get a
canoe and now paddle you later white man
speak with forked tongue what is that
supposed to mean old Indian saying all
old Indian say it
why are you insinuating that the white
man is in the red man's friend
why who was it who swindled you out of
Manhattan Island for 24 bucks why man
yeah Anna who was it who turned you into
Ward and stuck you in front of a cigar
store my man and who was it who puts
your head on a nickel and took the
nickel away slot machine why man it's
none of heap big tell face warrior
Jackson yeah he'll face Jackson killed
50 best warriors I think we take white
men's legs time to horses and make a
wish
hey sounds like you want to part my hair
all the way to my balls
I don't think so Geronimo hey hey hey oh
no I'm not gonna get a hatchet job
good throat cheat that's the old pepper
Randall Randall he stuck his finger in
my plum he stuck his finger in your what
hey you must have Indian in with the
Village People Randall Randall are you
okay hi there's three of you yeah I'm
the one in the middle
Oh have your two friends let's get out
of here what now genius okay I got this
thing off figured out fit the reason why
we can't find my grandfather is because
basically you cannot duplicate the same
time space continuum really an Einstein
what the hell does that mean what that
means is is that the time machine cannot
be in the same place at the same time
twice oh well that clears it up don't
worry don't worry I got it all figured
out okay all I have to do is just punch
in 1996 then hit enter then after that
all I have to do is hit the engage
switch when we're gone we're outta here
let's go 1996 right engage
you're in
Centurion yes hello who is it Oh No fuck
Oh
who would do something like this shoot
and fell over my new sandals apparently
we were attacked during the night sir
attacked by whom vandal sir
vandals captain vandals barbarian hordes
that sacked and pillaged during the
waning years of the Roman Empire the
nomadic tribe that expanded eastward
during the Celtic expansion in the late
century AD enough of this nonsense
on a full report very well sir well it
appears we have several pairs of badly
soiled sandals tent walls have been
spayed painted with graffiti and the
worst news of all sir your chariot is on
cement blocks and well so the wheels are
missing
Centurion yes Marcus funny the whole
legions been egged sir egged yes
apparently the Legion was repulsive with
rotten eggs
that's not funny so once I could have
been put out the Vandals think it's
funny sir destroying property
endangering lives
I'll show them funny find those vandals
I want their heads on poles in front of
the camp for the whole empire see
ah here we are
1996 you imbecile it's 196 you forgot to
put in the other nine somebody's coming
somebody's coming get out get out go go
go
look captain those bastard vandals stole
the wheels off this chariot - yeah they
have the most unusual chariots indeed we
better take it back to Centurions
Celsius well they can't do that what are
you gonna do about it it's their country
well we'll contact the American Embassy
in case you haven't noticed it's 196
their Romans America hasn't even been
discovered yet well then you think of
something smartass okay I got it
we'll go down to the Roman camp I mean
if you want to catch the big game you
got to go down where the watering hole
is come on
okay stay here I got an idea
yeah yeah yeah yeah okay put these on
I'm gonna go do as the Romans do
Centurion yeah Centurion hey what
infidel is the nerve to disturb some
journey Maxim Celsius hiya max listen I
hear yet you're having a little bit of
problems keeping the old wheels on the
chariot well I got a deal for you you
see I happen to have this view of a
chariot yeah used to be owned by a
little old lady used to only drive it
once a week that's down the temple over
at Babylon now fine-looking chariot like
that normally you'd go for something
like four hundred shekels over at madman
Rameses lot but no no no with me I can
let you have it for no money down and of
course you'd have to trade in that
funny-looking chariot over there with no
wheels on it you do that we got a deal
Hughes chariot sells me I despise your
chariot salesman my first wife ran off
with a used trade salesman
guards arrest the sand flea hey you know
I'm gonna get myself a cheap lawyer
would you like us to do with him Sir the
punishment shall be fit his low stature
first people have wild horses drag him
around arena then we will feed him to
the Lions and what's left feet of the
crocodiles Yeah right
you and what army huh Oh Queen Nefertiti
queen denial widow a rootin tootin Dada
couldn't take it wasn't surprised my
queen
you know this son of a goat unfortunate
as it seems he's my servant
Achille the heel yeah talk to Tucker
don't man I'm violent stuff like that
found that I want to go back go back to
Egypt you know where it's nice and safe
you know and now I want to be back with
the pyramids that stands so pointy and
erect like a young supple breast of a
sorority pledge is it your wish that I
spare this dog how can I get back to you
on that mMmmm yeah I
just um just have him wash your chariot
so I'm ready to go
thanks thanks a lot
come your highness would you like to
partake in food and wine mmm sounds good
to me I haven't eaten in two thousand
years hey you guys easy okay okay yeah
you know we got Tigers of my time to
rethink its spell okay I'm cleaning I'm
cleaning nice stuff
hey what a Thousand pardons Centurion I
was mesmerised by a lusty fruit and I'm
bewitched by your beauty enchanted and
I'm mortified
kiss me max
uh load on a mile of course
yes
Oh
come on Queen Nefertiti it's time to go
time is money
about a million bucks worth well I guess
it's true time wounds all heals see you
man
I've got a flight to catch what let's go
come on okay and we enter 1996 again
okay Nimrod make this thing go off like
a roman candle ray in the name of Zeus
what manner of devil tree is this so
tell me did your Centurion go off like a
roman candle - don't start with me
shithead I did what I had to to keep you
from becoming the main course for a
crocodile yeah that's a croc all right
what are you fucking goofy ylb huh huh
now you've done it you're not this
full-tilt we're out of time and into
space well now we're fucked that means
we're in a time warp I mean for a danger
of everything from being hit by a meteor
falling into a black hole in space oh
man return return oh this is you Nina
you know where'd you go oh this is great
what the hell step into the light
earth creature oh yeah well fuck you I
don't think so I got to stop this thing
and find Nina she's not where the hell
am I
those are yours 25 25 oh great
I wonder if man is still alive well I'm
gonna save woman I guess I'm gonna have
to find her
stop you human rat get your stinking
paws off me you damn filthy
I've always wanted to say that anytime
anywhere go go
missed him by that much
what's the same story boy finds gorilla
boy loses girl
I think the hell am I going I'm
according to this I've traveled
backwards and the time again but how far
okay okay
well this looks just as good as a spot
as any of the land and go ahead and get
my bearings easy now the hell is that
smell choppin sort shit I planted a
bedrock
excellent an anatomically correct human
female flesh pod hey creep my arms of
course not
the light you were involuntarily
consumed by was a neutralizing beam but
fear not the effect is merely temporary
great am I on behalf of His Majesty's
space Navy I am Admiral or dork
you are a space cruiser somewhere in a
ford galaxy destination is our home
planet Zee Borg a planet your kind calls
Pluto it's not the size of your planet
that counts it's how you use it
sadly I do not possess the proper sexual
organs necessary to have intercourse
with earth creatures when this was
revealed imagine my disappointment oh
yeah I know how you felt it's like the
time I found out that Kermit the Frog is
nothing but a big piece of folks
mishandles but do you have to do that it
is merely a rectal probe I am an alien
it is what we do excellent
you will be sufficient for my experiment
spare me my theory is female humans are
essentially party organisms and will
have intercourse with the same sex of
their or similar species at will
I shall observe and what makes you think
I'm gonna cooperate with this peep show
you see this device oh that stupid lava
lamp Angela to human this is not merely
a lamp but the uranium q-36 space
modulator it has the explosive power to
destroy the entire planet Earth
cooperate with us or it will be hurtling
toward Earth at the speed of warp factor
six okay dork give it your best shot
wise choice earth creature
sure go home with you hey what the boy
dork
is that you galaxy no I have a job for
you you big static cling on I just had a
line on an executive from Spacely
sprockets okay and this guy was gonna
put me up in a luxury penthouse on the
tropical moon of me to our galaxy no you
owe me who paid for your flesh orbs and
asteroid augmentations
okay well let's make it quick so I can
give back to Uranus lounge and my future
man okay
is this chick the victim precisely
procede females clean each other
procede let's do it sister Barbarella
you sure are cute I'm going to enjoy
this yeah I think you will mm-hmm
Oh
[Laughter]
god
why you two system
yep you over on my planet make sure you
drop by will do oh whoa those thoughts
were scared the bejeebers enemy hey
girls
I'm just call me hunk my name weena this
is Mookie oh yeah you look like you like
Nikki know me weena this is Nikki yeah I
think I got it right the first time
all right say Frank she looks like the
governor kind of pardon near 30 seconds
after they flip the switch that's bird
nest heritage what's up say tell me did
you just come around the rocker from
under it
well hunk be our new man we tired of old
ones they never wipe feet when coming to
cave never put seat down on toilet rock
always hit us overhead with Club what
they want to fool around
well my college anthropology class
didn't really prepare me for this but
that's the study of men erect yeah well
I just come on over there and I'll show
you look at this posture lucky for you
I'm a chiropractor
let me help you kill ya oh oh we not
feel better yeah you that make we know
what
we make Zug Zug here hit us on head okay
if you insist
give me a bit lizard Wow what APIs Janus
is this hey oh yeah this is booth
friendly little minx aren't you you know
we just don't talk anymore
mmm
uh-huh
yeah oh yeah
ah
oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
that's it oh yeah
Oh No there comes ugh and ugh they are
back from hunt poop
his first thing wouldn't happen to be
ally with it now
you know the last time I saw a mug like
that I had a string of numbers
underneath it
uh-oh kill hug and that if I can help it
ah that's it some poison gas here girls
put on your gas Max City al you catch
you in the funny papers I gotta get out
of here before I'm serving a man I gotta
go find Nina okay
the computer should have a record of
where Nina was the last time before she
disappeared okay
passionate departed window in space 73
55 between the Milky Way and afford
galaxies okay all I have to do is go
back and go through that window wait a
minute there's a chance that I might
lose the time machine that's your chance
I'm gonna have to take okay the year is
73 55 ad and the correct coordinates you
know I think I'm starting to figure out
the hang of this thing okay now engage
almost there
53 55 64-bit by seven thousand well
grandfather thanks for the time machine
in the adventure here we go
73 55 in the window
hey you frog face stole my woman you
were Steve
readings mail earth creature it was
foolish for you to have come here you
should have abandoned the female unit I
have studied your species and I found
that man is not meant to go on seeing
the same woman forever
police in his case they run out of
quarters hey it is fortunate for me you
have materialized here at this time the
employer needs slaves to mine titanium
on the planet fallopian
you shall do nicely she's right he
doesn't have any phases anything danger
Will Robinson danger Will Robinson if
the earth creature drops the uranium
q-36 space modulator all life-forms here
will be terminated listen Tao unless you
want to be a Martian jigsaw puzzle you
better send us back to earth that's
Cleveland Ohio USA 1996 and do it now
affirmative you shall return to your
beloved earth in ten seconds
now return the uranium q-36 space
modulator to its rightful owner
oh no problem yeah catch baby we made it
Wow ah what an adventure it's some
adventure oh pretty damn scary if you
ask me well my series when you forget to
flush that's not funny
hey this is what I've been waiting for
come on let's go shopping and spend some
of that million you got all the time in
the world hmm I guess you're right hmm