right
Prince Charming is here at the check-in
ship
listen I'm gonna go handle table 2 and
then I'm going on break
my feet are done fell down like I got it
thanks
hi good morning Rachel so how's it going
so usual yes actually
ask it out
you just too chicken shit to do
why don't take it a while we threw away
time I had tired old diner I take his he
likes you Rachel you're right I don't
know what you like them and that should
be enough
Sylla Levi was ridiculous right morning
morning great idea on the breakfast of
my action I'm starving well full of good
ideas great ideas I was thinking um you
know if we have the individual companies
actually set up and manage their own
servers we could really get this ball
rolling on this whole merger thing and
happens ten in days instead of weeks
sorry hold that thought I want to wait
for Tony he's got some super idea to
make this merger happen quicker and I
want your thoughts on if I would have
known you were coming I uh what about
you one two there's not a date or
something uh-huh no actually uh yeah you
know you can you gonna have I know oh
because
I ate at home now why did the hell did
you come to the office with breakfast
it's because Ryan's been going to the
diner every day just to see um a
waitress there
oh the girlfriend oh yeah no we're just
friends
just friends it's the same one you've
been talking about for months my name is
Rachel hmm just friends has she married
or something sorry
go easy it's okay I'm just trying to
help the guy
it's gotta take some initiative doing a
long time without without getting any
action Hey come on Tony
it's okay sorry about that you ladies
enjoy your breakfast
I'm gonna go out and have a soda and a
smoke so is this one mine uh yes this is
yours
you know what if toys right Rachel yeah
well actually does make a valid point I
mean you do like her William well yeah I
guess I think about it almost every day
all right if you probably weren't going
to the diner every day I'm sure you'd be
upside down right now right yeah that's
that's likely I don't know I mean it
might offensive soon not a bad way to
start the day you gotta tell her how you
feel
all right people look for someone to
make me feel the way she makes you feel
right and you're taking it for granted
look was a wonderful thing for myself
yeah you're right you're right
yeah what are you waiting for go go talk
to her feels like now yeah now go talk
to her ask her out I don't know do
something pretty tonight at dinner
don't worry about it just get going go
okay well um enjoy your breakfast thank
you okay see you tonight
picking up chicks not kidding Rachel
Rachel I'm sorry Rachel just explained
it to him tomorrow I'm sorry sis I take
it that's the guy you were talking about
I don't know I should have just left
things exactly the way they were right
you had no way of knowing hey it's a
good thing you went back at least now
you know
but don't worry I promise it'll pass
them
Wow that was quite thank you I put my
foot in it yeah look right think you're
the assumption that the guy was like our
boyfriend or something yeah I mean it
could have been a relative maybe even a
friend I'm not gonna look at ask her out
now well you'll never know look right
sometimes you got to fight for the
things you really won life
I remember how difficult was to get make
his dad to accept me but I was so in
love with her that I made sure to do
anything to make that happen
what wait what do you mean was you don't
have me yeah I don't know I mean either
way I'll they decide you guys are really
good to me Ana
Thanks it's our pleasure okay yeah you
have a good night very careful I don't
that was good dinner what's after dinner
tomorrow's a new day you'll fix
everything that I hope so
if it's meant to be it'll just happen
see them I noticed we sound weird
so I don't even know him but I think I'm
in love
come here
Megan
Megan coming here I come honey you give
me a second
Megan yes honey Wow you like this and
what is all of this for well after
seeing Ryan's pain it kind of remind me
what I went through with your father
I almost miss the opportunity to be with
you I don't know who or where I'd be
without you in my life
oh my can we touch
so beautiful
Oh
oh my goodness
oh it was so good to soak yes oh yeah oh
oh yeah oh oh oh I want you in me how
are you man
oh yeah oh my goodness I get hold it
hold it honey oh oh oh yeah
Oh
oh yeah
oh-oh-oh
Oh huh
yes
just layout here
you want to camp out by the fire
Cosi
that's easy for you to say die that's
not your fault okay it's just that if I
hadn't shown up none of this would have
ever happened
I mean she's miserable now and I feel
terrible about it Oh are you like no way
of knowing you know he's right
don't worry honey it'll show up he
always does
you
and you look you look at the why don't
you just go home
the day's almost over we can handle it
I'm gonna I'm fine I'm fine I can finish
my chips go home sweetie come back fresh
tomorrow
they even know him I don't get it I
don't and you probably never will
she's in love
morning sis hey hey I can't I gotta run
are you out here actually I want to go
down to the diner see if anybody can
give me some information on that Ryan
guy what's your plan she been no plan I
just want to let the poor guy know that
I'm her brother not her boyfriend I
don't think that's such a good idea I
think it's a great idea
okay be afraid to really dig this guy
you know it makes me feel better why not
you know Rachel is there something
really good she's a good girl
seen you been shot
I love
maybe he's still hurt from the other day
I mean give it time he'll come around
hey what are you two up to Girl Talk
what are you doing here ah you know I
was thinking like a burger or shake I'm
really decided yet
enjoy I'm sick of looking at this food
I'm done I should have been out of here
hours ago
go home get some rest we can do it all
again tomorrow
laters this
Oh sober isn't a shake right oh uh uh
well you know what why not
how do you think I want to get this
robbery and banana milkshake and the
Angus and bacon cheeseburger and
anything else
water
then why did you because I wanted us to
grow you know I wanted to become closer
as a couple ain't know how I was gonna
work out with your sister staying with
this and then your brothers summer visit
but the truth is like the whole family
together experience I love you know I
will never stop finding reasons to love
you all right here we go
the you to Illinois yeah
I'm going to have this salmon
look I mean I know it wasn't all my
fault but I also know that I wasn't part
of the solution and if you're not part
of the solution then you're part of the
problem well I mean I don't see where I
was part of the solution I feel somewhat
responsible too I just stood there let's
fix it what let's get them together
and then do you have any info on him not
really no
come here come on come on aah my god
Sammy you must be out of your mind
really sounds like Thomas went through a
lot
Shelley it was so wonderful oh I'm so
happy for you you really deserve it
oh my god I'm getting married I know
it's so crazy babe
so guess who got engaged
um Thomas and Samantha huh you know how
do you know you're just excitedly loud
Maebh up sure the neighbors know Thomas
just proposed
hey Samantha
it sounds like congratulations are in
order
so congrats when's the big day yeah I
will hopefully soon yeah of course I'll
tell her okay
okay bye oh wait why did you hang up
well Thomas was calling her but she had
to go but she says you're on for noon
tomorrow
okay okay so get this okay so Thomas
takes her to Olivia's and then he's
got it his last name is Evans it's a
business credit card he works for do
fund investments well we need an address
working on it
Samantha coming oh there this is our
night I celebrate
it's the most important woman in my
whole life
Samantha you mean more to me than
anything that I would ever know your
love has shown me how to enjoy life and
you make me the man that I am today and
more I'm so lucky I found you I love you
I was so sweet babe my husband-to-be
yeah to my wife-to-be
yeah
I'll take care of you the wrist
Oh
yes
yeah
you
if this is an urgent business matter I
can have someone else help you no it's
fine now we just need to get a hold of
Ryan okay as soon as I have a free
moment I will call him myself and pass
him your number before we go do you know
what time we should expect Brian he's
gone he was here on a six-month business
assignment that ended a few days ago are
you sure you don't want me to get
someone else to help you it when I
looked up it was Thomas he was wearing
one of the waiters outfit he reached out
for my hand oh my god night I was so
breathless he gets down on his knees and
he looks up at me and he says well
you're married I didn't know what to do
I never saw it coming hello mrs.
Henderson to be Wow
Singh must have cost a fortune no not
really
it wasn't too expensive Thomas has an
uncle who owns a jewelry Mart and he
gets huge discounts well that is really
nice you know when you decide to pop the
question Roger you should give the
Thomas a call he'll call his uncle for
you well if I decided to go that route
I'll give him a call all right I gotta
go I have a bunch of stuff that I had to
do before 5:00 bye
make sure to tell Thomas I said Congrats
here's something on Ryan look Oh perfect
why are you two going through my stuff
sorry well can you be more clear you're
about what you're not saying anything
look it just means I don't know if
marriage is right for me
see that's all you have to say well I
didn't think you'd want to hear it you
know especially after your friend tells
you her proposal story no no honey
you've been nothing but honest to me
about how you feel about marriage and
that's tough enough but why you felt the
need to tell my friends Mantha is beyond
me
that's why I was upset she's my best
friend
do you imagine how that makes me feel
Shelly I battle with this every day but
when she fired off that when you're
ready jab I just I fired back and I
didn't think about how would make you
feel I'm sorry
do you love me
surely there's no one else I want to be
about I will always be by your side I'll
never leave you
yeah so this is my first blind date your
first look Alice loved playing cupid and
once you say yes she'll have you going
on a blind here today I really I really
couldn't say no I know no offense to you
I didn't I didn't mean to funny
she's my boss you know and I learned not
to say no to your boss good especially
if she's a woman I know you care about
me
I don't doubt that but are you in love
with me
so I'm 32 years old and I have no idea
how to answer that I don't even know how
love feels I mean how does someone
decide if they're in love
or not if I don't even know what it
feels like
well to me love is what you make it it
can be defined in so many ways it can be
how you feel about a person or or how a
person makes you feel or both and that's
how you define love Roger
I was ever explained it to him that way
kind of makes sense
so you're saying love is something
that's a little different for everyone
exactly it's what you make it
no one ever made me feel the way you do
and I've never felt this strongly about
anyone before I guess I've been looking
for directions to a place oh yeah what's
so funny
no Roger it's not funny
I just never made sense to me how you
never say you love me and yet you act
like a person in love well you're you
mean the world to me Shelly there's no
one I want to be with yeah what I feel
about you gotta be love I love you
Shelly and I love you Roger
Oh
then he spoke to you
oh my god
Oh
inside of me
yeah
Oh
good night good night David
but at this point I think it's best I'm
sorry that I never took her many
opportunities to tell you that I adore
you I kept telling myself to wait for
the perfect opportunity to tell you and
while waiting I fell in love with you
now appears that the opportunity is gone
something beat me to it
I can't begin to tell you how many times
you're pretty smart made my day so
wonderful
you truly are the good and my good
morning
I wish you only the best and I hope that
you're happy if you'd like to keep in
touch or you know when you just need a
friend
my email is Ryan the guy from the diner
I've always there's really nothing you
guys could have done well we certainly
didn't help matters any my surprise
visit made things worse like I know you
two mean well but things do happen for a
reason that's the reason we're here I
mean hopefully it'll just call soon in
that way we can just get this whole
thing sorted out oh I love you guys the
feeling is mutual and two months later
we split up and got a divorce
well what is here is really
go ahead that's not what was was
revealing were you then look I didn't
think I needed a reason although there
were plenty of them
I learned to go with my gut feeling and
if it don't fit don't force it if I
definitely force that one look if it
feels right go with me just follow your
heart it'll take out all the guesswork
no no no no look I told you mine now I
want to hear yours thank you I got
sneaky I was put it out mine's not even
like even close to as serious as yours
this is go Rachel
it's never
ever worked up the nerve teller
I let that devil situation is crazy
do tell I like crazy
all right that's silly
okay about six months ago I was
relocated to LA for help uh one of our
payer corporations with a merger down
the street from work there was a little
diner going there like every day to see
Rachel that's right
it's not every day you run into someone
that makes you feel wonderful
these are rare moments and in special
people there's only a few moments in a
lifetime where you meet that special
someone and if you let those moments go
by they're gone forever so don't take it
for granted I just felt like a time
would come when it would be perfect for
me to move forward and then I held out
for another perfect time and then
another and another sweetie now you know
there's no such thing the perfect time
is whatever you make it what do I do now
and too late
act on your moment now
well I should have seen this coming
- you're perfect for each other mm-hmm
where you headed off to um after work
pick up
whoa
Oh
you can't say you tried when you never
even took a chance I mean you just dated
your sake little bubble this whole time
so you wouldn't get hurt
coward rejection is all part of the
adventure and taking the chance we to
consider it you might be rejected
I let the love of my life being in love
yeah yeah oh it doesn't sound silly now
look some people you know they fall in
love with someone's physical appearance
and some people fall in love with a
person whose heart mine didn't somebody
vote
you're all heart mine kind of guy and I
really like that shows you got substance
not so funny I'm on a date with a girl
who's helping me understand how I
screwed up with another girl humble
would you like another glass of wine
actually have people already don't work
what
oh I the food you men are so dead
sometimes
what what do you think I'm explaining
your situation to you to fix it yes
thank you exactly not speaking figuring
of damn with me
now go get her she's yeah what about you
what about it now you're a really nice
guy Ryan and you're extremely attractive
and I can tell we have a lot of fun
times together but you're clearly in
love with someone else and I'm not
getting in the way of that I don't think
I could even if I tried you're in love
a go-getter well you are amazing if
you're amazing okay what do you eat here
oh yeah seriously
run before I come to my senses my way
I'm Rachel she's a waitress here you
just missed her you might catch her
right there yeah Rachel Rachel white
oh my god Rachel okay what are you doing
here I I'm I'm on my way to San Cisco
looking for a Ryan guy from the diner
found me
look it's
of a
I'm gonna love you since the moment I
laid eyes
these English
Oh
baby only
is officially out now
you