and timing is here second chip listen I
may or may not be able to and then I'm
going on break
my feet are done so now I got it thanks
Hey good morning Rachel so how's it
going now easy yes actually
ask in our home
you just to chicken shit
why don't you get a wall way through
overtime I told Simon I think he likes
you know Rachel you're right I don't
know what you like them and that should
be enough
silly guy shot at me ridiculous right
sounds good conversation morning morning
great idea on the breakfast in my action
I'm starving
well full of good ideas speaking ideas I
was thinking um you know if we have the
individual companies actually set up and
manage their own servers we could really
get this ball rolling and this whole
merger thing and have this ten in days
instead of weeks sorry hold that thought
I want to wait for Tony he's got some
super idea to make this merger happen
quicker and I want your thoughts on
together if I would have known you were
coming I uh what about you one two
there's not a date or something
uh-huh no actually uh yeah you know you
can you get mine you know
oh because
I eat at home now why did the hell did
you come to the office with breakfast
it's because Ryan's been going to the
diner every day just to see um a
waitress there oh the girlfriend oh yeah
no we're just friends just friends it's
the same one you've been talking about
for months my name is Rachel hmm just
friends is she married or something
go easy okay I'm just trying to help the
guy he's got to take some initiative
doing a long time without without
getting any action Hey come on Tony
it's okay sorry about that you ladies
enjoy your breakfast I'm gonna go out
and have a soda and a smoke so is this
one mine uh yes this is yours
you know what if one choice right
well Rachel yeah well actually does make
a valid point I mean you do like her
tell you well yeah I guess the thing
about it almost every day
all right if you probably weren't going
to the diner every day I'm sure you'd be
upside down right now right yeah that's
that's likely I don't know I mean it
might offensive soon not a bad way to
start the day
you gotta tell her how you feel all
right
people look for someone to make me feel
the way she makes you feel right and
you're taking it for granted look was it
a wonderful thing for myself yeah you're
right you're right
yeah I won't what are you waiting for go
go talk to her right now
yeah not now go talk to her ask her out
I don't know do something what about the
meeting pretty tonight at dinner
don't worry about it just get going go
okay um well um enjoy your breakfast
thank you okay see you tonight
no checks not kidding I'm sorry Rachel
just explain it to him tomorrow
I'm sorry sis I take it that's the guy
you were talking about
I don't know I should have just left
things exactly the way they were right
you had no way of knowing hey it's a
good thing you went back at least now
you know
present you like this
don't worry I promise it'll pass them
Wow that was quite dinner thank you look
right think you're of the assumption
that the guy was like our boyfriend or
something yeah I mean it could have been
a relative maybe even a friend yeah well
I'm not gonna I'm gonna ask her out now
only I'll never know
look Ryan sometimes you gotta fight for
the things you really won life how
difficult was to get Magus dad to accept
me but I was so alone with know that I
made sure to do anything to make that
happen
what yeah I don't know I mean either way
I'll be decide you guys are really good
to me Anna Thanks it's my pleasure
okay yeah well you have good night
careful I don't
that was a good dinner what's after
dinner tomorrow's a new day you'll fix
everything then I hope so if it's meant
to be it'll just happen see them
analysts we sound weird so I don't even
know him but I think I would love says
come here
Megan
Megan coming here I come honey give me a
second
Megan yes honey
Wow
you like this and what if all of this
for what I've seen Ryan's pain it kind
of reminded me what I went through with
your father
I almost miss the opportunity to be with
you I don't know who or where I'd be
without you in my life
mmm
oh my can we touch
perhaps
so beautiful
Oh
you go down oh my goodness
oh yeah
oh yeah me down
yes oh yeah oh oh I want you in me I
want you in me
oh yeah oh yeah as yours honey
as yours oh oh oh my goodness honey I
can't hold it I can't hold it honey
oh yeah yeah
Oh Oh
Oh
I love when you do that oh yeah children
just like desert yeah only good news he
is you Jim
oh-oh-oh-oh
Oh
yes
let's not go to the bedroom I just lay
out here you want to camp out by the
fire
it's cozy
that's easy for you to say die then it's
not your fault it's just that if I
hadn't shown up none of this would have
ever happened
I mean she's miserable now and I feel
terrible about it
oh you ignore him knowing you know he's
right
don't worry honey it'll show up he
always does
and you look you look at the why don't
you just go home the day's almost over
we can handle it I'm gonna I'm fine I'm
fine I can finish my chips go home
sweetie come back fresh tomorrow
they even know him I don't get it I
don't and you probably never will she's
in love
what is this hey thanks I can't I gotta
run yeah I should go down to the
diameter see if anybody can give me some
information on that Ryan guy what's your
plants you been no plan I just want to
let the poor guy know that I'm her
brother not her boyfriend I don't think
that's such a good idea I think it's a
great idea
okay Rachel really dig this guy it makes
me feel better why not you know Rachel
deserve something really good she's a
good girl
senior shot
I love you
maybe he's still hurt from the other day
I mean give it time he'll come around
hey what are you two up to Hey Girl Talk
what are you doing here
you know I was thinking like a burger or
shake I've really decided yet
enjoy I'm sick of looking at this food
I'm done I should have been out of here
hours ago
go home get some rest we can do it all
again tomorrow that is this
oh so there isn't a shake right well you
know what why not how do you think I
want to get this robbery and banana
milkshake and the Angus and bacon
cheeseburger anything else
water
why don't you because I want us to go
you know I want to spend closer as a
couple I know how is gonna work out with
your sisters staying with us and then
your employer's summer visit but the
truth is like the whole family together
experience I love you know all right
here we go
the u2 rated or
look I mean I know it wasn't all my
fault but I also know that I wasn't part
of the solution and if you're not part
of the solution then you're part of the
problem well I mean I don't see where I
was part of the solution I feel somewhat
responsible too I just stood there let's
fix it
what let's get them together
and then do you have any info on it not
really no
my god bear me you must be out of your
mind really sounds like Thomas went
through a lot
Shelley it was so wonderful oh I'm so
happy for you
you really deserve it oh my god yeah I
know it's so crazy
babe so guess who got engaged
um Thomas and Samantha huh
you know how do you know you're just
excitedly loud maybe up sure the
neighbors know Thomas just proposed
hey Samantha
it sounds like congratulations are in
order
so congrats when's the big day
yeah well hopefully soon yeah of course
I'll tell her okay
okay bye oh wait why did you hang up
well Thomas was calling her but she had
to go but she says you're on for noon
tomorrow okay okay so get this okay
so Thomas takes her to Olivia's and then
got it his last name is Evans it's a
business credit card he works for do
fund investments well we need an address
I'm working on it
Samantha come on ah there this is our
night okay so baby
the most important moment in my whole
life
cement that you mean to me than anything
that I've ever known your love has shown
me how to enjoy life and you make me the
man that I am today and more I'm so
lucky I found you I love you
so sweet man my husband-to-be to my
wife-to-be
yeah
take care of you the wrist
Oh
yeah
if this is an urgent business matter I
can have someone else help you no it's
fine now we just need to get ahold Orien
okay as soon as I have a free moment I
will call him myself and pass him your
number
oh um before we go do you know what time
we should expect Brian he's gone he was
here on a six-month business assignment
that ended a few days ago are you sure
you don't want me to get someone else to
help you
and when I looked up it was Thomas he
was wearing one of the waiters outfit he
reached out for my hand oh my god the
night I was so breathless he gets down
on his knees and he looks up at me and
he says well you're very I didn't know
what to do I never saw it coming okay
hello mrs. Henderson to be Wow thing
must have cost a fortune
no not really it wasn't too expensive
Thomas has an uncle who owns a jewelry
Mart and he gets huge discounts well
that is really nice you know when you
decide to pop the question Roger you
should give the Thomas a call a hill
cause uncle for you well if I decided to
go that route I'll give him a call all
right
I gotta go I have a bunch of stuff that
I have to do before 5:00 bye
make sure to tell Thomas I said Congrats
here's something I'm Ryan look Oh
perfect
why are you two going through my stuff
sorry well can you be more clear you're
about what you're not saying anything
look it just means I don't know if
marriage is right for me see that's all
you have to say well I didn't think
you'd want to hear it you know
especially after your friend tells you
her proposal story no no honey you've
been nothing but honest to me about how
you feel about marriage and that's tough
enough but why you felt the need to tell
my friend Samantha is beyond me that's
why I was upset she's my best friend you
imagine how that makes me feel Shelly I
battle with this every day but when she
fired off that when you're ready jab I
just I fired back and I didn't think
about how would make you feel I'm sorry
do you love me
surely there's no one else I want to be
a bit I will always be by your side I'll
never leave you don't know
yeah so this is my first blind date yes
first look I was loved playing cupid and
once you say yes she'll have you going
on a blind date today I really I really
couldn't say no I mean no offense to you
I didn't I didn't mean to suhara me
she's my boss you know and I learned not
to say no to your boss especially if
she's a woman I know you care about me I
don't doubt that but are you in love
with me
so I'm 32 years old and I have no idea
how to answer that I don't even know how
love feels I mean how does someone
decide if they're in love
or not if I don't even know what it
feels like
well to me love is what you make it
they can be defined in so many ways it
can be how you feel about a person or or
how a person makes you feel or both and
that's how you define love Roger
I was ever explained it to him that way
kind of make sense
so you're saying love is something
that's a little different for everyone
exactly it's what you make it I no one
ever made me feel the way you do and
I've never felt this strongly about
anyone before I guess I've been looking
for directions to a place yeah what's so
funny
no Roger it's not funny
I just never made sense to me how you
never say you love me and yet you act
like a person in love well you're you
mean the world to me Shelly there's no
one I want to be with I mean you what I
feel about you gotta be loved I love you
Shelly
and I love you Roger
Oh
okay
good night good night David
has to be in the form of the lighter but
at this point I think it's best I'm
sorry that I never took her many
opportunities to tell you that I adore
you I kept telling myself to wait for
the perfect opportunity to tell you and
well waiting I fell in love with you it
now appears that the opportunity is gone
someone beat me to it
I can't begin to tell you how many times
you're pretty smart made my day so
wonderful
you truly are the good and my good
morning I wish you only the best and I
hope that you're happy if you'd like to
keep in touch or you know you just need
to friend
my email is Ryan the guy from the diner
at gmail I love always there's really
nothing you guys could have done well we
certainly didn't help matters any my
surprise visit made things worse
look I know you two mean well but things
do happen for a reason nice things and
we're here I mean hopefully it'll just
call soon that way we can just get this
whole thing sorted out oh I love you
guys
the feeling was mutual and two months
later we split up and we got a divorce
well what is here is really
go ahead no I was like what was was
revealing reason oh I didn't think I
needed a reason although there are
plenty of them I learn to go with my gut
feeling and if it don't fit don't force
it but definitely force that one look if
it will say going just follow her heart
let's hear that all the guesswork
no no no no look I told you mine now I
want to hear yours okay I got that
sneaky I was absorbing it out with my
son even like even close to as serious
as yours
this is girl Rachel
it's never
never worked up the nerve teller
I remember that little situation is
crazy
do tell I like crazy
all right that's so lame
okay about six months ago I was
relocated by la foret de la one of our
payer corporations with a merger on the
street from work there was a little
diner I'll go and I liked every day to
see Rachel that's right
it's not every day you run into someone
that makes you feel wonderful
these are rare moments and in special
people there's only a few moments in a
lifetime where you meet that special
someone and if you let those moments go
by they're gone forever so don't take it
for granted I just felt like it Thailand
come when it would be perfect for me to
move forward and then I held out for
another perfect time and then another
and another sweetie now you know there's
no such thing the perfect time is
whatever you make it what do I do now
and too late
act on your moment now
well I should have seen this coming -
you're perfect for each other
mm-hmm where you headed off to um after
work
pick up
okay
Oh
[Laughter]
you can't say you tried when you never
even took a chance I mean you just date
your safe little bubble this whole time
so you wouldn't get hurt I was brave
coward
look rejection is all part of the
adventure and taking a chance which you
consider might be rejected
I let the love of my life support
for being in love yeah totally
what a love yeah
oh it doesn't sound silly now look some
people you know they fall in love with
someone's physical appearance and some
people fall in love with a person whose
heart mine didn't somebody boat you're
all heart my kind of guy and I really
like that
she's got substance what's so funny I'm
on a date with a girl who's on helping
me understand how I screwed up with
another girl hummable would you like
another glass of wine
actually I'm people ready don't worry
order what
there are the food you men are so dead
sometimes
what what do you think I'm explaining
your situation to you to fix it yes
thank you exactly not speak of figuring
out dinner with me now go get her yeah
what about you what about it now you're
a really nice guy Ryan and you're
extremely attractive and I can tell we
have a lot of fun times together but
you're clearly in love with someone else
and I'm not getting in the way of that I
don't think I could even if I tried
you're in love
a go-getter well you are amazing if
you're amazing okay
Oh seriously but why come to make that
this boy
I'm Rachel she's a waitress here you
just missed her
you might catch her just like that but
yeah Rachel Rachel what
oh my god Rachel okay what are you doing
here I I'm I'm I'm Elina and services go
looking for the right guy from the diner
Oh me
look bitch
other
love useless
iliza
visitors
hmm
maybe I can't
Oh
[Laughter]
is officially our but now
you