with it
I'm gonna be able to and I'm going on
break my feeders done
showdown
good morning Rachel
the
Oh
industry chickenshit
she likes you you're right I don't know
what you like them and that should be
enough
Sylla Levi was people thought that he
ridiculous right sounds good good
conversation morning that anyway morning
Marmot great idea on the breakfast in my
action I'm sorry
well well a good idea I'm great that
want to hear some ideas I was thinking
um you know if we have the individual
companies actually set up and manage
their own servers we could really get
this ball rolling this whole merger
thing and have this done in days instead
of weeks sorry hold that thought I'm
gonna wait for Tony he's got some super
idea to make this merger happen quicker
and I want your thoughts on the matter
oh there is born it one race if I would
have known you were coming I what about
you one two there's not a date or
something
oh no actually uh here you can you get
mine no one oh because
at home now why did the hell did you
come to the office with breakfast it's
because Ryan's been going to the diner
every day just the waitress there oh the
girlfriend I don't know we're just
friends just friends it's the same one
you've been talking about for months my
name is Rachel hmm just friends
is she married or something sorry go
easy it's okay I'm just trying to help
the guy he's got to take some initiative
doing a long time without without
getting any action hey come on Tony
it's okay sorry about that you ladies
enjoy your breakfast I'm gonna go out
and have a soda and a smoke I'll be back
in ten minutes so is this one mine yes
this is yours
pineapple hot sauce interested yep what
if I move toys right well Rachel
yeah well actually does make a valid
point I mean you do like a million well
yeah I guess I mean I think about almost
every day all right
if you're probably weren't going to the
diner every day I'm sure you'd be upside
down right now right yes that's likely I
know I mean it might affect it so not a
bad way to start the day you gotta tell
her how you feel all right people look
for someone to make me feel the way she
makes you people right and you're taking
it for granted
look what was this a wonderful thing for
Miss out
yeah you're right you're right
yeah come on good what are you waiting
for go go talk to her right now yeah now
go talk to her ask her out I don't know
do something what about the meeting a
pretty piece tonight at dinner
don't worry about it just get going
doesn't go so okay I'm Wow um enjoy your
breakfast I will thank you okay see you
tonight yeah
I'm sorry Rachel just explain it to him
tomorrow I'm sorry sis I take it that's
the guy you were talking about
all right noises what things exactly the
way they were Brian had no way of
knowing hey it's a good thing you went
back at least now you know
don't worry promise it'll pass them
it'll pass
Wow that was quite thank you look right
to carry the assumption that the guy was
like our boyfriend or something yeah I
mean it could have been a relative maybe
even a friend I'm not gonna ask her out
now oh you'll never know
look Brian sometimes you gotta fight for
the things you really won life I really
how difficult was to get make his dad to
accept me but I was so in love with her
that I made sure to do anything to make
that happen
what yeah I don't know I mean either way
I'll decide you guys are really good to
me you know Thanks it's our pleasure
put your jacket on it is cold very much
is cold all right I almost forgot
yeah oh well you have a good night very
careful
that was a good dinner what's after
dinner tomorrow's a new day you'll fix
everything that I hope so
if it's meant to be it will just happen
see them I noticed we sound weird so I
don't even know him
but I think I'm in love says come here
Megan
Megan coming here I come honey give me a
second
yes Wow
you like this and what is all of this
for well I've seen Ryan's pain it kind
of remind me what I went through with
your father I almost missed opportunity
to be with you I know who or where I'd
be without you in my life
you
can we
see
so beautiful
oh honey
rinse water
biani people dance me
oh my goodness
Oh
lay me down
yes huh
oh yeah I want you in me how are you oh
yeah oh oh yeah that's yours honey oh oh
oh my goodness honey again hold it hold
it honey
oh my goodness
Oh
French Open to sleep Tessa yeah oh yeah
- oh yeah
Oh
Oh oh yeah Oh weakness yeah oh yeah yeah
oh don't you still don't you dare 700 oh
my goodness
oh yeah
to play out here you want to camp out by
the fire
it's cozy
you
that's easy for you to say so that's not
your fault it's just that if I hadn't
shown up none of this would have ever
happened
I mean she's miserable now and I feel
terrible die you ignore him knowing you
know he's right
don't worry honey he'll show up he
always does
I'm your new up seat why don't you just
go home
the day's almost over we can handle it
I'm I'm fine I'm fine I can finish my
chip go home sweetie come back fresh
tomorrow
some does even know him I don't get it I
don't and you probably never will
she's a must
I can't run yeah I'm gonna go down to
the diner see if anybody can give me
some information on that Ryan guy what's
your plan she's been no plan I just want
what the point I know that I'm her
brother not her boyfriend I don't think
that's such a good idea
I think it's a great idea okay
virtually to date this guy you know
makes me feel better why not you know
chances are some really good girl
I love you
maybe he's still hurt from the other day
I mean give it time he'll come around
hey we need you up to fuck what are you
doing here no I was thinking that like a
burger or shake I really decided yet
enjoy I'm sick of looking at this food
I'm done I should have been out of here
hours ago
go home get some rest we can do it all
again tomorrow
there's this
oh so very shake grace well you know
what why not
that was easy I want to get this robbery
in banana milkshake and the Angus and
bacon cheeseburger and anything else
water
yeah because I want us to grow you know
I want to go closer as a couple I know
how it's gonna work out with your sister
staying with us and then your father's
summer visit but the truth is like the
whole family together experience I'll
let you know all right here we go you
too
you
look I mean I know it wasn't all my
fault but I also know that I wasn't part
of the solution and if you're not part
of the solution then you're part of the
problem well I mean I don't see where as
part of the solution I feel somewhat
responsible too
I just stood there
let's fix it what let's get them
together
and then do you have any info haunted
not really no
come on
ah my god
Jeremy you must be out of your mind
really sounds like Thomas went through a
lot
Shelley it was so wonderful oh I'm so
happy for you you really deserve it
oh my god I know so crazy Hey
so guess who got engaged Thomas and
Samantha huh
you know how do you know you're just
excitedly loud maybe up sure the
neighbors known Thomas Jeff proposed
except hey Samantha
sounds like congratulations are in order
so Congrats when's the big day
yeah well hopefully soon yeah of course
I'll tell her okay
okay bye oh wait why did you hang up
well Thomas was calling her and she had
to go but she says you're on for noon
tomorrow
okay hope you forget this so Thomas
takes her to Olivia's and then
got it his last name is Evan it's a
business credit card he works for do
found investments well we need an
address I'm working on it
Samantha
the most important moment in my whole
life Samantha you means to me than
anything that I've ever known
your love has shown me how to enjoy life
and you made me the man that I am today
and more so like I thought you I love
you
hateful my husband to be my wife to be
yes
I'll take care of you the rest
Oh
Hey
good
Oh
you
yeah
Oh
you
if this is an urgent business matter I
can have someone else help you you know
it's fine now we just need to get ahold
Orien okay as soon as I have a free
moment I will call him myself and pass
him your number
thank you so much you really appreciate
oh um before we go do you know what time
we should expect Brian he's gone he was
here on a six-month business assignment
that ended a few days ago are you sure
you don't want me to get someone else to
help you
and when I was up it was Thomas he was
wearing one of the waiters outfit he
reached out for my hand oh my god right
I was so Restless he gets down on his
knees and he looks up at me and he says
well you're very love it I didn't know
what to do I never saw it coming okay
hello mrs. Henderson to be Wow stingless
of custom fortune no I'm not worried it
wasn't too expensive Thomas has an
alcohol who owns a jewelry Mart and he
gets huge discount well that is really
nice you know when you decide to pop the
question Roger
you should give Thomas a koala he'll
cause uncle for you well if I decide to
go that route I'll give him a call all
right I gotta go have a bunch of stuff
that I have to do before 5:00 5:00
make sure to tell Thomas I said Congrats
here's something I'm Ryan look Oh
perfect
why are you two going through my stuff
sorry
well can you be more clear you're about
what you're not saying anything
look it just means I don't know if
marriage is right for me see that's all
you have to say well I didn't think
you'd want to hear it
you know especially after your friend
tells you her proposal story no no honey
you've been nothing but honest to me
about how you feel about marriage
and that's tough enough but why you
thought the need to tell my friends
Meadows beyond me that's why I was upset
she's my best friend can you imagine how
that makes me feel Shelly I battle with
this every day but when she fired off
that when you're ready jab I just I
fired back and I didn't think about how
would make you feel I'm sorry
do you love me
chilli there's no one else I want to be
a mess I will always be by your side
I'll never leave
yeah my first blind date yes first what
I was a love playing cupid and once you
say it
she'll have you going on a blind you
today I really I really couldn't say no
I don't know him - I didn't I didn't
mean to put already she's my boss you
know and I learned not to say no to your
boss especially she's a woman
I know you care about me I don't doubt
that but are you in love with me sorry
I'm 32 years old and I have no idea how
to answer that I don't even know how
love feels I mean how does someone
decide if they're in love or not if I
don't even know what it feels like
well to me love is what you make it it
can be defined in so many ways it can be
how you feel about a person or or how a
person makes you feel or both that's how
you define love Roger
I was ever explained it to him that way
can make sense
so the same love is funding a little
different for everyone
exactly it's what you make it no one's
ever made me feel the way you do and
I've never felt this strongly about
anyone before I guess I've been looking
for directions to a place I learn yeah
what's so funny
no Roger it's not funny
I just never made sense to me how you
never say you love me
and yet you act like a person in love
well you're you mean the world to me
Shelly there's no one I want to be with
you what I feel about you've got to be
loved I love you Shelly and I love you
Roger
Oh
you
goodnight
all right I apologize has to be in the
form of the lender but at this point I
think it's best I'm sorry that I never
took her many opportunities to tell you
that I adore you I kept telling myself
to wait for the perfect opportunity to
tell you and well waiting I fell in love
with you now appears that the
opportunity is gone
something beat me to it
I can't begin to tell you how many times
you're pretty smart my day is so
wonderful
we truly are the good in my good morning
I wish you only the best and I hope that
you're happy if you'd like to keep in
touch or you know when you just need a
friend
my email is Ryan the guy from the donor
Gmail but I've always been right there's
really nothing you guys could have done
well we certainly didn't help matters
any my surprise visit made things worse
like I know you to mean well but things
do happen for a reason not the reason
we're here
I mean hopefully it'll just call soon
that way we can just get this whole
thing sorted out oh I love you guys
referring Mitchell and to my favorites
but I've been regarded worse
Oh
Oh what was your survey
yeah
another was was revision bring you them
I didn't think I needed a reason
although there are plenty of them I went
to go with my gut feeling and the don't
feel it don't force it but definitely
for that one look this birthday goes too
far higher those we got all the
guesswork
no no no no look I told you mine
no I wanna hear yours okay sneak in
there absorbing my venom like even close
to in serious and killing this girl
Rachel
never
never worked up the nerve
I read that little situation preview to
tell like crazy
all right thanks Willie
six months ago I was relocated to LA for
a tail bone one of our pair of
corporations with merger on the street
work there was a little visor on going
there like every day this is Rachel
that's right
it's not every day you run into someone
that makes you feel wonderful
these are rare moments and special
people there's only a few moments in a
lifetime where you meet that special
someone and if you let those moments go
by they're gone forever
so don't take it for granted I just felt
like it Thailand come where would be
perfect for me to move forward and then
I held out for another perfect time is
in another in another sweetie now you
know there's no such thing the perfect
time is whatever you make it what do I
do now and too late
act on your moment now I don't care
well I should have seen this coming
we're perfect for each other mm-hmm
where you headed off to and that's wick
[Laughter]
pick up
Oh
[Laughter]
ah
you can't say you tried when you never
even took a chance just dangerous take a
little bubble this whole time so you
wouldn't get hurt I'm afraid of Lolo
dirty coward
look rejection is all part of the
adventure and taking the champions you
considered maybe rejected
let's deliver my life support well being
in love yes that country
what huh oh it doesn't sound silly look
some people you know they all love with
someone's physical appearance and some
people fall in love with a person's
heart mine didn't suddenly vote here
I'll hire my kind of guy and I really
like that she's got substance I'm on a
date with a girl who's on helping me
understand how I screwed up with another
girl comical would you like another
glass of wine actually a people ready to
order or what
or dog food you men are so dead sometime
what do you think I'm explaining your
situation cheery to fix it yes thank you
exactly not speak of fishing enough damn
with me now go get her
Los Angeles yeah what about you know
what about it now you're a really nice
guy Ryan and you're extremely attractive
and I so we have a lot of fun time
together but you're clearly in love with
someone else and I'm not getting in way
that I don't think I could even if I
tried
you're in love
- computer well you are amazing if your
baby
I'm Rachel - she's a little waitress
here you just miss her you might catch
her right that good yep
oh my god Richard okay
what are you doing here I am looking for
a guy from insiders
look
of a
nice
you
mmm
Oh
is officially our
you
Oh