Written by truc1979 for
https://av-subs.alwaysdata.net
In life,
we'll sometimes play
roles to mask who we are.
To hide our fears, protect our hearts.
We'll smile through the pain,
laugh at bad jokes.
Tell others we're okay
when we're really not.
But who are we when
that mask comes down?
When we can no longer hide?
When we must exist
in that raw open space...
...of truth.
So...
You know the reception is downstairs, right?
Yeah...
I came up here to be alone.
Are you friends with the
bride or the groom?
The bride.
Oh, okay. Me too.
How do you know her?
- She's an old friend.
- She's an old friend of mine too!
And no: we didn't date.
If you were wondering.
I wasn't.
So listen: I'm new to
this town and uh...
I was wondering if uh... you
could show me around town, and uh...
No.
Wow... you just wound up
really tight, aren't you?
No. I'm just not interested.
Hm. Playing hard to get, huh?
I like it.
You'll be doing me in
my hotel before midnight.
And now I just want to
rip all these buttons off.
I like the way you're talking.
Wait wait wait...
Do you think we should
call the babysitter first?
She told us we got all day.
Okay...
But I mean like should
we check on Isabelle...
Jesus...
It's been a few hours.
Look honey, you are
ruining the fantasy, okay?
Alright, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, you're right.
Okay. We ***, alright?
This is just a one-time thing.
I'm not looking for a relationship.
Good. Me neither.
Oh my gosh, you're gonna make me come.
Yeah... don't stop.
Oh my god... wow...
You're really good at that.
- Really pretty genitals.
- Thank you.
I want to see what it looks like.
There's nothing like sucking a cock
that you haven't sucked before.
Oh, you wear special panties for me?
You never know if you're gonna get lucky.
Oh, so fucking true.
But I always know.
You often have one night stands?
Oh yeah...
You'll never have to talk
to me again right?
I'm never gonna talk to you again.
That's cool, ***
I think this is your
favorite position, uh?
Is that your regular gig to
find a horny girl at a wedding?
It just depends on the wedding.
'Cause my pussy is so wet,
this is sliding all over.
Don't tease me too much.
You're gonna make me come again.
*** pussy tightening around your cock.
That was fun.
I've never had a one-night stand before.
Yeah, you have.
Ray, stay in character!
Yeah. Oh yeah, yeah yeah.
Okay. I got it.
Okay. We should probably
go check on the baby.
Oh! Yeah, yeah...
Yeah, it's just been our new thing you know,
just like how you guys are playing
with your whips and your chains,
He's been really into
the whole role thing...
(...it's been amazing...)
Oh, oh, really?
No way.
But of course we can't
have Isabella at the house
because you know, she's a little baby.
So we're gonna take her to mom's house...
Oh yeah, that sounds like fun.
Emma?
Are you even listening to
anything that I'm saying?
Oh yeah of course I'm listening.
You know, you sound like you're zoning out.
Why don't you call me back when you
actually have an interest in my life?
Please...
Please let me come right now, please...
Can I come? Can I?
Nope.
Do you have any idea how
much I hate you right now?
"Hate" was the farthest thing to
how I felt about Mr Frederick.
In the last year we'd gone
through a lot of changes.
We'd relocated to Atlanta
Georgia for his company.
If uprooting your entire life doesn't
bring a relationship closer together,
nothing will.
And we were closer than ever.
Four years ago,
I never would have pictured
being in a relationship with a man
that I'd move the country for.
But falling in love often changes you.
Mr Frederick and I had fallen into
such a beautiful pattern.
Not the kind that couples dread
but the kind that really works.
The kind that gave us a handful of days to
reconnect with some semblance of normalcy.
While still providing us enough time
to relish our deviances.
Balancing the two wasn't always easy.
I'd become so accustomed to being his sub,
that downshifting to conventional
living at times...
...proved challenging.
Are you masturbating at the dinner table?
Yes.
Are you going to punish me?
No, it's your day off.
He was strict about
honoring those days off.
No matter how hard I
tried to persuade him.
Tempting emma but no.
You are so mean.
But that just made our
"days on" all the more sweet.
For me there was no
greater pleasure than those days.
Waking up, knowing I
got to play his sub.
Not that I was playing at all.
The truth was I felt
more myself as his sub,
as his sub than I ever did as Emma.
There was barely a trace
of her left anymore.
I was fearless,
with hard-nose becoming
ever more infrequent.
In fact, putting limits
on my experiences
had become more terrifying
to me than taking risks.
Stick it in.
I love how cold it
is when it first goes in.
- Do you like watching that?
- Yeah...
I'm so full right now...
I love how much you enjoy this.
Why is that?
I don't know.
It doesn't hurt?
It's a little uncomfortable, but
there's nothing I can't handle.
So would you say you enjoy anal, vaginal,
or both the same time the most?
Do you realize that anal sex has become
your favorite topic of discussion with me?
You love the fact that you turn me on
to something i used to be terrified of.
Don't you?
No easy feet (***?)
So which is it?
I don't know...
It's so hard to choose...
Would you prefer it if it was a...
...another man's dick in
there rather than just a toy?
Is this a hypothetical question
or a serious one?
Serious.
It's not a no...
...but it's not a yes either.
You surprised me more
than anybody i've ever met.
Why did you think I was going to say no?
Yeah.
Yes i did.
You know, I'm not the
same Emma I used to be.
I have a lot of insane fantasies now.
And that's all because of you.
No, that's all because of you.
I'm just the catalyst.
I love making your cock so hard.
I love having your cock inside me.
I have to clean all this
pussy off your cock first.
I'm freaking out!
(Is that a maid uniform?)
- Yeah, it's role playing night.
(- Okay.)
(So what's wrong?)
This!
(Why? I mean it suits you.)
No!
It's not supposed to suit me,
it's supposed to be me
pretending to be someone else.
Right.
You're his maid.
But I'm already his maid:
I do the housework, I do the dishes,
I scrub the toilets...
And now I dress like his maid.
Nadia, maids do not dress like that.
They wear rubber gloves and sweatpants,
not push-up bras and short shorts.
When a husband dresses
his wife like a maid,
that's it, that's the end of their sex life.
Like what else is that for?
As inane as this might sound,
I was a little envious of Nadia that night.
Regardless of her issue with Ray's fantasies,
at least he shared them with her.
Mr Frederick had always focused on mine,
always shying away from sharing his.
And I wanted desperately
for him to open to me.
The way Ray had with Nadia.
You did remarkably well tonight.
I can't believe you lasted the whole time.
I've gotten very good with restraints.
Well it's reward time,
I'll drop a bath in a while.
I want to request
permission for another reward.
All right, permission granted.
I want to hear about some of your fantasies.
What do you mean?
I tell you about my fantasies all the time.
In fact, I, usually,
issue them as direct orders.
Things that you haven't experienced yet,
and things that you want to experience.
Not just for me.
I love that you push me
to explore my sexuality,
and it doesn't always have to be about me.
I want it to be about you too.
In fact, you've told me that you
fantasized about being with other women.
Yes.
So why not act on that?
I don't know why you're
afraid to tell me these things,
it's a fantasy of yours and...
...we're definitely known for turning
fantasies into reality, so...
why not that reality?
Where is this coming from?
You do so much for me all the time.
I just want to do the same for you.
Do you remember how scared you got just
from seeing me talking to Audrina?
But everything is different now.
I don't care.
I'm not willing to risk losing
you over something I don't need.
But you won't lose me.
(Two years into my relationship with Audrina,)
we had a very similar conversation
just like this.
And she sounded just as confident as you do now.
I think it would be fun.
And why's that?
What man doesn't want
to be with another woman?
Keep pleasuring yourself.
Who did you have in mind?
She's called Rebecca.
I know her from my old job.
And what is it about her?
It's her face.
It's what i picture every
time I fantasize about you...
...having sex with another woman.
You've done that?
I'm doing it right now.
Thinking about you inside of her.
I want to earn that reward.
I mean you please another woman.
Let's have you earn this one too.
No coming till I say so.
Did you ever go through with it?
Yes.
You ready for this?
I can't wait.
Alright Rebecca, you can come in.
Get on all fours on the bed.
Pull your dress up.
Pull your panties down.
I don't want you to take your
eyes off of us for a second.
Spread your legs wider.
Oh my god that feels so good, yes...
Stay right there.
Audrina!
Right here.
Stay with us.
Good choice Audrina.
Very good.
Audrina.
Please don't tease me, sir.
Good, she's calling me "sir"
without even asking.
She's got great hands, Audrina.
Rebecca.
Yes sir.
I want you to walk over,
and give Audrina a kiss.
- Okay?
- Yes sir.
Do you like the way his
cock tastes on my lips?
Audrina, you're the only one
for me. You know that?
I love you.
Audrina thank you so much.
I had no idea it was gonna
be this much fun.
It could have been a...
...intensely satisfying experience for both of us.
Why wasn't it?
Because I got selfish,
and I didn't realize at the time...
...that it was really bothering her.
And she wanted to go back to a
more traditional relationship.
- But I would never want that.
- I know.
That doesn't change the fact that...
It's not worth it to me...
...to jeopardize what we have.
Although he seemed adamant about it now,
I knew one day,
when the time was right,
I'd prove to him that his fantasies
were my fantasies.
And that I was open to absolutely everything.
What would you like me to
bring you from Los Angeles?
Do you remember that chocolate shop
down the street from us?
Yes I do.
You can bring me a few treats
from there, I'd really love it.
I'll bring you a whole box of those.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Now...
I left tomorrow's outfit hanging in the bathroom.
And don't think that just because I'm gone
that you get three days off.
I know.
No masturbating.
The whole time?
You'll survive!
This is so not fair.
It's not supposed to be fair.
Hello?
Emma?
Yes. Who's this?
It's Kelsey from the corporate office.
Emma, I just got word that William Frederick
was killed in a plane crash this evening.
They're saying it was engine failure or
something like that. I...
I don't have any other details, but, I...
I'm so sorry Emma...
Thank you for letting me...
Thank you for letting me know.
Reports are saying the engine failure
was responsible for the plane crash.
Although investigation is still underway.
The three passengers have been identified as
pilot John Bennett,
co-pilot Andrew Rogers,
and billionaire William Frederick.
Frederick was well-known philanthropist and
a highly respected member
of the Atlanta community.
His contributions to medical
research included
the funding of the downtown Polaria
children's cancer center earlier this year.
He was 35.
For days I just sat there.
Unable to comprehend what life
even meant without him.
(Emma, bring me the black tie.)
It took almost a week
before I could even take off the final
outfit he'd chosen for me to wear.
I didn't want to accept
there would never be another.
Or that the world he and I had created
over the last several years
had now become nothing more than a memory.
And that this journey we had embarked upon,
had come to the most bittersweet of ends.
I stayed with Nadia and Ray for a while
when I got back to the west coast.
It was a world that I'd evolved so far from,
that it was hard to be in the thick of it again.
All that brightness and sterile wealth.
They both did everything within their
power to try and fix me.
Hey, I made you some brownies.
I know they're your favorite.
I'm not really hungry.
Okay.
I don't know why you just didn't listen to me.
Like I told you, Emma doesn't like flowers.
Oh my god.
- All women are flower people.
- No.
Emma isn't. She's not like every person.
I spent all this time picking this out,
you could have let me know ahead of time.
I did, but ...
But nothing could distract me away
from the painful reality of the situation.
I would never see Mr Frederick again.
Remember when we used to do this all the time?
You may not see it now but...
Life has its reasons...
Even for heartbreak.
I wonder who I'd be if I never met you.
Be you.
That's not what I mean.
Emma, this was in you before me.
I could tell that the second I met you.
It'll be a part of who you are forever.
To a life of hope and promise.
- Too hot?
- Yeah.
Well it has some cleansing properties,
so you want to make sure to finish it.
We could all use some cleansing around here.
So, I was thinking we can
take a day trip this morning.
I don't think Emma wants to go on a day trip.
Of course she does.
Everybody likes a day trip.
Okay, where are we going?
Palm Springs!
Golfing?
No. No golfing Ray.
This is family bonding.
They have this place called "paint a memory".
We can go and paint some ceramics, and...
(Why?)
Because it's something we can do together.
Something we've never done before.
(I have a new task for you today.)
Something we've never done before?
A little role reversal.
Okay...
You are going to be the dominant.
Are you serious?
Amidst the chaos of Ray
and Nadia's suburban crisis.
Memories of Mr Frederick pulled
me back to that life,
that world.
Now you can make any demand
of me that you want,
- within reason of course.
- Oh my gosh!
I never thought that you would ever come...
But, however,
there will be consequences
if you do not convincingly fulfill this role.
No asking for permission,
I want you to establish authority,
and be assertive.
Now i am giving you this
freedom until 10 pm tonight.
At which point you'll be stripped of this power,
and you'll return to your role as my submissive.
Your time begins...
now.
Why do we even have to do it at all?
Because it's something...
I tried to stay present.
But my mind kept drifting back to that
last day i spent with Mr Frederick.
Yeah, I mean, but she doesn't. She's like...
No.
I'm sick and tired of you always...
We had reached a new level of
trust in our relationship that day.
- No please...
- ***
But it's different for a guy.
And no masturbating either.
Like in some inexplicable way,
we knew that this would be
our final day together.
And that we wanted to write
one last epic chapter.
What is this?
Your final task.
Wait here.
I want to prove to you
that what we have is different
than anything you've had before.
Emma, no...
Let me give this to you.
It's as much for me as it is for you.
All right, but... Emma...
I'm in control of your choices tonight.
Remember?
Have a little faith in me.
Just sit...
and watch.
- Do you like what you see?
- Yeah.
My tongue feels so good.
Take it easy, mister.
Do remember that I'm in control tonight.
Yeah, one more hour.
Just watch for now.
Is this in your *** Mr Frederick?
Yes Madam.
That's what I like to hear.
Oh, I think you should come taste this.
Taste her lips first.
I want you to taste the rest of her.
Is he doing a good job?
***
Make her come with your mouth.
Hear her feel all the
pleasure that you give me.
Don't you think she
deserves to come ***?
Do it slowly.
I just want you to feel her mouth,
I don't want you to feel anything else.
- Do you like to feel the back of her throat?
- Yes
It's such a huge turn on
watching her suck your dick.
Do you like that?
I'll let you taste this too.
That's what i like to hear.
We're making our pussies so wet.
I think that's where dick needs to go next.
Do you like having two girls?
I love your hands so much.
Her lips look so good around your dick.
I want to see what your dick
looks like inside of her.
She's such a good girl.
*** come now,
you better make sure you ask permission.
I wanna taste her cum of here.
I love watching her swallow your dick.
See how much fun we can have.
I guess you're right.
- I'm sorry that I ***
- I love you so much.
- Don't forget to ask for permission...
- Yes madam.
Stick that dick inside her.
Such a good girl.
I need to taste it.
- You like having two girls servicing you, ***?
- Yes I do.
Now I want you to sit on his face.
And you, I want you lick her pussy.
I want you to use both of that holes.
Stick it way down at me.
You are not very obedient.
That ***.
I love watching that...
- Focus.
- Yes baby.
Fuck me first.
Just like that.
We don't want to be punished.
No coming without permission.
Just a ***, just a ***...
- Is it ok if I come?
- Yes
Yes, you may.
I want you to put all your cum all
over her perfect little tits.
- Yeah?
- Hm-hm
Can you do that for me?
Can you be a good boy and
come all over this little slut?
I want you to come.
I want you to come all over these tits.
Look at that, it's 10 p.m and
I feel like punishing you.
I didn't do so good?
I'm about to leave town,
and you do this to me.
It was bad?
It was incredible.
You're incredible.
Emma? Emma?
Were you listening to
anything I just said?
Of course.
Okay, so paint a memory.
Things were difficult for a really long time.
Memories of Mr Frederick were always
there, just beneath the surface.
Robbing me of the present, and holding me
to something that no longer was.
But the point to all this hasn't been to
tell you about the epic love story
of Emma and Mr Frederick.
It's to tell you the story of my life.
And all of its new beginnings.
I continued on my journey as a submissive
two years after Mr Frederick died.
I couldn't deny my own truth.
Mike Mr Frederick said it was ingrained in me.
So I reached out to a dominant
named Michael Sullivan.
I told him about my grief,
and he suggested using BDSM
as a way to heal my pain.
It began as a therapeutic relationship,
in which I paid him to dominate
me a few hours every week.
Easing me back into that familiar world.
Everything we did was an exercise in trust.
We never drafted up a formal contract
because initially I had no idea were my
hard-nose even existed anymore.
Sometimes they manifested themselves
in the most unexpected places.
But he took things slowly,
allowing me as much time as I needed
to surrender to the experience.
He toyed with new ways of building
up my level of restraint.
Pushing me just to the edge of my breaking point.
But i never broke.
I was determined to overcome the fear
that came from trusting someone new.
No matter how intense the situation or the pain.
What is that?
It's an electric wand.
Will it hurt?
The fear of it is going to be
more intense than the actual pain.
And just remember:
pain can be a pleasure.
He had this uncanny way of knowing
exactly when to push me.
And when to back down.
And was sensitive to the process in ways
I never would have imagined from someone
I was just beginning to know.
But no matter how sensitive
he might have been,
Nothing would have prepared me for one
particular day we spent together
Today's exercise is an eye contact.
That's not BDSM.
Of course it is.
It's an exercise that pushes
you beyond your comfort zone.
I'd rather be just stick to the physical things.
Being submissive is not just about the physical.
You know that.
Listen,
All I'm asking for is 30 seconds.
For 30 seconds you have
to stare at me in the eyes.
You can count each and every one in your head.
But you can't look away.
I don't understand what this is supposed to teach me.
Is this a hard no?
No.
Then we can begin when you're ready.
There's a lot of courage in what you've done.
Most people would have just rolled over.
I'm ready.
Nobody could ever fill the
void of Mr Frederick's loss.
He was my first love.
And in some ways he was my greatest love.
But he wasn't my only love.
Take off your shoes, get on the bed.
Come here.
I'm scared.
Well you have every right to be.
What if I can't do this?
Then use your safe word.
What's bringing on all these concerns.
I'm afraid I might like it.
That's kind of the point.
Stop. You're beautiful.
When I think back on the last 10 years of my life,
I'm overcome with a profound sense of happiness,
the road I traveled to get to where I'm at right now.
A strong, courageous, woman who's no
longer living this socially acceptable existence.
But one who's found her truth,
fallen in love with that truth.
And become the person she was always meant to be.
Sure,
life didn't work out as I might have imagined.
Life never happens perfectly.
There are often setbacks and challenges and
frustrations and heartbreak.
But as Nadia once said,
There is reason. Even for heartbreak.
And this was mine.
We all play roles and wear
masks from time to time.
It's what we do.
It's how we get by.
Sometimes it's to make ourselves
feel good about ourselves.
Sometimes it's to fulfill that inner need
we have to be something we're actually not.
And then there are those times
when your guard is down,
and that mask comes off.
When your heart is open,
and the only thought is of this one
precious moment.
And you're left beautifully,
perfectly, comfortably, exposed.
Hold it in place.
There you go.
I think you're ready for the real thing.
Oh yes please fuck me.
Give you one hand.
You should turn around.
I like that.
One day, when I'm ready,
a while from now,
I'd like to tell you my story,
and how I got here.
I'd like to hear that.
And what would this life story be called?
The Submission of Emma Marx.
Written by truc1979 for
https://av-subs.alwaysdata.net