=======================
Credits: impaired963
Fix or feedback: please let me know
truc1979@laposte.net
=======================
Gosh Bruce!
I'm stuck!
This game might be too advanced for a young boy, Bruce.
It's actually quite rudimentary, Lisa.
All you have to do is think...
...16 moves ahead.
That's all.
Well, I'll leave you two to your past time.
Tomorrow, my father is hosting that, umm...
...fundraiser for the deaf children with the blind parents.
The seamstress is coming to do my wardrobe.
Poor, poor children.  Destiny is quite unkind to them to say the least.
As long as they're fine individuals.
Such as your father.
I'm sure they would never lose hope.
So go along dear.
I'll see you for dinner.
[kiss]
Riddle me this, Miss Carson!
What is the difference between you...
...and Bruce Wayne's...
...bank account?
There is no difference.
You both pique his...
...interest.
[screams]
Bruce!  Did you hear that?
Yes.
And judging by the time of day, it's probably Alfred...
...groping Aunt Harriet.
Holy Viagra!
Commissioner Gordon...
...somebody left an envelope for you.
Well thank you dear.
The Riddler!
He's kidnapped Lisa Carson, the famous heiress.
The pompous...
...worldly master of foul play.
Are you thinking what I think you're thinking?
I'm afraid I am.
The devil with pride, Chief!
There's only but one man living that can stop him.
Whoever he may be behind that mask of his...
...our only hope...
...the Cape Crusader.
Master Wayne the phone is ringing.
Thank you Alfred, but I'm...quite busy with this challenging game.
Sir, it's the...special phone.
Holy checkmate!
Yes, Commissioner.
Sorry to deserve you Batman.  We have an emergency.
The Riddler's on the loose.
He's kidnapped Bruce Wayne's girlfriend.
Surely you must be jesting.
Alas, I am not.
We haven't time to lose.
To the Bat pole.
I turned the batteries to power!  Turbines to speed!
Hello!
Look.
You don't have to hold me captive.
My father is very wealthy.
And my fiance' is Bruce Wayne!
They'll pay whatever ransom you desire.
So....
...the kind of ransom I want your father cannot pay.
Riddle me this, Miss Carson.
When is cheese bad for a mouse?
When...it's in a trap.
And you, Miss Carson, are the cheese.
And Batman... is... my....
...fat....rat...
[laughing]
Well this bed looks awfully uncomfortable.
Don't you have any better accommodations?
I would be...
...very....appreciative.
Perhaps a softer mattress can be negotiated.
[laughs]
[laughing]
You don't want a mattress that bad?
Oh, god, you're big!
Bruce isn't.
Have you met these?
I wanna slip into something a little more comfortable.
Unzip me.
[giggles]
That's better.
That's a dirty mouth.
A cock in my mouth.
I'm such a dirty girl.
Where else do you wanna put your cock?
Huh, Riddler?  Hmm?
Riddle me this?
When is a pussy like a flower?
When?
When it has...
...too lips!
[laughing]
Ohh!  Harder.
Oh, you're perverted!
Oh, you're perverted.
Oh, this is so wrong!
More.
I wanna sit on that.
Yes, stick that pussy out there!
Oh, my.... Be careful...Be careful with that thing!
You put all that pretty cock...you put all that pretty cock in my butt?
I know it's so small.  And you fuck my pussy so good.
...for you?
Oh, my asshole knows your cock so well.
Oh, I'm so tight!
I will get your cum.  Oh, yes.
Oh, my...Oh, my...
Oh, it's driving me crazy!
It's so nice...
Am I gaping pretty for you?
Cum on my cock!
Commissioner, how's Ms Carson?
That cowardly puzzler...he better not harm a hair on her head.
I take it you and Bruce Wayne are acquainted?
Yes, Mr. Wayne has graced me with his friendship and...
we've had meaningful conversations from time to time but....
...please, the stipulations on the ransom?
Well, Batman here's the thing...
...there is no ransom request.
Unprecedented!
I think I might know what it is he's after.
He wants us.
To come find you.
What a dastardly, twisted plot!
But Batman...
...that sounds like a trap!
Precisely Robin!  Which is why we now have an advantage.
I say we play along, but...
...cautiously.
I think I may have some information on the whereabouts of the Riddler.
Quick Robin! We haven't a moment to lose!
Holy gluteus maximus, Batman!
This Bat climb is sure hard on the buttocks.
Careful Robin.
Both hands on the Bat Rope.
Sorry Batman.
Batman and Robin!
What are you guys doing?
Holy hedgehog Batman!  Who is this?
Robin this is Ron Jeremy, without a doubt the hardest...
...working man in show business.
Women seem to find him strangely...
...irresistible.
Hey guys, why don't you take a break...
...and come have some fun inside?
Can't handle all these girls by myself.
I've got two free hands!
Very tempting but thanks.
Our pursuit of justice...allows us very few diversions.
But...by all means....
...carry on with your business, citizen.
Gosh Batman!
That Ron Jeremy sure has excellent taste in girls.
That single statement indicates to me the first oncoming thrust of manhood old chum.
Wait for me on the roof.
I'm gonna go inside.
Two masked crimefighters...
...walking into a discotheque could...
...draw some unwanted attention.
Oh, my god, it's Batman!
A large grapefruit juice please.  Yessir.
Are you looking for a friend?
I believe....
...you could say that.
I have a question.
How is a squabble like a bargain?
Very well.  It's because...
...it takes two to make it.
Hmm...
Do you like beautiful music?
Shall we?
What is your name?
Molly.
Here you go Batman.
Freshly squeezed.
Thank you.
You...
...entice me.
I accept your invitation to dance.
You shake a pretty mean cape, Batman.
This...it's nothing.
It's....
...spiked!
That's right, Batman, your drink is spiked.
The drug scopolamine is going to make you lose all of your willpower.
And the funny thing is...
...you're gonna follow me back to where the Riddler has that heiress.
Lisa...
Yeah, Lisa Carson.
She's not even that pretty anyway.  I don't know what Bruce Wayne sees in her.
I...must...resist.
You can't resist Batman.
Your willpower is gone.  You're only going to take orders.
And in fact, I'm gonna have fun with you before you go.
Do you like that?
I'm drooling all over your cock.  Do you like that?
Stick that tongue out there.
I bet he's begging for this pussy.
You want it so bad.  Look at you.
Look at you.
One more inch and you'll be in this pussy.
You want me to sit on it don't you.
Is that what you want?  Me to sit on that cock?
Worship my big ass.
Put your hand all over it.
Spank me.
Kiss me....Fuck me.
I wanna taste it!  I wanna taste.
Oh, you wanna put that cock in my wet pussy?
That pussy is so juicy!
Fuck me like that.
Fuck me!
Oh, stick it back in.  Stick it back in that pussy!
Oh, yes!  I wanna cum!
Oh, fuck me!
Back and forth.
You like that?  Yeah.
You like when that pussy fucks you back, don't you?
You want me to take that cock from you, stroke by stroke?
Keep your cock right there.
Oh, no, no, no.  You're going to cum in my mouth.
Blow your bat right in my mouth.
Now let's get going.  I got to find your dumb heiress.
Commissioner!  Batman's gone!
What?!  Batman is gone?
Yes!  I'm afraid he's been kidnapped by the Riddler.
Excuse me Barbara.  We have an emergency here.  Oh.
Don't worry, Daddy.  I understand.  Love you.
Love you too, dear.
A thought strikes me.
So dreadful...
I scarcely dare give it utterance.
Could this be the end of Batman?
Holy transformation!
One minute she's plain Barbara Gordon....
...librarian...
...and the next...
Looks like you guys can use some help.
BatGirl!
For heaven sakes, BatGirl we can use all the help we can get right now.
Commissioner, I believe I have an idea.
You wanna catch a criminal, the best person to ask is...
...another criminal!
That's right, Robin!  And I think I know where to find one.
Follow me!
I use my Bat Scanner to pinpoint the possible hideaways of the Joker.
Something tells me...
...he knows where we can find... the Riddler.
Holy free fall, BatGirl.
I got you.
Is that a battery in your pocket or are you just happy to save me?
I...I...make sure to have both hands on the rod.
Rope!  Rope!
The Riddler will be arriving soon.
With the masked fool.
And silly heiress.
I'll get rid of Batman and Robin for good!
Holy conspiracy!
[laughs]
The Joker!
King!
Of all super criminals.
[laughs]
Gotham first, I think!
Then...
...the world!
[laughs]
Curb your tongue, funny man.
You and I...we have a deal
But of course.
My feline friend.
You can have your way with the dynamic duo.
Just before I destroy them...[laughs]
We're waiting for the winged caped crusader.
Perhaps we could warm up a bit.
Uh...please Joker!
The mere thought perturbs me!
Besides....
I have a more infinitely fiendish plan for them...
Very well.  Have it your way.
There is more than one way to skin a cat.
Woman...
Now get out!
I need to relax before the Grand Finale!  [laughs evilly]
Would you like a massage, Joker?
How about a full body rub down?
Both ideas sound smashing, acutally.
Oh yes!
What the heck!
Cover your eyes, BatGirl!
This spectacle is not for a lady.
Don't be silly, Robin, it's hot!
Let me be your personal go-go dancer.  Yes, yes, let me see that!
Pretty, pretty.
Going to suck your dick good.
She sucks it real good!
Let me taste that cock!
Oh, Joker!
I know what you like.
You make my pussy so wet!
Tast yourself on it.
Are you gonna ride that dick?  Oh, yeah
It feel good in your pussy?
It's so big!
I love to watch you fuck!
She's such a dirty girl!
More cock for you?
Yes, more cock please.
More cock for me.
Shove it back inside me.
Oh, fuck me!
Oh, my goodness, put it inside my tiny twat.
It's so deep inside my pussy!
It's such a good view!
You like being in this little whore hole?
Yeah.
Your cock feels so nice!
Oh, come on, fuck me Joker.
Get down here, I'm coming on your faces.
Now remember, remember...
I want you to smile when you take the load.
We always do!
It tastes good.
Holy popshot!
The Riddler better bring Batman soon, or...    Or what?
You gonna show me why they call you Boy Wonder?
Gee BatGirl!
When you put it that way?
Oh my god, Robin!
I'm coming!  I'm coming!
I wanna make myself cum!
Give it to me!
Very impressive, Boy Wonder!
Looks like you let the bird out of the cage.
Get him!
Who better to complete your plan?...
...than the Prince of Puzzles?!
The King of Conundrum...
...the Count of....
It will just a matter of time...before my trusty sidekick figures out...
...your dastardly plan!
And comes for my rescue.
Oh, really now!
Tsk...tsk...and another tsk...
Batman.
You witch!
What?  With all your troubles...
...still haven't learned good manners?
A real gentleman would kiss a lady's paw.
You are no lady.
In fact, you....
Batman!
I cannot tolerate a man with no breeding.
Enough of this child's play!
This time.... the joke's on you!
Silly crime fighters.
[laughing]
What deviltry are you up to this time, Joker?!
One zap from my very funny ray gun...
...and you're fini....caput....!
...defunct!  Defunct!
You won't get away with this so easy!
Easily.
Easily.  Good grammar is essential, Robin.
Thank you, Batman.
You're very welcome.
Wait a second, Joker!
That was not the plan!
Then the plan...
...was a joke!
Wait! Wait!  Wait!
The rich lady...should bring a fine ransom.
She'll bring lots of money!
Who cares about a few dollars?
When you can finally be rid of the masked menace!
Wait!  Kill him first!
I always hated that little fucker!
Batman, your lips are so sexy when you're angry.
Your eyes so dashing beneath that mask.
Just remember, you owe we me one.
Riddle me this...
Holy glass jaw, Batman!
You can bring these nefarious criminals to justice, BatGirl.
We will personally deal with our feline felinous.
Thank you, Batman.  You are a remarkable man!
Oh, it was nothing.  Nothing at all.
In fact, I hear your fiance'...
...Mr. Wayne, was quite the remarkable man himself?
He is a remarkable man.
You two have a lot of similar qualities.
Thank you.  Thank you.
Now it's your turn, CatWoman.
Our duty as duly deputized officers of the law is to put you behind bars.  Nonetheless...
...your gesture shows there's some good left in your moral fiber.
But we are indeed indebted to her, Robin.
She did save our lives.
We should show leniency, but...
Without compromising our moral principles.
Holy dilemma, Batman!  What are we to do?!
I think I have the purrfect solution!
We must give credit where credit is due.
She may be evil, but she is quite attractive.
Holy threesome, Batman?
Indeed.
'Yeah, I wanna get fucked!
Yeah, I want it!  I want that Bat Cum!
Your nice hard cocks cum all over my dirty, kitty face.
That was very, very pleasing, Cat Woman, but...
...it is time to go.
Of  course, Bat Man, but....
..give me a minute to freshen up.
You wouldn't want the prison warden to see me all covered in your Bat Cum would you?
Robin, she has a point, but do it in a timely manner.
Of course.
Well, you know what they say...
...cats have 9 lives.
Well, I hope bats have at least 2>
CAN THIS BE IT FOR THE DYNAMIC DUO!
LEARN THE AGONIZING ANSWER!
DON'T MISS THE NEXT EPISODE!