==========================
Please send corrections or
or missing "***" words
to truc1979@laposte.net
==========================
Vince, it's a long time friend attorney and
drinking buddy
I have to tell you got to
stop making some payments
and I saw Ellen today and...
Oh shit is Ellen bitching again?
That's there's a right to complain you're way behind
Who's side are you on anyway?
I'm on both your sides you know that
You still there?
Have any suggestions?
Yeah, yeah I have some suggestions I suggest you start making
some payments
Believe me Jerry I am
making payments on that three-bedroom
house I bought, Gloria's jewelry, that that
fucking honeymoon in Europe that I couldn't even afford
Vince look I sympathize with your
problems but we're talking about Ellen
she's having a very hard financial time
of it and you got to start doing something
I'll see what I can do
Yeah. Talk to you later
Ah that's better now we can concentrate
on some serious business
Oh Baby.
I hate the smell of that cigars
I'm sorry baby I'm gonna give him up one
of these days
How much good sir?
Oh hi Pam
What can I get for you today?
How about a large iced tea?
Anything else? How about today's special?
Yeah I'll be fine
Okay
Did you have to show off like that?
I was just trying to be nice
Yeah... but not too nice
But it's easy
Your snap crotch
Are you lawyers don't know anything?
Let me do it
Can you do it?
It's not a snap
Yes it is
Babe, suck on here
Brewster's residence,
Gloria Brewster speaking
Gloria?
Gloria is that you? You sound funny
- Everything's all right?
- I'm fine! I'm just
waiting for you to get home I'm warming
something up for you right now
Don't tell me you're finally learning how to cook
No but I do have something cooking
Well honey I'm afraid you're gonna have
to put it on the back burner I gotta see a client
Can't he wait?
I'm afraid not. What is it you got warming up?
Hold on, I wish you'd listen to it
Did you hear me out?
Gloria did you buy a cat?
No silly I have a pussy and it's meow
is *** harder for you
I swear baby if I could I'd come home right now
But I can't.
You just keep it warm for a couple of hours
and I'll get there
How about giving it a kiss over the phone?
See you later
Ooh that gave me goosebumps all over
Hurry home, okay, and do it in person
Bye
Come in my mouth
I spoke to Vince he said he'd try mixing payments
Jerry, that's what he said the
last time and the time before that
I know. He's not a bad guy
And I know that. I was married him for 15 years,
remember
It's just I cannot make it financially
alone anymore
Well. What a fun I *** ***
some money
Jerry you know how I feel
about that, but thank you
Now it's time that husband of mine that
ex-husband of mine left after his
responsibilities and I think I know just
how to do it
Oh yeah? Tell me how?
I think I'm gonna pack up my troubles I
move into a brand-new house. House where
there are more bedrooms than the current
owner can use
Ellen you don't mean you're gonna go...
I certainly do. Watch me:
honeymoon cottage here I come
Boy you think we'd have more ***
possessions after all this time into
good thing we don't own all this
furniture honey I never fit in with your
father's *** or anyway
so you sure you
want to go through this I know we've
been through it before but...
All I know Mark, is
that we've got to do something I'm out
of a job and our bank account is zilch
but I can get a job, mom.
And quit college? No honey I won't hear that
Just for a semester or two
Yes and that's what I said all those
years ago I always promised myself I'd
go back to school and I never did and I
don't want the same thing to happen to you
I guess dad was pretty excited when
you told him huh?
She didn't tell him!
honey I was going to but well you you
know how your father is
You should have told him
Yeah I guess you're right I should
have told him
Tell you what, we'll stop on the way and
I'll call him then
Honey go ahead and order I'll go call
your father and tell him the good news
ok
Hi! I don't think you're right here before
I just moved into the area
Oh, good, so you can get back
to the restaurant again
Could be
I'm Pam Wilson, what's your name?
Mark. Mark Brewster
Brewster...
There's a guy named Brewster comes in a lot
He drives a red convertible
That's my dad!
Me and my mom we're gonna move in with him
Great, so you will be coming back in again
I do more than *** customers
Can give name of *** things to stop by
Great, I'd like that
Well, there was nobody home so I guess
we'll just have to surprise them
Hi
Mom, this is Pam Wilson
Nice to meet you
Hello dear, nice to meet you too
What can I get you folks?
2 Deluxe's and 2 rough beers
Okay, come right up
You couldn't get him on the phone, huh?
Honey I tried but nobody was home
Sure you dialed the right number?
Mark, after all these years I know your father's number
Aren't you getting a little friendly
with that kid over there?
Dad, give me a break
(Ohh...)
(Ohh... ohh)
Oh Christ, a sec you scared the shit out of me
Gloria you haven't been taking any
of those tranquilizers again, have you?
You know how they affect you
I want you
Gloria!
Hello, anybody home?
The good sign is door is open
That means your father's expecting us
Honey why don't you bring the rest of
the things in and I'll scout locations
They found the extra bedroom honey
yours is downstairs
Is Dad here?
He certainly is
But I don't think he wants to be bothered right now
So why don't you go ahead and unpack
and I... I guess I'll go
in the kitchen start fixing supper
Okay
Oh Vince that was wonderful
you're the greatest
Oh so are you baby
So are you
Where did this come from?
Oh, oh, this is lovely
I've always dreamed of having a coat like this
That's lovely Gloria, but
Oh I tried to walk passed it
I did it in fact several times but it just kept
saying to me buy me buy me buy me Gloria
It also tell you what to use for money?
My Charge Card of course
Of course
I knew you wouldn't mind
Gloria there's something we got to talk about
Of course honey but first let me
tell you that you're the most wonderful
*smack*
and generous husband a girl could ever have
Gloria.
Jerry asked me and ***
He's a nice guy and I know he's
your best friend but he just wouldn't
understand about such luxuries
Take this fur coat for instance
Oh I'd like to take that fur coat right back to the store
Vince, be serious, you know you want me to
look nice and besides
I say that if you've got it, flaunt it
But I don't have it
Sure you do Honey. Maybe not as big as
Jerry's but your little doodoo is plenty
big enough for me
Gloria, I'm not talking
about my little doodoo god damn it
I am talking about this mania you
have for spending every penny I make
Sometimes before I make it
Hi, I didn't mean to interrupt
Go ahead finish your argument I just
wanted to stop by and say hello
Goodbye
Wasn't that your ex-wife?
That was Ellen alright.
Alright help!
What is she doing here?
I don't know but I sure is
shit intend to find out
- Mark!
- Hi dad
Have you seen your mother?
She's in the bedroom
Don't you ever knock?
In my own house?
This may be your house but this is my bedroom
Oh since when?
Since right now
Oh, hell it is. Get your bags and
get out of here please
You throw me out on that street, Vince Brewster,
I will take you to court so fast
your heads gonna spin
The judge will award me this whole house
just for that child support payments
What's going on here?
Oh... it looks like we've got a border, Honey
Two borders.
My son Mark will be staying downstairs
Vince, get this this... this creature out of our house
I've already told her
And I've already told him that we intend to stay
We'll be one big happy family
I'll do the cooking Gloria can do the cleaning
I don't do cleaning
We have a woman come in twice a week
Okay, I'll do the cleaning and
Gloria can do the cooking
I don't cook either
Well what do you do, Honey?
Uh, maybe you're good at sucking cock
Or there's a woman coming twice a week and do that too
Vince, do something!
Good idea. I *** *** Mark unpack.
- Nice coat sweetie
- Vince!
Oh Gloria calm down
Yeah I know all about it yes yes
yeah we could get rid of all
we could get Ellen out, yeah,
and then you know what happens
then Ellen takes Vince to
court ends up with the house and you're
out on the street.
How do I know? I'm Ellen's Lawyer
that's how I know honey.
But honey, listen listen I'm everybody's friend in
this, okay? I'll you know. Relax, let it go
for a couple days, and we'll see what
happens. Don't worry about it.
Jerry, if that bitch stays here I'm gonna
make her life miserable
It's good to see you Mark
'to see you dad
(they talk at the same time)
But Mark I know that I haven't been
around to see as much as I'd like
but the agency it's getting bigger and
getting married and ***...
It's okay dad, I understand
That it's moving in here like this
I've tried to talk mom about it, I really did, but...
You know how headstrong she is
Oh for Christ's sakes what's the big deal anyway
It's more than enough room in
this house than two people need
Mark,
you and your mom you're welcome to stay
here as long as you like
Thanks, dad
Finish something
Where do you want this?
Wow, that's heavy...
Hello?
Hi, it's me, Pam Wilson
the girl from the diner, do you remember?
How could I forget?
That's sweet. I've been thinking about you a lot
I've been thinking about you too.
Really?
I have got some free time
if you'd like to come over
Come over to your place?
Sounds great but what about your folks?
No problem we'll have the place all to ourselves
Be right over
Great. See you then. Bye bye
You'll be right over where?
Oh I've got a date with one of the neighborhood girls
Wow that was a fast work
I was hoping you'd help me with the dishes
Hey y'all up with the dishes
No thank you, I can handle it
Hey, yeah yeah yeah, what the hell?
Besides we got a built-in dishwasher
You just go out and you have yourself a good time, son
Alright!
I've gotta take a shower and change clothes
Thanks a lot, dad
Make sure she uses birth control
What are you trying to do? Make points?
No no. I wasn't trying to make points
No?
Okay, I was trying to make points
It's not too late, is it?
No, it's never too late
Oh, speaking of late, I've got to call
Jerry about our date tonight
Oh... so... we've got a date with Jerry
tonight huh?
Not "we", Vince. "I". I have a date
with Jerry tonight and I've got to call
him and let him know what time
Hi Mark. Good to see you. Come on in.
Good to see too. You look great
Come on in the bedroom
Just *** *** on top
Sit down
So what do you want to talk about?
How about sex?
You mean *** right now?
No silly! I don't want to have sex now
I just want to talk about it
Are you still a virgin?
What a dumb question. Do I look like a virgin?
I don't know
You're a virgin?
Of course not!
Do I look retarded or something?
I'll bet you still have your cherry
Guys don't have cherries
No... they have something better
Before you came I was dancing
Would you like to see me dance?
Yeah, sure.
***?
Take off your pants
Have you ever seen a girl's pussy up close?
Only in pictures
It's okay. Come on.
Take a look
It's okay. Go ahead.
Look it. Kiss it.
Yeah, like that.
Good enough to eat?
Yeah
That's good
Way back I wanna pee first
Wait a minute, I'm not into that kinky stuff
Silly! Not on you! In toilets.
***, come with me
Okay
I thought you had to go pee
I don't
I *** *** do it on my bed, you know
Okay
Come here, *** *** ***
I want your cock in my pussy
Let's go to bedroom
No, I don't want to wait. Still right here.
What's that noise?
*** *** it
Pam? Where the hell are you?
What was that?
Oh my god it's my dad
*** you. Oh no, we don't have time, it's too late
Come in here. Hurry, hurry
It's kind of surprise that you called tonight
It was kind of short notice, I'm sorry
Hey, no, that's okay
You can call me anytime
Is this social or business?
Strictly social
It's been a long time since we've seen each other
It's probably nice to get
out of the house too
Does it show?
No and I could imagine that
your first day at the Brewster's could
be a little trying
Actually it hasn't been that bad
Vince is handling this whole thing very well
What does Vince have to complain about?
He's got two wives one cooks the other fucks
I'm sorry
it's okay. It's the truth
Gloria thinks I moved in to
steal Vince away from her
And she's right?
I don't think so
Did you call me tonight to prove to
Gloria that you weren't after Vince?
That's part of it. Are you angry with me?
No no, that's what I'm on earth for: to be
abused by beautiful women
What's the rest of it?
The other part of it is that I wanted
to be with somebody that I care a lot about
I feel comfortable with
So do you want to fuck?
Thanks I needed it
Thank you
Remember the first time you made love?
Yeah, you haven't ***
Force of habit
You're thinking of him now?
You really want to know?
Sure
He never entered my mind once
Vince *** is through. Done. Kaput.
You're still crazy about him
It's sure I am.
Stupid.
Hey look, Vince,
it's about last night with your ex-wife
Oh yeah,
You did do her the last night, didn't you?
Have any fun?
Of course no,
What kind of fun could I have with a
beautiful woman like Ellen?
You're still in love with her, right?
Me? Interested in Ellen? Don't be ridiculous
Okay so you don't mind me going out
with her, doing things with her?
Doing things with her?
No, of course not, Jerry
Good. I'm relieved to hear it
I sure if we talk
*** this afternoon if you want
I've got a better idea
You remember that old bar we used to go
to down by the beach?
Why don't we meet there say about seven o'clock?
Okay great
be just like old times, two of us
together, owling at the moon
Alright, I'll see you then
Thought I'd take a deep
Go ahead
Water is great. You should try it
No thanks. I can't swim
Oh well, in that case you should let me
teach you. Come on.
No
You don't trust me
Should I? If I drowned you'd have a clear
field with Vince
You know something?
You're absolutely right
Huh?
You and I, alone, here. All I have to do is
give you a push, into the water you go.
You'd swallow so much water you just be
gasping and kicking around you'd drown
like a rat
Don't worry sweetie,
I wouldn't dampen a single golden hair on
your precious head
ah
Come on, grab me.
Oh, it's okay sweetie
Sit down
Come on, let's go inside the house
Oh
I'll be alright
Yes I know you will
Shut up while I try *** here
Why are you doing this?
Because you're wet
If you don't dry you off
you catch pneumonia and then
I'll be stuck taking care of you
You saved my life
I think nothing of it
If it wasn't for me you've never fallen into
the swimming pool in the first place
Thank you
I'm sorry I guess I shouldn't have done that
I just wanted to thank you
What you say is a sad story Vince
*** got both the girls in the house
Just one big and happy family
I know. What am I gonna do?
I don't know Vince
I *** you gonna do
I don't know, I'm asking you
I listen but...
I'm a lawyer not a marriage counselor
I'll drink to that
- Let's drink ***
- I'll drink to that
You know something pal?
What's about buddy?
I have discovered something very important
Hey Vince, tell me something
Yeah
What is it you discovered so very important?
What's that?
Vince, you said you discovered something important
Oh yeah
I discovered that women are basically all alike
I have known that for years
and then they all got tits and pussy
There's more women than just tits and pussies, pal
You *** kinky I wanna guess
Take those two for example
Oh man if I do
So female
Why can't women be a little more like men, huh?
I don't know Vince
***
- Hey
- Yes, we are
Mind if we are joining you?
Hey, why? We found a ***?
Come on, sit down here
I couldn't help to hear your discussion about women
*** found it quite fascinating
Can we talk about you to ***?
That's right
Well, ***
Tell us something,
my buddy here says he thinks all women are
alike. What do you think about that?
Well, look around, I must guarantee there's not
another woman in the place like me, don't you think?
Yeah
I could be wrong
Why don't you guys come over to our place
for a little adventure?
What do you say Vince?
Now, I have nothing to do
- This is the life, no?
- Yep
No worries at all
Yeah, no wife, no ex-wife
Pretty good, huh, Vince?
Oh yeah
Of course you know Gloria
is no slouch in the cocksucking
- ***
- That's true
What do you mean "that's true"? How would you know?
I *** *** before you did
Oh yeah, that's right
Ellen's pretty good too
That's right
How would you rate her on a scale of 1 to 10?
Hmm... I guess I'd say
about seven and three-quarters
Seven and three quarters, huh?
That's all?
That's as far as my measuring stick goes
Now boys, let's have some real fun
No way
- ***
I really appreciate... this... this...
It's ok, buddy?
You're in no condition to drive
Okay, *** in the couch. Bye
Hey hey hey, wait a minute
This is a three bedrooms house
Oh yeah, well...
Gloria and I sleep one of the bedrooms
You wouldn't want to sleep with Gloria
and me would you?
No offense pal, but I
have no desire to sleep with you
I've my son Mark, he's sleeping in the other bedroom
You wouldn't sleep with Mark, would you?
Not if there's any other choice
Well I have
You're forgetting something
Forgetting something, What I forget?
The third bedroom
Oh yeah, well, Ellen's sleeping in the third bedroom
Exactly it
No no, you can't sleep there
Why not? You've done a hundred times
She's my wife
That's ***
I happen to be a lawyer and she happens to be your ex-wife
and I guess they wouldn't hit fucking ex-wife
in a world that I have fucked 100
Okay you can sleep with Ellen
You can't fuck her
Why not?
I'm still in love with her
Yeah? I see
- And you can't fuck Gloria
- Why?
'Cause I'm in love with her
Alright that's okay pal, we got a deal
- Okay
- Shhh
Gloria
Gloria? Are you alright?
Oh I feel wonderful
Oh shit you haven't been taking
those tranquilizers again, have you?
I had to. I was too excited to sleep
You know how they affect you
"Excited". What do you mean "excited"?
About Ellen being here
Yeah well we'll talk about that in the morning
She saved my life
That's nice
I was going down for the third
time and then she pulled me out
And then we came up here and we both
went down three times
Good night Gloria
Good night sweetheart
Pills. Always taking pills
I'm sorry Mark, I didn't know my dad was
gonna be home tonight too
No, it's okay. It's better here anyway
we won't be interrupted
Just be real quiet
- I don't want to wake up anybody
- Ok
***, give me a break
Kick you pants off, come on
Hurry up, I'm all ready
Why you hurry, we've got all night
We do. Alright.
Come here
Do I look nice?
You like that?
I do some work?
Are you alright?
Yeah I just have to go to the bathroom
Are you back
Wait, I gotta go to bathroom first
What again?
You know how I am
Just remember where we left off, okay?
- Yeah right
- I'll be right back
Oh, what was that?
Hey I told you I remembered where we left off
You know Vince, I'm sorry about calling
this a little doodoo. Actually it's a very
nice big doodoo
Oh peace say Gloria... Stop wandering
around and come on back to bed
Gloria
Ah, that's how I like it
It's great baby...
You're the best
Where have you been?
You won't believe me if I told you
What are you doing?
It's getting late, I've to go home
Oh ***
Oh I know...
We'll just have to do it some other time
Oh damn
Come on, I'll take you home
- Yeah, good morning
- Good morning
Hey Sugar
Why are you doing here? Where's Vince?
Vince just left for work
I feel so miserable Jerry
You shouldn't, baby. Take *** happy with that
I thought so too but I'm just kidding myself
He's a wonderful guy, he's a marvelous husband...
Hey you know something else: he's my best friend
But Jerry...
I don't love him... I love you, I should
have married you
Hey sweetheart, you didn't married me,
you married Vince. And you better get the
hell out of this room we'll talk about
this... ***... more rational moment
- Come on go out
- No
Rough night?
Huh yeah, what I can remember of it
Jerry's still upstairs in bed
Yeah, guess I'll let him sleep it off
He might be. Generous of you
Yeah look, I'm sorry about that
It was his idea
I wanted to sack out in the couch
I didn't even know he was in bed with me
Is Gloria up here?
Oh yes
Where's Mark?
Oh he left already
He said he had an appointment
I think he has a girlfriend
Oh...
Just like old times, isn't it?
Not quite like old times, Vince
Back in those days we never knew where
our next meal was coming from
Yeah. We were happy
We were happy, don't we Ellen?
Yeah, I thought so
Where'd we go wrong?
We didn't go wrong. I was the one who went wrong
I was a bossy nagging wife
You are gonna tell me I'm wrong don't you?
No. You are bossy nagging wife
But it's what I needed
you gave me the boost that I needed Ellen
Yeah, I gave you a boost right into another woman's arms
I guess I hurt you more than I should have
Yeah, you shouldn't have hurt me so much
That's okay, I got over it
Did you?
You'd better go to work
Okay
Hello?
Ellen?
Ellen, this is Vince
Ellen I don't... It's about time I started doing
things right
I love you and I want to marry you again
What the hell... I have something to say about this?
No. I mean, yes. I mean...
Well, what about Gloria?
Gloria doesn't love me
she loves Jerry. Always has.
And Jerry loves her
Well, why don't you come home?
We can talk about it then
Okay Baby
Okay
I think we're all gonna need the
services of a good attorney