[Music]
[Applause]
and there she was my laundry angel sent
from above to make the long tedious
hours spent in this dismal place just a
little bit more bearable gorgeous sexy
smart funny
she was all that and more
[Music]
perfect in every way damn it Oh
I don't believe this not again
okay who did it who stole my underwear
was it you
no no no I guess not
man this is really starting to piss me
off
if I catch that little I'm gonna kill
him all right well on that note I think
I'm going to get out of here before you
start talking strip-searched that that
doesn't sound like fun but it is laundry
day and I got my ugly fish on the ground
and that's definitely not for Mexico
good luck finding your panties
Oh
it was kind of nice meeting Scott
Christine
yeah sorry about the panties dealing
thing
and that's how we met Scott I mean not
Ralphy the sniffer that's a whole nother
story but I'll get to that later
fish underwear huh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my god I can't believe you're still
in bed get up you lazy beast I've
already done like three loads of laundry
[Applause]
speaking of loads uh you are disgusting
besides that's not for me that's for
whatever little tramp you were just
dreaming about come on baby you know I'm
only dreaming about you
Yeah right no seriously you were um at
the laundromat
two new clothes uh-huh and the machine
was busted so everything was still
soaking wet
[Music]
[Applause]
so um the t-shirt got wet as you're
pulling them out made those nipples
stand up nice and high yeah you can see
your nipples kind of right through your
shirt kind of poking out man it was hot
[Music]
look around see no one
[Applause]
[Music]
you are allows milliner
to show me how hard those nipples stand
up babe
[Music]
[Applause]
sperm
[Music]
[Applause]
Hey
[Music]
Ernie
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah
ah
Oh
[Music]
oh yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
yes
yeah
[Music]
ah
oh yeah
oh yeah that's it right there
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
oh yeah
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah oh
parts of my company
yeah
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
what are these
looks like panties to me yeah dumb shit
I know whose are they I don't know what
they are no my red panties mysteriously
disappeared again Adam I'm going to ask
you this one more time whose are these
and how the fuck did they get under
there but like I said I don't know like
I said you're a lousy liar you know what
I've had enough of you why don't you
pack up your shit and get out well but
well what am I supposed to go what about
me I don't care why don't you move in
with Little Miss panties there come on
Chris don't be like this
quit yakking and start packing what
you've got my back Chris and just like
that
he was gone and I was single I almost
forgot what it felt like the thought of
being on my own
meeting new people it's kind of exciting
and one of the things I was most excited
about was seeing Scott again sounds
weird but I couldn't wait for laundry
day and there she was again the laundry
mat was quickly becoming my favorite
place to be but every time I saw her I I
just got so nervous I didn't know what
to say or do I mean come on the first
time I ever saw her I told her about my
fish underwear what was I thinking why
couldn't I just be calm and cool why
couldn't I just walk up to her grab her
kiss her
fuck it Danny why not I mean what's the
worst that could happen
[Music]
or what are you doing perhaps a more
subtle approach hey there how about you
and me hooking up maybe a little dancing
a little romancing what do you say yeah
[Music]
okay so maybe that wasn't such a great
idea
but I mean how was I supposed to know
she didn't like me maybe maybe she
doesn't like guys at all maybe she's
just getting out of a horrible
relationship and has sworn off men for
good yeah that's it she's gonna switch
sides and become a lesbian yeah a
lesbian a hot sweaty hard-bodied
lipstick lesbian she came to the laundry
mat to stalk her prey toying with them
teasing them there's no stopping this
insatiable Beast she wants only one
thing to feed on female flesh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
Oh
[Music]
yeah
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
what the fuck you do or what the fuck
doesn't work what you mean doesn't work
just machine work let me show you
something these machines look at
machines they aren't for a cop machines
versus machine works
this machine is like lady lady like this
it is not is the lock lock lock lock
lock is hitch it go from hold to for
caught for conform conform code form
coke look lady you see don't hit machine
you hit the machine I hate you
hey lady let's try this again shall we
and remember be cool and don't do or say
anything stupid
Oh boxers I guess they're your
boyfriend's no actually I just became a
single oh good good I mean not so good
for him but good for me at least I hope
so
this night and seeing you around and
that you were cute and I was just
wondering maybe you could give me a
number we I could call you sometime we
would go out have some fun yeah sure why
not cool I got a pen paper
now remember I need my beauty sleep so
no calls before 10:00 no cause after
10:00 got that feel
[Applause]
you're not a stalker are you there's
that one restraining honor I don't like
to talk about that very funny I'll talk
to you later
[Music]
don't be a pussy don't people see don't
be a pussy
you can do this man you can do this
oh man what if she's changed her mind
what is she still sleeping well worse
yet what if she got back with her
boyfriend maybe I should just hang up
yeah I mean she's probably not home
anyway just just hang out Pam
[Music]
got a callback yeah
come on think of something witty I know
you can do this hello hey how you doing
it's Scott
oh hey was that you that just called and
hung up yeah
my cellphones it's crapping out nobody's
damn cell phones yeah I know so what
time is it anyway
it's 10:01 I didn't mean to wake ya
sorry no that's okay I did say 10 to 10
I just didn't think you'd be so punctual
so what's up
hello I know you did not just call and
wake me up to do the heavy breathing
thing hello you know what either Hey oh
there you're hey sorry about that life
my phone isn't working for shit yeah now
what were you saying something about
heavy breathing I kind of like the south
of that uh well racy for a first phone
call but hey whatever flex your buckle
who's gonna start me okay um let's see
what are you wearing oh you are a little
freak aren't you okay I'll play along
I'm wearing my school girls skirts I
like that I saw that your basket the
other day
okay if this is going to work you just
need to stop talking you're starting to
weird me out okay okay it's all you good
where to begin
the place is deserted
[Music]
there's a warm breeze coming from the
machine
the clothes are going around and around
the rhythm is mesmerizing I'm starting
to get so hot
[Music]
and then I feel your touch
it sends a shiver through me
[Music]
and then
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
what's that beep what's that beeping on
a second
hello oh hey mom yeah hold on I'm on the
other line okay hold on I'll be right
back sorry uh listen that's my mom on
the other line I promised her we get
together for lunch today so I gotta go
no no no no don't know somehow you were
doing so good I gotta go
you can't leave me like this look I've
really got to go and besides I just
can't have phone sex with my mom on the
other line it's just creepy this this
just isn't fair I know it's not I'll owe
you one and you can finish the job I
have full faith in you and remember I
swallow
Swallow huh
[Applause]
[Music]
okay oh hey been here long
no just to start have you been
okay good in you well you know same old
same old laundry day
laundry name yeah laundry day
nice work that English Lit thing's
really paying off oh man you are such a
doofus I mean how long cool can you be
she is so out of your league just look
at him he's so cute
and he even separates his colors just
look at her she is so hot
look at those panties come on dude go
for it come on ask her out I wish she'd
just asked me out and I wonder why he
never called me back come on don't be a
pussy ask her out go ahead no you go
first uh I'll just wondering what you
were doing tonight maybe we could go
ahead and do something
yeah you're right you you probably
already have other class maybe some
other time
no it's okay I was just gonna ask you
why you never called me back that first
phone call was kind of fun you don't
know how about I wanted to and you're
not gonna believe this but I swear it's
the truth
I got a roommate named Tommy he's got a
girlfriend
and she always thinks he's too messy so
she picks up after more once well this
week it was laundry my stuff got mixed
up with his stuff
that's what happened oh you see the
number was in the jeans she wanted the
jeans and before I knew it that the
number had disappeared yeah at that old
story I swear it's the truth
give me it again I'll call you I don't
know
come on give a guy a break we'll go out
well fine you are a toughy what why do I
got a deal I'll do anything anything
okay we'll see how bad you want it
here's my address
if you're a good boy get the phone
number later later
later say a dish deal lights and darks
in cold colors in warm so the dryer on
low don't breathe the fabric softener oh
and keep an eye on my panties
keep an eye on the panty you can do that
and that was how it started
nothing really romantic or anything just
short sweetened to the point with the
touch of sarcasm
at the park I say huh no customer no
bathroom Jesus man look I'll pay
Baburam for customer only no laundry no
customer a bathroom do you believe this
guy
come on just let me as a bathroom sure
and let him use bathroom the next guy
use bathroom then bomb down three he was
bathroom
pretty soon half of Los Angeles won't do
piece in my bathroom we're going to
cleaner Europe
you know you know cleaned and a clean
tear you clean no customer no bathroom
[Applause]
may I
then
there I'm a customer yeah now he's a
customer no I am so sorry to tell you
you must read other sign no shirt no
shoes no service no customer
go ahead I will laughs a promise
[Applause]
be sure to wash those hands real good
hey let me do it did you say Oh jack
it's the shirt
[Music]
[Applause]
Wow
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Wow you look amazing
so how did it go good good shrink
anything lose any panties no all present
accounted for did you sniff any of them
uh no but I really like those black
fairly ones on the top there really
since you're such a good boy
[Applause]
better uh yeah is this this mean I get
my date now or are you hoping for no
panties so let me get this straight
you've never heard a lot of sock theory
I mean it's move in fact a fancy
university did a whole study on it okay
all socks come in pairs right what about
ten packs even those they may start off
as ten singles but you know mysteriously
unpredictably they end up in pairs and I
mean there's no rhyme or reason no
pre-planned process they just end up in
pairs and stay in pairs
the last sock theory exactly well people
who just like socks they don't think
they found that perfect mate that pair
until the unthinkable happen they break
up but people break up every day yeah
and lots of socks go missing I mean you
know what the statistics there um no but
when people break up they have good
reasons I mean it's not like some big
cosmic mystery or anything yes sometimes
like sometimes the missing sock simply
fell out of the basket but what about
the rest of the time okay nobody reached
in the Machine and stolen the dryer
didn't eat it I mean a soft just simply
disappears like the love sometimes love
just disappears there's no notice or
warning to simply God
Wow that's really deep
so then the poor lost Lovelace sock just
wanders around trying to find its mate
well that's one theory
me personally I think there's a big sock
swinger party that old single socks hang
out at and trying to get lucky you're
good he really was he was cute funny
kind of smart but it was more than that
I couldn't quite put my finger on it yet
but there was definitely something as
much as I'd like to invite you in I
can't it's that the whole first date
thing
first a thing right yeah well you know
technically you can all that time we've
spent talking in the laundry huh
I mean we easily got two maybe three
dates under our belt nice try but no and
what about that whole IOU thing for that
whole phone sex fiasco I mean it's a
perfect time to cash that in now you're
so cute okay but you better be a good
kisser
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
fucking swamp
[Applause]
yeah here
[Music]
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
oh yeah
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
fuck you
here comes beautiful
[Applause]
[Music]
all right swap their chocolate
mmm that was nice
well at least he didn't suck in bed
that's always good he didn't mind eating
pussy and he had a really nice cock he
talked a little too much during sex but
I can probably break him a bat all right
I didn't suck I was actually kind of a
stud right on look at her man she is hot
and you just fucked her who's the man
thank God I didn't wear the fish
underwear
[Music]
what a nice girl like you're doing place
like this my laundry so go away oh come
on don't be that way and they can help
you with pain if you let him oh come on
can't be that bad
can't be that bad no I am stuck putting
my expensive clothes and these filthy
machines that I've had God knows whose
laundry ennum why why you ask because my
goddamn asshole ex-husband by man let
her have fishing woman like you'll do
his laundry he's got his clothes they're
mine and anyway that's not the point
I shouldn't be doing anyone's laundry
the only reason I'm stuck having to
stoop to this level is cuz my goddamn
asshole husband can't keep his hands off
big titty bond little girls and
unfortunately by the time I figured it
out and had had enough his crack team
lawyers make it where I walked away with
nothing
left me penniless with nothing but my
clothes out of my walk-in closet goddamn
prenups what has brains to appreciate
young girls good to look at but nothing
compares
every woman you are ravishing woman what
do we have here
oh I just found this on the floor you
mister drop him no excuse please
oh my god red-handed phone is on the
floor oh yeah what are these that did
not kill you you don't do this
don't you come back at you
fucking bad events very good WordGirl
what's going on
I got the Baggies dealer I'm sorry I
missed all the excitement
okay so I was following him around to
all the dryers and stuff it was pulling
them out and putting them in his pocket
and then I put my arm around his neck a
knife your nose right not even and go
ahead you are so cute
[Laughter]
that Berkeley you were being smart about
the from it
Oh your words they cut like naive yeah
we'll get used to it
perhaps I see you later yeah such venom
I like it hey hey jerk-off machine
that's the thanks I get
crime fighting business is a thankless
job do you want to start it uh yeah sure
oh my god Scott is that you Julia mmm
it's so good to see you can't believe
this I just been back into town and
you're like the first person I ran into
what are the odds of the hat yeah what
what are the odds
well we should get together and see if
the old flames still there huh uh yeah
well we'll see okay I'm Stan my mom's
just ill have a number yeah yeah oh oh
oh my god I can't believe this Wow
see ya call me okay yeah bye bye
I've seen I can explain all that save it
don't be like that
see you later call me bye Christine wait
don't I don't want to hear that how
overreacting and being stupid I don't
want to hear any of your bullshit
excuses unfortunately I've already heard
them I just got out of a relationship
with a cheating prick I don't want
another one
bye Christine of all the luck that chica
hadn't seen in like two years shows up
at my laundry mat and then start
smacking on me this is bad
are you gonna fix this one Scotty me boy
I figured I'd give her a little time to
cool down but a week had passed now and
she still hadn't returned any of my
calls
she hadn't been in a laundromat either
I've been waiting around since 8:00 in
the morning it's now 9:30
I guess it's officially time to give up
man how time flies when you're miserable
oh man
hope this comes out I am now that stuff
usually doesn't come out very easy my
watch I be a little more careful shut up
so do you even know whose DNA that is I
will shut up it's that guy Steve from
remember we met him on Friday at the bar
I think his name was Steve I think his
name was Steve hmm
oh honey you're not a slut you're just a
very friendly girl okay I'm Allie
uh I leave you with your stain and I
will call you tomorrow
you suck I'll say if you really want me
to no it's okay you can go okay bye okay
bye
oh yeah alone at last
[Music]
[Applause]
okay so on a slut
[Music]
oh yeah come on spin cycle
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
Oh
[Music]
now I can see why our machines are
breaking down all the time you're trying
to make me rich
[Applause]
no these machines aren't really designed
for that I'm so embarrassed
well certainly not gonna tell anyone I'm
not gonna stop you I'll be by our little
secret
what can I tell anyone
well a couple guys down at the dryer
repair shop but they wouldn't believe me
anyway
it's about closing time look ahead like
this door and keep you from me to stern
are you sure you're not gonna tell
anyone now so okay
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
huh
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
we love the floor to make some I love
the floor then we parked our army more
but the fucking what the fuck is this
shit
who've been talking here is that dog oh
yes it's dog what does it look like to
you look like Russian or that pretty
baby mom what you don't like dogs
Oh No Dante love dog dog love something
just don't like sheet on floor
Oh would she you had a poopoo bad butchy
bad Buchi bag I'm sorry is there
anything I can do to make it up to you
well maybe you have dinner with Dante
wow I've never seen him like anybody
good you go jump on Jojo good good how
can I say no after that usually he snaps
and snarls at everyone good
would you have big breath poor little
dog well it's date then I promise you
won't be disappointed
but they has much to offer right woman
you worry about money no more than damn
hard money 12 laundromats I take care of
you don't worry
well okay when would you like to go how
we leave now fuck the laundry we come
back for it later come
okay Sunday north will you take care of
girly off machine
[Applause]
hey hey so you know that cute guy that
was here last Sunday have you seen him
around you mean the one that you were
kissing oh yeah isn't Scott no I really
haven't seen very much him at all lately
why how do you know him well
we used to date a long time ago and then
I moved away and I thought into him last
week and I was hoping to hook up with
him but but what I never heard from him
never called so I was wondering if you'd
seen him how do you know him
did he ever tell you about the fish
underwear the one oh my god where does
he live uh he used to live at 116 Oak
Street apartment um 304 I think okay why
[Applause]
what an idiot I am I knew better than
this you can't let one bad relationship
ruin all the rest you can't throw almond
into the asshole pool well you probably
could but you have to keep an eye out
for the nice ones that float to the top
you better think of something really
good if you're gonna get this one back
[Music]
[Applause]
hey so do you believe all that stuff
about the lost sock theory yeah yeah I
guess I did
sure good because we couldn't buy this
manner
[Applause]
the last sock theory who would have
thought what you don't want to see Dante
Fox are for each girl it is your loss
she's one hot piece of ass
[Music]
pet the dog trick it worked every time
you're like he helped and
five days cock has been called
meaningful
magic huge
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
ah
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
I know
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
Oh
[Applause]
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh fuck
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh
[Music]
[Applause]
whoa
[Music]
[Applause]
huh
[Music]
[Applause]
you are excellent cocksucker
[Music]
[Laughter]