so you having a good time you look great
tonight
it must be the pizza Oh start
really Jake another party it's not just
another party so Lou
come on trying to get some rest
don't tell me you're trying to go to bed
at nine o'clock off Friday come on in
I'll make your drink and keep the little
umbrella and everything that's a beach
in here Jake I'm serious
so am i I literally have a beach in my
kitchen I know this really good Santa
look just try not to get so drunk that
you forget to come fix my sink again
tomorrow
come on have I ever let you down you
really don't want me to answer it was
four years ago bobbles he's in a better
place now
goodnight you later
so where were we
mmm coffee smells good doesn't it tastes
even better
I should about do it don't tell me you
really read this I would expect you to
appreciate a love story well especially
when that doesn't involve body shots and
edible underwear see that's where you
got me all wrong I drink beer and I
don't wear underwear
look
Oh
oh my god
ah
Oh
[Laughter]
I can take this
Oh
every inch the fucking oh that's good
[Laughter]
Emma oh nothing
having a little breakfast in bed course
I didn't forget dad's 50th birthday no
no you do not need to invite a nice girl
from church who no mom do not invite her
oh because well I'm gonna invite my
girlfriend
what's a mom you have a horrible
reception I I can't I can't hear you
shit shit you didn't tell me you had a
girlfriend what I a donuts
that's my mom wait do you wanna be my
girlfriend excuse me
do you want to be my girlfriend and go
meet my parents look Jack it's Jake
right Jake
I just don't think I'm ready for all
that you know commitment commitment I
don't want you to be my real girlfriend
oh so I'm not good enough to be your
real girlfriends sandy wait here's an
idea why don't you fuck yourself Jack
it's Jake
Oh quite the ladies man huh so who's
your neighbor
uh that was Jake that's Jake the one
you're always complaining about yeah why
he never said he was so cute well yeah I
guess he does have that boyish charm
thing working for him what oh my god
you like him I do not yes you do I've
seen that look before
oh really and when was that mr.
smartypants
the guy that worked at the coffee shop
on Fifth Street I had a crush on that
guy
precisely okay well if you don't like
him then you won't mind if I ask him out
I thought you decided to become a
lesbian that was just a phase a phase
what about Heather now she wasn't
serious and really because that looks
pretty serious to me sherry or door
whazzup oh my god
oh my eyes oh really
no bye I'm good thanks
ah
oh yes
everyone Shiva nice and fucking what
hello
oh my God he's fucking kidding me
oh my god
yeah
Oh
yeah fingers deep inside your pussy
oh yeah
fuck it
well that will teach you to knock next
time well most people lock the front
door before getting freaky on the sofa
what if I've been the postman or
something where do I ask you in oh god
you're such a perv which brings me back
to the topic at hand can I ask Jake out
no why not because because yeah that's
what I thought
besides don't you have a date with your
boyfriend well I wouldn't call it a date
he's not my boyfriend but I thought you
said he was perfect for you he is then
what's the problem
I don't know well I think I know I think
you have a crush on someone else hello
Lisa
hello Anna come on I just really really
need this favor I know I said I'd call
but hey Beth it's Jake
oh you're married hey Carly how you been
a lesbian Stacy Stacy there's no reason
to be hostile I'm calling now hate me
but hates such a strong word I said I
was sorry
hey Jake expecting a hot date actually
yes yes I am
let me guess mr. sweater vest your new
boyfriend his name is Thomas and he's
not my boyfriend
I'm sorry did you need something yes I
need a favor a really big favor will you
be my girlfriend
what look let me pay you $200 to come to
our parents place and pretend to be my
girlfriend
what the hell are you still drunk look I
told my mom I have a girlfriend and I
got to go to my dad's 50th birthday
party and I don't have a girlfriend
called she's girls I hang out with
sometimes but none of them are really
girlfriend of all except for Tina she's
just about perfect but she has this one
metal toe it's like so much long on the
other one but no I'm really scared
because my mom's gonna try to set me up
with these church ladies and my dad's
gonna yell at me because I upset my mom
and it's really can you take this $200
huh else I'm really screwed oh here's my
de 250 no chick beautiful Thank You
Thomas Jake okay
hope you're hungry punished to 50 and
gift certificate Carlos Oh Charlies
chili factory is that a maybe
Wow my compliments to the chef
really how's the new recipe those a
little nervous to try it out really
Marissa it was fantastic
thank you would you like some more wine
oh no no more for me thank you
oh let me help you up
would you like some dessert yeah you
could sit out
Oh
oh my god
god
just like
yeah
[Laughter]
similar word for a bowl of develop
what's more you neighbor this afternoon
seemed a little frazzled he was trying
to talk me into being his date for his
dad's party actually he was trying to
pay me to be his date he's made the same
guy that has a girl every night yeah huh
well I guess being a pig just come up
with him then didn't it was that
supposed to mean no play woman's
emotions I mean going it alone Spacek
coma I've known Jake since we were
freshmen in college and I would hardly
consider him a pig a bit misguided maybe
but certainly not a bad guy I mean last
spring when I broke my foot he brought
me food every day and he's always fixing
my sink with my stupid little pick up
his phone
okay sorry I didn't mean to make you
defensive I'm not defensive clearly
are you fucking kidding me
a crossword puzzle yep who the fuck
brings a crossword puzzle to a girl's
house and actually works on it on their
first night together which is exactly
why I asked him to leave look that in
the snoring I mean he sounded like a
grizzly bear with sleep apnea my god
well this frees you up to take hot
neighbor boy up on his offer I knew I
shouldn't have told you about that come
on what have you got to lose you should
totally go I can tell you're thinking
about it besides my birthday is next
week and you could totally buy me a
kick-ass birthday present with the bribe
money bitch I know but you love me yeah
yeah
Marissa let me just say me nicely what
ask me nicely to pretend to date you and
meet your parents and make it good
you're serious deadly
will you be my date and go me my parents
that's the best you can do if you do
better than that Russell will you please
be my date and come with me to my dad's
birthday party come on put the feeling
behind it you're enjoying this aren't
you
Oh more they'll ever know fine
Marisa will you please do me the honor
of accompanying me it's my father's
birthday party and pretend to be my
girlfriend
hmm okay oka oh my God thank you
but it's $500 and I'm gonna need the
check in advance here we are
we're nervous
hey long it's nice to meet you Miller -
pleasure
please call me Diane and this is Bob hi
such a pleasure to meet you see Tino did
you have a long trip yeah thirsty need
something
yeah are you hungry come sure thank you
hey mom have you noticed we don't have a
butler get the bags
good to see you guys - so this is the
guest room there's extra blankets in the
closet and I put out fresh towels in the
bathroom thank you isn't this just cozy
honey well let you two get settled and
get ready for the party tonight is there
anything else you need okay so do you
want the left side or the right side of
bed
I mean I'm a more of a left side kind of
guy but I'm also a giver so if you want
the left side of the bed I'm totally
good we are so not sleeping together but
you could sleep on the floor
fuck that for five hundred bucks you can
sleep on the floor I in bed well if
you'll excuse me I'm gonna go take a
shower and get ready for the party
okay honey I'll meet you downstairs stop
calling me honey okay muffin
oh I have to tell you how pleased Bob
and I are the Jake found such a nice
girl he was just going on and on about
you you should have seen the girl he
brought the last time I would swear that
he paid her really
now we think he hired her from some
escort service or something probably
just to get a rise out of me
Jake hasn't had any serious dating since
Hillary his high school sweetheart
this is Jake's girlfriend Marisa I'm
Marissa this is Jake's sister Joanna
jake has a girlfriends I said the same
thing well it's a pleasure to meet you
you too so how was Europe well I brought
back a souvenir this is Sasha hi nice to
meet you no you clean up well oh my god
Jake is that you this is so nice to see
you
it's good to see you too huh have you
been I think good really good so uh what
are you doing here Oh your mom invited
me weeks ago of course she did Oh
Marissa this is Hilary Hilary Martha oh
sorry to interrupt
Marisa there's someone I want you to be
so have you been I mean good yeah I have
to tell you you look really amazing
thank you said yeah so when you say you
and her date our friends what kind of
friends are you
well she's my neighbor and she used to
type a friend that charged me 500 bucks
to pretend to be my girlfriend well it
was so nice to meet you nice to meet you
too
keep an eye on that one I never liked
that bitch she may fool my parents but I
know a gold digger when I see one
she hasn't changed since high school
she's only perfected her craft
I like that idea
excuse me
- gather in you
oh I hope you sorry it's just me you
know I think it's really cool what
you're going to help out Jake what do
you mean he told me everything I
personally wouldn't have held out for
$500 though oh and you can have the bed
actually you can have the whole guest
room all to yourself you don't have to
thank me
I'll be right excuse me
oh there you are come on it's time to
sing to your dad
you
[Laughter]
Marisa
what are you doing what does it look
like I'm doing I'm leaving I already
called the car service
why cuz you're an asshole
we can't believe you told Hillary about
our deal and why so you could get some
ass tonight
you made me look like a hooker no you
you're misunderstanding really so you
didn't tell Hillary that you paid me to
be here
I well yes but it's not what I meant
look I try to do favor obviously it was
a big mistake
what did you do what well I just thought
the woman that you're in love with into
her car leave in love with I don't think
so don't even try it you're my brother
I know you burn anyone and I've never
seen you look at someone the way you
look at Marissa you're mistaken
she's not even my real girlfriend she's
my next-door neighbor and up here - come
here why would you do that to get mom
off my back oh that's funny
well it doesn't change the fact they're
crazy better and she's crazy about you -
you don't know you're talking about she
told me to give you this
there you are
it's wondering where you ran off to I
can't talk right now who said anything
about talking right because you've done
just about enough of that haven't you
is where the fuck do you get off on
telling Marisa what I said Oh Jake
didn't mean to of course you did you
exactly what you're doing you're
vindictive bitch you always have been
oh wow just wow how dare you attack me
when you're so fucking pathetic you have
to pay some chick to go out with you
Marissa's not just some chick she's my
friend and I happened to be in love with
her I'm in love with her
I'm completely utterly in love again
congratulations I'm so happy for you
did you meet on that what are you doing
here I mean I thought you left
forgot my purse so did you every word do
you still think I'm an asshole
absolutely listen I'm really sorry I
mean it's just that shut up
you should
let me get ya
Oh
fuck
fucking come
yeah
Oh fuckin good
Oh God look it like
fucking car yeah
Oh
yeah
yeah fuck me
Oh
yeah
so you forgive me still want to go shoe
shopping
Oh what if I were so nervous