so you having a good time I'm not great
you look great tonight
there must be the pizza Oh start
really Jake another party it's not just
another party luau
come on trying to get some rest
don't tell me you're trying to go to bed
at 9 o'clock on Friday come on in
I like your drink and please the little
umbrella and everything I've some beach
in here Jake I'm serious
so am i I literally have a beach in my
kitchen I know this really good sanur
look just try not to get so drunk that
you forget to come fix my sink again
tomorrow
come on have I ever let you down you
really don't want me to answer that was
four years ago bobbles he's in a better
place now goodnight you later
so where were we
mmm that coffee smells good doesn't it
tastes even better
I should about do it
don't tell me you really read this I
would expect you to appreciate a love
story well especially when that doesn't
involve body shots and edible underwear
see that's where you got me all wrong I
drink beer and I don't wear underwear
look
Oh
please
oh my god
Oh
ah
hey whoa oh nothing
having a little breakfast in bed course
I didn't forget dad's 50th birthday no
no you do not need to invite a nice girl
from church who mom do not invite her oh
because well I'm gonna invite my
girlfriend what's a mom you have a
horrible reception I I can't I can't
hear you
shit shit you didn't tell me you had a
girlfriend
what hey I don't that's my mom wait do
you wanna be my girlfriend
excuse me got it do you want to be my
girlfriend and go meet my parents
look Jack it's Jake right Jake I just
don't think I'm ready for all that
you know commitment commitment I don't
want you to be my real girlfriend oh so
I'm not good enough to be your real
girlfriends sandy wait here's an idea
why don't you fuck yourself Jack it's
Jay oh quit the ladies man huh
so who's your neighbor uh that was Jake
that's Jake the one you're always
complaining about yeah why he never said
he was so cute well yeah I guess he does
have the boyish charm thing working for
him
what oh my god you like him
I do not yes you do
I've seen that look before oh really
and when was that miss smartypants the
guy that worked at the coffee shop on
Fifth Street had a crush on that guy
precisely okay well if you don't like
him then you won't mind if I ask him out
I thought you decided to become a
lesbian that was just a phase a phase
what about Heather how she wasn't
serious and really because that looks
pretty serious to me
Sherri your door was up oh my god oh my
eyes oh really
no bye I'm good thanks
ah
oh yes it Oliver one Shiva nice and
fucking lip
fucking
hello
fucking feeling so fucking deep oh my
god are you fucking kidding me
oh my god
yeah
Oh
if you just being inside please
okay fucking time fucking fucking
fucking conjuring in your mouth fingers
deep inside your pussy
pardon us oh yeah
fucking sweet little oh my god
well that will teach you to knock next
time well most people lock the front
door before getting freaky on the sofa
what if I been the postman or something
where do I asked you in oh god you're
such a perv which brings me back to the
topic at hand can I ask Jake out no why
not because because yeah that's what I
have thought besides don't you have a
date with your boyfriend well I wouldn't
call it a date he's not my boyfriend but
I thought you said he was perfect for
you he is then what's the problem I
don't know well I think I know I think
you have a crush on someone else
hello Lisa
hello Anna come on I just really really
need this favor I know I said I'd call
but hey Beth it's Jake
oh you're married hey Carly how you been
a lesbian Stacy Stacy there's no reason
to be hostile I'm calling now hate me
but hates such a strong word
I saw how sorry
hey Jake expecting a hot date actually
yes yes I am
let me guess mr. sweater vest your new
boyfriend his name is Thomas and he's
not my boyfriend
I'm sorry did you need something yes I
need a favor a really big favor
good will you be my girlfriend
what look let me pay you $200 to come to
our parents place and pretend to be my
girlfriend the hell are you still drunk
look I told my mom I have a girlfriend
and I got to go to my dad's 50th
birthday party and I don't have a
girlfriend
all these girls I hang out with
sometimes but none of them are really
girlfriend a bull
except for Tina she's just about perfect
but she has this one metal toe aside so
much longer than the other one but no
I'm really scared because my mom's gonna
try to set me up with these church
ladies and my dad's gonna yell at me
because I upset my mom and it's really
gonna take this $200 huh else I'm really
screwed ah here's my de 250 no Jake oh
it's beautiful thank you Thomas
Jake Jake okay okay hungry punished 250
and gift certificate Carlos Oh Charlies
chili factory is that a maybe
Wow my compliments to the chef
really yes it was the new recipe I was a
little nervous to try it out really
Marissa was fantastic thank you
would you like some more wine oh no no
way thank you oh let me help you back
would you like some dessert
yeah you could sign up
Oh
yeah
just like
[Laughter]
seven little word for a bowl of develop
what's more your neighbor this afternoon
it seemed a little frazzled he was
trying to talk me into being his date
for his dad's party actually he was
trying to pay me to be his date he's
made the same guy that has a girl ever
Bernard yeah huh well I guess being a
pig just come up with him then didn't it
was that supposed to me well playing
with woman's emotions I mean go to that
ballon Spacek coma I've known Jake since
we were freshmen in college and I would
hardly consider him a pig a bit
misguided maybe but certainly not a bad
guy I mean last spring when it broke my
foot he brought me food every day and
he's always fixing my sink my stupid
little pick up his phone
okay sorry I didn't mean to make you
defensive I'm not defensive clearly
are you fucking kidding me
a crossword puzzle yep who the fuck
brings a crossword puzzle to a girl's
house and actually works on it on their
first night together which is exactly
why I asked him to leave look that in
the snoring I mean he sounded like a
grizzly bear with sleep apnea my god
well this frees you up to take hot
neighbor boy up on his offer I knew I
shouldn't I told you about that come on
what have you got to lose you should
totally go I can tell you're thinking
about it besides my birthday is next
week and you could totally buy me a
kick-ass birthday present with the bribe
money such a bitch I know but you love
me yeah yeah Lissa let me just say let's
green Eisley what ask me nicely to
pretend to date you and meet your
parents and make it good you're serious
deadly
will you be my date and going my parents
that's the best you can do if you do
better than that
Russell will you please be my date and
come with me to my dad's birthday party
come on put the feeling behind it you're
enjoying this aren't you
Oh more they'll ever know fine
Marisa will you please do me the honor
of accompanying me to my father's
birthday party and pretend to be my
girlfriend
hmm okay Coco oh my god thank you
but it's $500 and I'm gonna need the
check in advance here we are
we nervous hey it's nice to meet Miller
- pleasure
please call me Diane and this is Bob hi
hi such a pleasure to meet you he knows
you have a long trip
hey thirst you need something yeah are
you hungry
okay sure thank you hey mom if you
noticed we don't have a butler get the
bags
good to see you guys - so this is the
guest room there's extra blankets in the
closet and I put out fresh towels in the
bathroom thank you isn't this just cozy
honey well let you two get settled and
get ready for the party tonight is there
anything else you need okay so do you
want the left side or the right side of
bed
I mean I'm a more of a left side kind of
guy but I'm also a giver so if you want
the left side of the bed totally good we
are so not sleeping together but you
could sleep on the floor
fuck that for five hundred bucks you
could sleep on the floor I in bed well
if you'll excuse me I'm gonna go take a
shower and get ready for the pub okay
honey I'll meet you downstairs stop
calling me honey
okay muffin
oh I have to tell you how pleased Bob
and I are the cheek found such a nice
girl he was just going on and on about
you you should have seen the girl he
brought the last time I would swear that
he paid her really
now we think he hired her from some
escort service or something probably
just to get a rise out of me
Jake hasn't had any serious dating since
Hillary his high school sweetheart
this is Jake's girlfriend Marisa I'm
Marissa this is Jake's sister Johanna
Jake has a girlfriends I said the same
thing well it's a pleasure to meet you
you too so how was Europe well I brought
back a souvenir this is Sasha hi nice to
meet you no you clean up well
funny I was just gonna say anything
about you oh my god Jake is that you
this is so nice to see you
it's good to see you too huh have you
been I think good really good so uh what
are you doing here Oh your mom invited
me weeks ago of course she did Oh
Marissa this is Hillary Hillary Nessa
oh sorry to interrupt
Marisa there's someone I want you to be
so how have you been I mean good yeah I
have to tell you you look really amazing
thank you said yeah
so when you say hundred eight our
friends what kind of friends are you
well she's my neighbor and she used to
type a friend that charged me 500 bucks
to pretend to be my girlfriend well it
was so nice to meet you nice to meet you
keep an eye on that one I never liked
that bitch she may fool my parents but I
know gold digger when I see one
she hasn't changed since high school
she's only perfected her craft
I like that idea
excuse me
okay together continue
oh you sorry
it's just me you know I think it's
really cool what you're doing to help
out Jake
what do you mean Shh he told me
everything I personally wouldn't have
held out for $500 though oh and you can
have the bed actually you can have the
whole guest room all to yourself you
don't have to thank me I'll be right
back excuse me
oh there you are come on it's time to
sing to your dad
[Laughter]
Marisa
what are you doing what does it look
like I'm doing I'm leaving I already
called the car service
why cuz you're an asshole
we can't believe you told Hilary about
our deal my sticky get some ass tonight
you made me look like a hooker no you
you're misunderstanding really so you
didn't tell Hillary that you pay me to
be here
I well yes but it's not what I meant
look I tried to do a favor
obviously it was a big mistake
what did you do what well I just thought
the woman that you're in love with into
her car leave in love with I don't think
so
don't even try it you're my brother I
know you burn anyone and I've never seen
you look at someone the way you look at
Marissa you're mistaken
she's not even my real girlfriend she's
my next-door neighbour not here to come
here why would you do that to get mom
off my back oh that's fun yeah well it
doesn't change the fact they're crazy
about her and she's crazy about you too
you know you're talking about she told
me to give you this
there you are
it's wondering where you ran off to I
can't talk right now who said anything
about talking right because you've done
just about enough of that haven't you
it's where the fuck do you get off on
telling Marisa what I said Oh Jake
didn't mean to of course you did you
exactly what you're doing you're
vindictive bitch you always have been
Wow just wow how dare you attack me when
you're so fucking pathetic you have to
pay some chick to go out with you
Marissa's not just some chick she's my
friend and I happen to be in love with
her I'm in love with her
I'm completely utterly in love again
congratulations I'm so happy for you
did you mean all that what are you doing
here I mean I thought you left
forgot my purse so did you every word do
you still think I'm an asshole
absolutely listen I'm really sorry I
mean it's just it shut up you should
have
let me get ya
Oh
fucking come
yeah
Oh
I
oh my god
because like the puppy stuff
yeah
ah
Oh
yeah
I think
me
yeah
so you forgive me
negotiation Oh what if I were slowest
you